You're bleeding through your bandage.
Good morning.
Don't we need to get you to a doctor?
I am a doctor.
That didn't come up last night?
We didn't do a lot of talking.
I'm good.
You never told me what caused your accident.
I was stabbed by a patient.
That'll teach me to overbill.
YOU HAVE A NEW TEXT MESSAGE
FROM HOUSE
DING DONG
If she likes crippled guys, I'm free for the next six minutes.
What do you want?
45-year-old truck driver, recurrent seizures.
No metabolic or structural... does this look like a good time?
Sort of.
At least as good as the other 12 times
that I've called and paged you in the last three weeks.
Those times I just didn't feel like talking to you.
Kinda like now.
I'd apologize again,
but I'm still waiting for you to accept the first one.
You do work for me.
I am entitled to ask when you're coming back.
I don't know when I'm coming back. I don't know if I'm coming back.
Got a problem with that,
fire me.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
豪斯医生  第八季第12集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：绿
Nice.
It's good to see you in the hospital, as a patient if not as a doctor.
Believe me,
I'd rather be the guy with the clipboard.
How you doing?
Arrhythmias are gone.
Fine motor control is improving.
Not what I meant.
If you need to talk to someone,
a professional...
I'm fine.
Fine enough to get back to work?
You don't have to work for House, but you do owe me 20 clinic hours.
What, getting knifed doesn't buy me an extension?
Buys you whatever you need. But I know you.
If all you do is physical therapy and your nighttime version of it,
you'll lose your mind faster than you regain those fine motor skills.
EXAM ROOM TWO
I, uh, have this terrible pain
in my left shoulder.
It came out of nowhere.
And nothing seems to help.
Any other symptoms?
Chest pain? Lightheadedness?
No. None at all.
What were you doing when the pain came on? Just sitting and praying.
She'd been helping to make the altar breads that morning,
but no hard physical work or repetitive motion.
A couple of possibilities.
You have enlarged lymph nodes, so I'd like to start by ruling out breast cancer.
And I do mean "rule out."
It's probably nothing.
I'm gonna do a quick breast exam.
Do you mind stepping out for a moment?
Not at all.
That was so I could ask about the second possibility.
Left-sided pain means it could be angina,
which is made worse by stress.
Might not be a coincidence that the pain started
on the verge of a major life change.
How did you know?
Blue Veil means you're a postulant, haven't taken your vows yet.
Brown Vestments means you're Carmelites,
cloistered nuns, which explains the chaperone.
You're about to withdraw from the world for good.
I was a seminarian.
Who obviously didn't take his vows.
Cassock made my ass look fat.
Do you mind unbuttoning your shirt and lying down for me?
Okay.
I have had second thoughts.
I'm kind of a wreck.
A life of perpetual enclosure and almost complete silence?
If you weren't wrestling with this, I'd say there's something really wrong with you.
I'm going to admit you.
There's a little mass here, and I'd like to get it checked out.
It's just a benign fat deposit. Her imaging's clean.
Stress test too. It's not angina.
So why the shoulder pain?
Is it possible that she hurt her shoulder?
- Thanks a lot. - I didn't tell him.
You were cagey about where you were going. And Chase being cagey in general.
Good chance I'd find the two of you in the same cage.
So I had Park follow you.
How you feeling?
Better.
Heard your arm's healing nicely.
Good to see you on your feet. Patient's a nun?
You turning back to your long-abandoned faith in time of trouble?
She was next up in the clinic. And I don't want your help.
You got stabbed.
You blame me.
But what did you learn about me that you hadn't known for years?
Maybe I was an idiot before and I'm not one now.
Or maybe the reverse is true.
Thanks for all your help.
Your soul sister is having a fungal infection
from the unprocessed wheat in the altar breads.
Explains the shoulder pain and the jumbo lymph nodes.
Thanks for all my help.
I'm... I'm sorry I led House to you.
It's part of the job.
Maybe we could get a meal after work tonight,
if you want some companionship.
You asking me out on a date?
No.
I just... I guess that sounded...
must be scary to be back.
All those knives and needles.
Infected blood and tissue everywhere you look.
Just thought you might need someone to talk to about it.
Just knowing you're there for me is enough.
Thanks.
Ever surf Kirra point?
Obviously you're Australian.
I've surfed all over the gold coast.
Don't tell me you have. The closest I got was Waimea Bay.
I grew up on Maui.
If you don't mind me asking, why are you becoming a nun?
You asking 'cause I surf?
Well, I know that Jesus walked on water but...
Plus the average postulant is a lot younger than you.
What were you doing before this? Not much of anything.
Worked as a nanny. Moved around a lot.
Bunch of failed relationships. And then what?
God spoke to you? You heard the calling?
Something like that.
Does there have to be some dramatic moment where the skies part?
Usually, yeah.
Is that what happened to you when you entered the seminary?
Mom drank, dad worked. They stuck me in catholic school.
Priests and nuns were the closest I had to family.
Turned out that wasn't much of a reason to join the priesthood.
Is that why you left?
Something like that.
I think I may throw up.
What's wrong with me?
Not a fungal infection.
You're probably wondering, why the soda balloons?
I'm not. Well, I'll tell you.
You're not the only one whose life spiraled out of control
when you got knifed in the ventricle. Taub has decided...
I need help with my patient. She's vomiting.
That's not from a fungal infection.
What are you planning to do now that you're not working for me?
I have no idea.
Almost dying's been clarifying. I can do anything.
You can do anything.
So you come back to the same building you've worked in for years.
Guess you can cross that off your bucket list.
Can we get to my patient sometime soon?
As soon as you admit that you're a confused mess, sure.
You'll help me.
'Cause even though you don't find my case interesting,
you find my interest in it interesting.
Well, when you put it that way...
Ascending colangitis.
Missed me. Can't be, bilirubin's normal.
Clinical signs can show up days
before lab signs.
This is great. We should make this a regular thing.
She can't feel her foot at all.
What does this mean?
It means I've got to spend more time consulting with a colleague.
17-ketosteroid levels are low.
How can he be hyper-sexual?
He tried to tongue-kiss Park when you were closer.
You think his sexuality is normal?
I need more help. My patient has a new symptom.
Ischemic foot.
Get the lecture out of your system so we can talk about my case.
Let me start with an allegory.
Okay, I'm curious.
Your overreaction to your stabbing
is to blame me even as you are drawn to me.
Taub's is to take moronic self-defense classes
that won't defend him against anything.
Krav Maga.
Which helped me block your shot and will continue to help me
defend myself in a building full of drugged-up strangers.
Taub has to accept that by instinct and genetics
he is a coward, who's better off running and hiding at the first sign of danger.
I've already fended off six of your blitzkriegs in a row.
And the seventh? And the eighth?
And the Nth?
If you get him, what's that gonna prove? That unexpected things happen.
By definition, no class can teach you to expect them.
Which is why Taub is idiotic to study them,
and you're idiotic to attach any significance to them.
Blood clot.
Her D-dimer's normal.
On the other hand...
What if he's right about the blockage but wrong about the cause?
Vasospasm.
That explains everything but the lymph nodes.
And any minor infection could have caused those. Calcium channel blocker to treat.
Are you okay? I almost got you killed by bringing a scalpel into that room.
I could feel better about that. You saved my life too.
I think the ledger's clear.
But how can you not be traumatized?
Can't change what happened.
Can only make better choices from here.
So you're zen about it but won't let go of your anger toward House?
I'm seeing a trauma counselor. I think you should too.
I'm okay.
Just knowing you're there for me is enough.
Convent lets you have this?
I borrowed it from one of the nurses.
I'm still on temporary vows.
It may be the last time I hear Eminem for a while.
You're using an iPod.
But I've never seen you use rosary beads.
What day did Jesus die?
I know, one gospel says passover,
another says the day before.
How many times did the cock crow before Peter's third denial?
Once or twice?
You can't argue away my faith.
Why?
Because it's so strong
even plain contradictions...
because it's not that strong.
I'm not saying I don't have faith.
I just haven't felt the calling yet.
No one joins the clergy without having that epiphany.
That God's love is speaking to you directly.
It's the silence, the contemplation,
the order. I need them.
Hoping everything else will come later.
That's not an answer.
If you want silence, you can get ear plugs.
I tried the outside world.
It wasn't enough. Have you been married?
No.
No kids. You never found a career.
Doesn't sound like the outside world got much of a try.
What you're headed towards now,
14 hours a day in silent prayer,
never having a family,
never touching another human being.
Just because that's what you'd miss the most.
The nurses talk.
Nothing's wrong with having fun.
They said you were almost killed three weeks ago.
You go right back to fun?
Is that why you wanna be a nun?
Someone broke your heart.
No.
I'm just looking for something more.
So am I.
I'm late for work in the clinic.
Really? George Washinbaum?
He was a character in the Flintsteins.
Just hiding out till House leaves the cafeteria.
The self-defense classes, you think they're making any kind of difference?
Not as much as House's surprise attacks.
He thinks three steps ahead, so I do too.
Which is why you should accept his apology and come back on the team.
He's annoying, he's maddening.
But he makes us all better.
Note to self.
Foot color's good.
Arterial pulse is good.
Capillary refill's good.
And her shoulder pain is all gone.
Looks like you're ready to go home.
I'll get the car and meet you out front.
I'd say I'm in the book,
but not the one you'll be reading from now on.
Six years ago, I was a nanny in Honolulu for this beautiful two-year-old boy.
I loved him.
Probably spent more time with him than his own parents.
One day I was in the park talking with another nanny.
He wandered out of the sandbox into the street,
into the path of a moving car.
That could have happened to anyone.
I don't think so.
And even if it did, they'd blame themselves for the rest of their lives too.
You shouldn't.
You shouldn't run from what can still be a good life.
I'm running to God.
After what happened to you, don't you wanna remake your life?
Not by hiding myself away.
I hope it works out for you.
It is gonna be hard.
Not touching anyone.
Who knew mother inferior was a smoking hottie.
No wonder you're playing handsies with her.
You think I'm hitting on a nun?
Angry at God or I just need a challenge?
Or you're terrified of intimacy,
which is why you're a serial slut.
But right now you're grasping at an emotional life raft.
Ideally someone for whom intimacy's not an option.
That actually makes sense, which I can't say about anything else you've been doing.
I'm not emotionally involved with her.
And much as I'd love to hear you contradict me,
I have a 7:30 appointment to explore my intimacy issues
at La Scala.
I'm talking to this agent. He's a bit of a sleaze.
But he's really excited about representing me.
Although he can't take on any new clients right now, he's trying to get mean audition
for one of those online soaps. Have you ever watched one of those?
Am I boring you?
Unfortunately, yeah.
Sorry.
You're not supposed to be here.
Or anywhere. Yeah.
You were right.
I was running away.
Oh, now you're shy.
It's brighter in the morning.
So are we gonna spend the rest of eternity
in a lake of fire while pointy-tailed demons
poke at us with sticks?
This is a little scary for me.
I had a whole life planned.
Not that I wasn't struggling with it.
And then I met you.
Don't worry, I know you're not the relationship type.
I'm not not the relationship type.
I was married once. Relax.
You're fine.
So what's next for you?
I have to find a place to live.
Get my old job back.
Sure, I'll feel guilty, start doubting.
As long as you keep dealing with your doubts
in the same way then...
Moira?
I'm sorry, did you say something?
Your neck. What?
Are your ears ringing?
Yeah. What does that mean?
We've got to get you back to the hospital right away.
The artery that's bringing blood to your brain,
it's coming apart. Means you could stroke.
I've paged a team of our best doctors. I don't have to cough as much.
It's clotted up.
Is that bad?
We're almost there.
Get me her O-two level.
What are you doing? I want to make sure I can position her wrist properly.
- For what? - A.B.G.
I don't need an A.B.G. Just get a pulse OX.
I'll do it. Grab a consent form.
Go!
We need to operate right now, okay?
Good to operate.
Repeat this, no ifs, ands, or buts about it.
No about it and no ifs.
Get her into O.R. 11.
Carotid dissection, four-inch pulsatile mass in her neck,
and some Broca's aphasia. It's got to be a clot
keeping her from bleeding out. Pulse?
Bounding, four-plus. It was a three-plus 20 minutes ago.
20?
Thought she just got here.
That blood looks pretty dry.
Cut yourself shaving?
You know, that can happen
when the nun you woke up with coughs blood on you.
You slept with a nun?
Forget nun, you slept with a patient? Former, to both.
Internal neck trauma, that's impressive.
It's happened to me a few times.
Up high.
Dr. Chase.
Clot's broken. Bring her in and pack her nose.
I'm gonna need number three Vicryls.
I'm gonna fix this. You're not gonna operate on her.
Kapur and Carlyle are unavailable. Reilly's done far fewer dissections than I have.
He's also slept with her far fewer times than you have.
Your judgment's compromised.
I spent the night with her.
Doesn't change how I make an incision.
Tell him!
Do the surgery.
You're trying to score points with him at the risk of a patient's life.
He's the better surgeon.
Vascular clamp. You're not gonna put her on bypass?
It'd take a half hour to set up. You clamp now, she could stroke out.
She's already got neurological symptoms.
We wait 30 minutes, she'll definitely have brain damage.
You're trying to make sure she's either perfect or dead.
She's not going to die. If I get this done in five minutes, she won't stroke out.
You don't know that you will.
And you can't know because you can't think clearly about her.
Vascular clamp.
Occlusion time 9:46 and 23 seconds.
Vascular scissors.
We're over five minutes.
Ultrasound.
Good flow. Lighten the anesthesia.
You're not gonna close the wound first?
No.
Can you hear me?
Repeat this,
no ifs, ands, or buts.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
I'm sorry about before.
You're scared, aren't you?
That's why you wanted companionship.
That's why you cried out when House shot at Taub.
What exactly are you scared of? A needle stick?
Some other nut pulling a scalpel?
I'm scared of everything.
It sucks that there was a stabbing. But you'll get over it.
Like you have? You weren't even there.
I know, I... I left the room.
It was pure luck.
I was in the room. That was pure luck too.
I get that you're scared and guilty.
You're still a doctor.
I don't have time to teach you to act like one.
We removed the artery.
I found nodules. Could mean lupus.
Negative A.N.A. Where are you going?
Great thing about assigning Taub fraudulent lab work is you know exactly
where he's gonna end up.
Great thing about assigning Taub obviously fraudulent lab work
is you get to watch his inner paranoiac at work.
And then...
Two to the head.
Can we talk about my patient? Quite a journey.
Starts with a surgical tool in your heart and ends with a surgeon's tool in a nun.
What's the plan? Plan's to cure her.
Well, if it's not meaningless sex, kinda screams out for an end game.
You're the dog that's chasing the popemobile. You sure you want...
Oh, my God.
Taub is interrogating the janitor.
He must think that I hired him to attack...
actually, why didn't I do that?
Plaques could be confused for nodules.
- Which would mean... - Syphilis.
Explains the shoulder and foot involvement.
Hope you practiced
the immaculate contraception.
Lock and load.
Boo-yah
Boo-yah to you too.
But I hadn't had sex in years.
Tertiary syphilis means you've had the disease for at least that long.
Does that mean you also have it?
Probably not contagious at this point.
Can it cause hallucinations?
It's unlikely. Why?
While I was on the operating table, it didn't feel like a dream.
I saw the boy who I was caring for.
The one who died.
He walked right up to me.
What did he say?
He just held my hand.
It was like he forgave me.
Do you think that's crazy?
I think it should give you solace,
help you to move on.
You slept with your patient?
You're off the case.
I saved her from brain damage.
You think my judgment's the least bit compromised?
She's still sick.
If she dies, we'll be in the middle of a brand-new investigation.
This is about you covering your own ass.
I gave you time, Leeway,
and you decided to do whatever the hell you wanted.
House can dance all over the rules, gets me knifed, and he gets a pass.
I break a rule, no one gets hurt,
but you kick me off my own case?
Unfortunately, yes.
I'm sorry. I took that scalpel for you.
That's why I did this.
Three weeks ago,
you never would have slept with a patient.
And you never would have operated on her after.
You need help.
I need to get away from House and everything that reminds me of him.
By breaking the rules, not caring what anyone else thinks.
You're gonna get away from him by turning into him?
It hurts.
Right upper quadrant, pain and distension.
What's wrong with my stomach?
Nothing. This is your liver.
The liver failure could be from intraoperative hypotension.
Checked the anesthesia sheet, pressure was fine throughout. Thrombus?
That voice in the hall that none of us
have any reason to be listening to is not surprisingly wrong.
Abdominal ultrasound was negative.
Then we have to assume liver failure
is just another symptom of whatever she's got.
Trousseau's syndrome could send clots, cause the ischemic foot.
Add the enlarged lymph node, macrocytosis.
Disseminated T-cell lymphoma. Wilson said it wasn't cancer.
Wilson says it's not breast cancer.
Sarcoidosis. Normal ace level.
Highly insensitive for sarcoid.
Negative chest X-rays aren't. Then we've got to biopsy.
Yeah, Foreman's clearly wrong.
You're clearly not grasping at straws
'cause you're clearly not emotionally involved.
I know you want to believe that this is something we can cure.
It's not. I'm sorry.
How soon will they know if it's cancer?
Within hours.
And if it is?
There's always chemo.
You say that like it's not gonna work.
Could extend your life.
Years?
I'll be here as much as you need.
You still never told me why you left the seminary.
Mary Knoller.
Wife of the groundskeeper.
He caught me with her, got me with a rake.
Those scars on my ass you may have noticed.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
Because it was so shallow.
I wasn't exactly wrestling with great theological questions.
I don't believe that.
You don't sleep with the groundskeeper's wife,
not unless you're struggling with whether you belong there.
I always wanted to believe.
Would have made my life a lot easier.
It never took.
Doesn't...
Mean...
It's too late.
Are you having trouble talking, like before?
I can get the words out. Just feels heavy when I do.
Where?
Wherever my chewing muscles are.
I'll be right back.
House finally got you.
- He tried but... - I gotta go.
You shoulda seen it. It was perfect.
She has jaw claudication.
If you only heard claudication and carotid dissection...
I'd say giant cell arteritis.
And I'd tell your former teammates to put her on steroids.
She's gonna live.
Yeah.
And then what?
They say my liver function's better. That I can get out of here soon.
And when you do, I'm gonna take you to puerto escondido.
Mexico? The Mexican pipeline.
Early may is when the surf really picks up but...
what's wrong?
I spoke to the prioress.
You're going back?
I felt the calling. When you saw the boy.
I felt God's love, his grace.
I've been waiting my entire life for that. It's not real.
I know you didn't feel anything when you almost died.
I did. You felt oxygen depravation.
You felt your brain releasing noradrenaline.
You didn't say that before.
I wanted you to move on with your life.
I wanted to reassure you.
I wanted you to feel better.
And now you don't?
Now...
I think I love you.
"Noradrenaline and near-death experiences."
Oh, dear.
You saw God? She did.
She wants to go back to the monastery.
So now you're preparing a Powerpoint presentation
to keep her in your garden  of earthly delights. You're an idiot.
Because I found someone I love? Because you're an idiot.
At least you two have that in common.
Her feelings are based on a chemical process.
They're gonna wear off. You just slept with her.
Your brain is exploding with oxytocin.
You think that's gonna last through the ages?
She's throwing away her life because of blind faith.
So are you!
She's found something she wants to build her life around.
It's a total illusion, but apparently she'll take a little ignorance with her bliss.
And you want to take that away?
How many times have you thrown the truth in people's faces?
Because it's the truth, not because we're gonna live happily ever after.
Either your relationship just blows up
like every other non-magical romance,
or she stays with you but blames you for stripping all the meaning out of her life.
This has nothing to do with the truth.
You don't like that I'm reassessing my life,
that I want to change it, that I can.
Anyone can screw up a life. I never said that wasn't possible.
You're incapable of human connection,
so you want everyone to be like you.
If I wanted you to be like me...
I would be urging you to make a stupid, stubborn decision
that blows up your life and leaves you lonely and miserable.
You reassess your life when you've made mistakes.
You didn't. You just got stabbed.
Don't look at the book.
I haven't done a jugular line since my residency. I don't want to needle the carotid.
What's the first step?
Palpate the S.C.M.
Where?
Middle third of the neck.
I'm happy I knew you.
So am I.
Robert.
24-year-oldwater treatment worker with pyrexia and double vision.
Abscess?
Would have seen it on the MRI.
Diphtheria paralyzing the ocular muscles? No, paralysis was first.
- Aneurysm? - Not with this fever.
Maybe we're thinking about this the wrong way. Retro-ocular infection?
With no local symptoms?
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入