"The Patuxent River Naval Air Station near D.C.
Was commissioned in 1943 by John McCain's grandfather."
I'm thinking of going hang gliding.
Pax river is, like, completely flat.
Think that's why they tested the V-22 Osprey there.
I like naval stuff. I like their oranges and lint.
What looks like kidney disease, but isn't?
And where's Chase? Root canal and Berger's.
The first one was regarding Chase. Root canal, if done correctly,
doesn't look like kidney disease.
Got a case for you. Smells funny.
Patient had an idiopathic anaphylactic reaction.
It stumped two E.R. docs and an immunologist from Johns Hopkins.
Patient went from asymptomatic to fried kidneys in less than a year.
Stumped three internists and a department chair from Harvard.
14-year-old girl, intermittent attacks.
Four-year-old boy, consistently at death's door.
This patient died five years ago.
I didn't say which side of the door he was on.
The fact that he's dead makes it more interesting.
Four-year-olds do not die of Berger's.
I thought it was relevant. Death is a consequence, not a symptom.
If it's not a symptom, it's not relevant.
Shouldn't we be trying to maximize what we can save here?
14-year-old, your freom, our asses?
Right... Save your asses.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
豪斯医生 第八季第7集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：荒川小白脸
She was in a car accident when she was two.
She only had minor injuries, but her father died.
That was 12 years ago. You think that's pertinent?
No, I think it's sad.
She got sick in the middle of her 14th birthday party.
Which is sad and pertinent.
Maybe she was opening a present that triggered the reaction.
- Where's House? - Pissing contest with foreman.
Last thing she ate was strawberry cake,
but allergy tests for everything were negative.
Do you like your dentist? I'm still going to my pediatric one.
What's your dentist's name?
Williams. What if it's not an allergic reaction?
Hereditary angioedema or systemic mastocytosis could mimic anaphylaxis.
You're not sure of his name?
You just saw him this morning.
His assistant's name is Angie. Her home number is...
Normal complement studies. No skin leons.
You had a manicure.
This is fresh! You weren't at the dentist.
Why would you lie about that? To avoid having this conversation.
- Elevated BP. - What about pheochromocytoma?
Or an anaphylactoid reaction, which could be triggered by certain opioids.
You've had your hair cut three times since I've met you.
You can't be embarrassed about a manicure. There's gotta be a deeper reason.
Did House give you homework? She's not on any meds.
Haven't you heard? Everybody lies.
And the tox screen was clean.
Feel free to jump in at any time.
We'll check catecholamines for pheo and run an expanded opioid panel.
You see what the patient says about drug use when her mother's out of the room.
No, never. Nobody's here to bust you, iris.
We just need to know if... No, I already told you.
I just take vitamin C sometimes.
What exactly were you doing when you had your reaction?
Opening a birthday present. The magic 8 ball.
The joke gift, not the cocaine. Is that it?
Certain drugs could explain her reaction.
What kind of drugs? What kind did you have in mind?
Iris has always been a moody girl.
And now that she's a teenager, it's gotten worse.
So for the past few months I've been...
Giving something to relax her.
Diazepam. I tell her it's vitamin c.
Being normal is very important to iris.
She couldn't handle the thought of being on meds.
Anti-anxiety medications would explain it.
If we keep her off,
she'll be moody, but healthy.
Or it's something else.
James Wilson.M.D.
I need to DDX a patient with you. I thought you had a team for that.
According to foreman, they're only for DDXing people
who are still alive.
You have a dead patient?
Bigotry is boring when we add modifiers.
I don't see creed, LOR, pulse.
Foreman will find out you're taking this case,
and he'll bust you.
But you know that,
which means...
You want to go back to jail...
Because it's the one place you're unable to iulge your self-destructive habits.
Yeah, it's much more likely that I'm taking this case because I miss showering with cro-magnons
than that I actually happen to find it interesting.
Four-year-old kid.
His kidneys died, they transfused.
His lungs died. He died.
Have you seen bride of the monster? I just got the ed wood box set.
What if the chicken was the egg?
What if the lung involvement came first?
I don't really care about the movie.
I just don't want to indulge your...
Lupus.
Because this is a bad idea, House.
If the kid had a rash or some circulation issue...
Damn!
I just realized I'm late for my anger management class.
Traffic, for sure. Taxes. Definitely taxes.
Spoiled grandchildren. Platitudes.
Any others? And I lose my temper when someone suggests
that a handful of pop-psych catch phrases can control our most seminal,
intractable, and natural reacon to a dead child.
Am I right, Emory?
I don't think Emory wants to share right now.
They blew it, didn't they? They missed your son's rash.
A faint one, on his cheek.
He didn't have a rash.
I think we should talk about Lena's grandchildren.
They're alive.
Was he sensitive to sunlight? No.
Greg... Cold fingers and toes?
No!
Wegener's granulomatosis.
I need to examine your son.
You're a bit late for that... You ass.
With you and your wife's consent,
we can get an exhumation order.
Find out what killed him.
Ex-wife.
And you'll never get her consent.
She's moved on... New hub, new kid.
She wants nothing to do with drew's death.
Or me.
You're angry because your kid died.
More than that,
because you don't have an answer.
People need answers.
He's in a crypt at St. Jude's Cemetery.
You feeling any pain or cramping here?
A bit.
But not just there, um...
Here. Breast tenderness.
Have you been having regular periods, iris?
Not really.
What is it?
I think we should run a pregnancy test.
Iris isn't sexually active. She doesn't even have a boyfriend.
Pregnancy would explain all of her symptoms.
Can even cause some unpredictable allergic reactions.
How can I be pregnant if I've never even had sex?
We just need a drop of blood.
What's the matter?
My...
My arms.
I can't feel my arms.
At this rate,
I'm gonna need to pick out a plot for myself.
Thanks to your generous donation, you have all morning.
More like 13 minutes.
Before we proceed any further, doctor,
I'd like inquire as to exactly what procedure
you intend to perform on the remains.
Have you ever heard of the north American man/dead boy love association?
I consider these grounds to be a holy place,
and I would ask you to observe them with due decorum.
So you're taking bribes to plunder graves, and I need to show respect.
I think they got the cause of death wrong.
And if I find a hole in the cartilage of his nose,
right about here,
then it means I'm right.
Please be respectful.
I prepared the sarcophagus for you.
Thank you, Igor.
It's Milton.
You owe me a new pair of pants.
- She is pregnant. - Test came back positive.
So... She lost the use of her arms
and her innocence. A vengeful God?
Or...
Cerebral tumor. Vasculitis.
Ms.
I gather from the silence that Chase isn't there.
Nope, I'm here.
Where are you?
"Nowhere"... He said cryptically.
I assume you concur with the diagnosis.
Absolutely.
Even tugh there are three diagnoses?
And ms and vasculitis
usually get better with pregnancy.
Yeah, I was saying I agreed with the other one.
He's had his eyebrows waxed.
I met a woman
who likes her men well groomed.
All over?
I assume, from the silence,
that Chase has had a brazilian.
Cool. Interesting. Ouch.
Question is... Is this really about a woman?
Or is it about something more profound?
Another question is, could the paresthesia be caused by an std?
HIV-related mononeuritis multiplex.
I gatherrom the silence
that either you all agree with Chase
or you're just staring at his emasculated brow.
In either case, test for HIV and do an MRI to rule out tumors.
And check Chase for testosterone.
Blood work was negative for HIV.
All the money's on tumor.
How was the brazilian? It was fine. Hurt a bit.
What about House's theory? Why'd you really do it?
'Cause I'm vain and shallow.
And you weren't before?
The girl I was seeing wasn't.
There's nothing profound here.
No tumor, either. It's not her brain.
Everything looks good.
What's the matter?
My arm, it's...
Still nothing?
No, now they're sore.
Paresthesia's gone.
Could the bruising be caused by a physical trauma?
You think she fell out of bed, repeatedly?
A blood disorder. Maybe thrombocytopenia.
A vitamin K deficiency or scurvy could explain bleeding problems,
and prnancy could exacerbate it.
Boys, do a home search. Girls, do lab tests.
I'm pretty sure that's not sexist.
Where have you been?
Picking up dry cleaning.
Filling up the tank. Violating the dead.
If you don't believe me, call the monitoring company. I did.
Unfortunately, the Patuxent River Naval Air Station
was GPS testing and disrupted the signal,
at the exact, same 45 minutes you weren't here.
Well, if I'd known I had 45 minutes of freedom,
I'd have gone hang gliding.
I admire the creativity.
What happens when the stunt doesn't work?
Think you're gonna have to pay off a bet?
Think I'm gonna triple your clinic hours?
I'm gonna call your P.O.,
and you're gonna go back to jail.
There are mees' lines on his fingernails, so now I'm thinking heavy metal poisoning.
You're an addict.
And I'm an idiot for thinking that your addictions
were limited to pills, anti-social behavior, and sarcasm.
Sorry.
Vicodin repeating on me.
You're also addicted to puzzles.
You show all the classibehaviors.
Lying, neglecting responsibilities, and you can't stop,
no matr how devastating the consequences.
Working on a medical case is not a parole violation.
It's my job description.
Your job description is doing what foreman tells you to do.
Never mind bride of the monster. You need to watch Norma rae.
Before we get started, I just want to thank you all for agreeing to relocate.
Um, I had an appointment in this part of town,
and I absolutely didn't want to miss this meeting.
But, uh, thank you.
I'm buying.
Not literally.
Hey, Emory, should we, uh, powder our noses?
Hey, did you know your ex-wife still lives right behind this place?
She finishes work at 4:00.
Picks up her new kid at 4:15.
Gives us about 20 minutes.
I made some calls.
It's amazing what people will tell you if you ask brutally enough.
Was that table here?
Some kinds of pressure-treated wood can contain arsenic.
We shouldn't be here. We don't have a choice.
This is the only way you're gonna get your answer.
Does your ex leave a spare key anywhere?
How did he look?
Peaceful.
Vitamin k deficiency's a bust. Fridge has more spinach and broccoli than a farmer's market.
The brazilian...
You said it hurt "a bit."
You've had one? More than one, and you haven't.
They hurt all your bits. That's my dark secret.
What's yours?
I had the nails and eyebrows done, but that's it.
I just needed to create a distraction, though.
I met a TV producer at a dinner.
She asked me to appear on the medical segment.
Screen tested it yesterday and shot it today.
You're a TV doctor?
It's a one-off. When's it air?
Two hours ago. Otherwise, I'd still be lying.
This is what she was opening
when she had her attack.
Will anyone believe Chase is an actual doctor?
"Don't count on it."
She does have a boyfriend. Love letters.
Porn. The nasty kind.
Torture, rape... Animals.
Sweet kid.
This is all that's left.
One box in the bottom of a closet.
He used to wear those stupid things all the time.
Used to have to pretend I was scared.
Made in the people's Republic of Lead Paint.
Back door.
Let's get out of here first. We need to catch the end of our class.
I met him at school.
He was the only boy that liked me.
It's a little more than like.
We haven't had sex.
Oh, come on, iris. You're pregnant.
So I'm just lying about everything? Well, you lied about the boyfriend.
You obviously lied about sex
and this... Garbage.
They're his.
He can't keep them at his place.
Well, I'm glad we could be so accommodating.
What else don't I know?
Honey...
What is it?
He came here last night.
And he told me I should leave.
But I didn't want to, and he got mad.
He hit you? Physical trauma.?????
We should call the police.
I won't tell them anything.
That's ridiculous. He beat you!
What is it? It's getting hard to see.
What the hell is happening to me?
Rubbing alcohol, vinegar.
Not sure what this is. Aren't there actual medical tests?
Dead patients usually get a lower standard of care.
Pink means lead.
Orange means Mercury.
And rust means arsenic.
And what's brown mean? Scotch.
He used to call him "deezer."
He couldn't say "zebra."
He'd have his own words for everything.
We called 'em "drewisms."
How does your ex-wife do it?
How come she's not... Angry and miserable?
She treated it like it never happened.
She never even cried.
Not even at his funeral.
I was a mess,
and she just sat there like...
A statue.
We have a problem. Does it limp?
Why do you care if he works on two cases?
'Cause next, it'll be three cases, then four.
Then animal cases and ghost cases.
Then animal ghost cases. Assuming, of course, we are talking about House.
You're just setting yourself up to fail.
He has a lot more to lose than I do, and he knows that.
He's rational.
No, he's not.
He's the most rational man I've ever met. Annoyingly so.
He isn't gonna put himself back in jail over a dead kid.
He's an addict, and he will put himself back in jail over a puzzle.
He'll back down.
Halfway through the perimetry exam, her tunnel vision went away.
She can see perfectly. TIA.
The word "transient" is right there in the name.
Ah, here we go.
Chesa, after giving the pics an eye or two,
I can confirm that Lauren's surgeries cost her some big bikkies.
Not only was there a gut tuck, nose tuck, and arse tuck,
but her new, fake norks stick out like nuts on a mutt.
The original script was...
Shh, shh, shh. Anyone notice...
He's enlightening us.
That's 'cause he's retooled the ol' todger.
Let's just hope no one cut the wrong wire, eh?
So you just wanted to look pretty on TV.
Question is, why did he want that?
Clinic time.
What do you want us to do?
MRA 4 TIA. ROFL.
Thought you only had clinic on Tuesdays.
Oh, you're right.
Hi. I'm here for the free flu shot.
I got a call saying...
I'm here to find out why you didn't care about your first kid.
Losing a child... Just breezed right through it.
How do you know about my first kid...
Didn't even squeeze out a single tear at the funeral.
Where are you getting this?
You couldn't wait to squeeze out a brand-new replacement kid.
Damn it.
You had no right to say that.
I know. I deserved the slap.
But I was hoping that you weren't capable of it.
Apathetic hyperthyroidism.
Could have kidney involvement. Could be genetic.
Definitely causes apathy.
I was hoping that your lack of emotion
was a symptom of something you could have passed on to your first son.
You know Emory. We belong to the same club.
He wants to relive this. I don't.
So I heard.
Emory was a wonderful man.
Never afraid to show his emotions.
Which is great, most of the time.
But when drew died...
It overwhelmed him.
I vowed I wouldn't let that happen to me.
That's why you left him? I left because of his eyes.
He had drew's eyes.
Who used to babysit drew?
My father, but...
His place or yours?
There are two types of people.
Those who can move on, and those who can't.
My father keeps up a good front, but he's just like Emory.
You need to leave him alone.
So he has two types of people inside of him.
Mra was normal.
Yeah, how did...
I found out where your boyfriend lives.
When I paid him a visit, he took off.
Ran in front of a car.
You're lying.
He's down in the E.R. right now.
Shut up, you lying sack of crap.
Iris!
How do you know I'm lying?
How do you know your boyfriend's okay?
'Cause I'm right here, you dick.
Iris has dissociative identity disorder.
Also known as multiple personality disorder.
Are you saying I'm crazy?
It's the mind's response to a severe trauma.
A person experiences something that's too difficult to accept,
so they create alternate personalities that don't have to accept it.
Some think it's quite a natural reaction.
Iris hasn't had any severe traumas.
The car accident?
I was two.
I don't remember anything.
These personalities that I'm supposed to have...
Where are they?
They only come out when you're afraid or anxious.
That's why House used the hurt boyfriend story.
But if there's no boyfriend, where did the bruises come from?
The pregnancy?
When you say your boyfriend hit you,
it means you actually hit yourself.
And the pregnancy...
Doesn't take a boyfriend.
Just a boy.
You may not be aware of half the things you've done.
How could this be happening
to my own daughter without me knowing it?
Diazepam was masking it.
Taking her off made it more apparent.
But I... I wasn't on... "Diazepam"?
What is that?
That's what those vitamin pills were.
Iris... I am so sorry.
I just... I thought you were moody.
I didn't want you to think you needed medication.
Oh, my God. I n't believe how stupid I've been.
We need you to help us with something.
Different alters can he different apparent symptoms.
Allergies, paresthesia, vision loss,
changes in blood pressure. Do you think I'm making this up?
Your symptoms are real. But some are physiological,
and others are psychological.
So there's something wrong with her...
In addition to the multiple personalities?
Yes, but we won't know what
until we access her alters and compare their symptoms.
Well, how do you do that?
Hypnosis.
Foreman's nogonna back down.
He's not an idiot. Yes, he is.
Just like you. If you keep being stubborn,
he will keep being stubborn. Eventually, you will screw something up.
Which will be bad news for both of you.
But... Only one of you will be in prison.
It just isn't worth it, House.
Okay.
Uh, y-yes, sir.
I... yes, I know I told you that I had a chiropractor's appointment,
but, uh, I got a flat.
I know, right?
So...
You know, don't send out the marines.
I should be back on the road in a few minutes.
Okaybye.
Dr. James Wilson, county coroner.
I'd like to ask you about your grandson, drew lemaine.
What did he do when he was here? Where did he play? What did he eat?
We watched lot of TV.
And ate biscuits.
Did you give him sidewalk chalk? No.
Finger paints? No!
A sandbox? It's like I said.
We watched a lotta TV.
You expecting someone?
What?
Dr. Wilson my ass!
I told you to leave him alone, you son of a bitch!
Temper trigger.
Who am I talking to now?
Nobody.
You must be somebody.
I'm too little.
Nobody sees me.
Nobody knows I'm here.
BP just went to 140 over 90.
What is it? My arms.
You can't feel them?
It's okay. We can fix that.
Do you hurt anywhere else?
Not right now.
But you used to hurt?
When I ate strawberries.
And when I remember...
Do you remember being hurt?
I remember everything.
Baby...
It's going to be okay, baby.
Iris? Why didn't you ever tell me?
It was my fault daddy died.
Oh, no. No. Yes, it was.
I was crying and he couldn't drive. It was my fault daddy's...
Oh, no. No, no, honey.
Yes. You were just a baby.
It wasn't your fault. No, shh.
Oh, baby.
It was my fault.
I'm sorry, mommy.
I'm so sorry.
It wasn't a miscarriage. Test shows she's still pregnant.
Okay, cross out everything that doesn't appear in every alter.
When she opened the magic 8 ball, that triggered a switch to a personality with a strawberry allergy.
Pregnancy, vaginal bleeding, and elevated b.P. Could be pre-eclampsia.
Worst case, could be an ectopic pregnancy.
We need to ultrasound.
Not seeing an embryo in the fallopian tube.
I'm not seeing an embryo anywhere.
Which idiot did the egnancy test?
I did one of them. Chase did another.
Taub did a third. Three tests, three positives.
What happened to your eye?
I grabbed park's ass.
Exoplanets.
I think he said exoplanets. Wait for it...
We can't actually see them...
But we infer their existence because of the effect they have on the star they orbit.
Pregnancy test only infers an embryo's existence
because of elevated hcg levels.
Which could also be caused by choriocarcinoma, which affects the placenta,
mimics pregnancy, and causes elevated BP and vaginal bleeding.
Occult choriocarcinoma, which is why we didn't see it on the ultrasound
tell all the alters that they have cancer.
Mom or dad?
Mom, dad, and mom's dad.
The good news is,
made me realize that you were right.
I can't drop it.
But now that I accept that, I feel much less conflicted.
I've ruled out wegener's, Berger's, heavy metal poison...
Two trains are about to collide,
and I'm trying to talk them out of it.
Feels like I'm missing something.
No, no.
You don't want to listen to me,
then I don't want to listen to you.
That is so fifth grade. I agree. And you know why?
Because I'm just as bad as you. I knew ts would fall on deaf ears,
but I just kept talking and talking.
You're right.
You don't even know what I just said.
That is ridiculous.
You said, "blah blah blah blah blah, deaf ears, blah blah blah blah blah."
Absolutely essential information.
Ray...
Ray!
Leave him alone.
What are you doing to him?
It's okay.
Mickey...
You? You brought him. I asked him to meet me here for a family reunion.
Ray!
Let's just get out of here, okay?
I know what killed your son.
You don't get it, do you?
I don't care what killed him!
It's called alport syndrome.
It's a genetic condition
characterized by kidney failure,
?????bronchial myomas, mees' lines,
and deafness.
Idiot. Drew wasn't deaf!
House... Son of a bitch!
Get away from them!
House, House!
It's a genetic condition!
Shut up! Genetic!
Your father has the gene. So do you.
It's grandpa's slight deafness that gave the game away.
You're apparently asymptomatic.
You could still pass the gene onto your children.
Plural.
You're lying.
He has high-frequency hearing impairment.
And so did drew.
That's why drew made up his own words.
'Cause he couldn't hear properly.
It's okay. Now that we know what it is,
he'll need treatment, but he'll live.
You know, there are platitudes that can help you with that.
I miss him too.
She's responding well.
Cuddy threatened him with clinic duty.
I thought threatening him with jail would be different.
Not an irrational thought.
I'm still sending him back.
He saved two lives.
Which means it's too late for me to back down.
It's no longer my choice.
It's just me telling him he can get away with anything.
I have to send him to prison.
Your job is to keep this machine running.
It's your choice to make House a useful tool or a monkey wrench.
Cuddy's way didn't fail because she didn't try to control House.
She managed him.
She knew better than anybody what a tool he could be.
What would Cuddy have done?
Ten clinic hours.
Cuddy's not here anymore.
You got 30.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入