Any problems getting the canisters out?
No. They were hidden exactly where you said they'd be.
Russians will finally understand the consequences
of occupying our homeland when we turn Moscow into a graveyard.
Erwich has just cleared airport security.
Then the authorities don't know anything's been stolen.
Not yet.
Then the only thing we have left to take care of is Bauer.
You paged me?
I need you to do something.
We have our hands full searching for the nerve gas.
Bauer is a priority.
I just signed a treaty.
Now all of a sudden
I find out that the terrorists
are still out there... with nerve gas.
You people have to listen to me.
I had a document.
It was hidden in my blouse.
It's gone.
Someone stole it from me.
This is what she was like before you sent her to Vermont.
Are you suggesting that I readmit her?
For her sake,
if nothing else.
Aaron, my wife is gone.
We have a priority alert.
You've been burrowing into classified CTU protocols without authorization.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Stop.
I know you logged on to the security subsystem
where you had no right to be.
Someone knew that Jack was alive.
It's critical to our investigation
that we find out who that was.
Did you let that man into CTU?
This man is a professional assassin.
He just killed Dr. Paulson, he tried to kill me.
Who told you to let that man into CTU?
The White House.
Mr. Cummings.
The following takes place between 12Pm and 1Pm
I don't understand the problem.
David Palmer was murdered because he was about
to expose Walt Cummings' connection to the terrorists.
When Cummings failed to frame me for Palmer's murder,
he tried to kill me.
All that may be true, Jack
but we don't have proof.
We can prove that Cummings used
Spenser to get Jack's assassin into CTU.
All we have is Spenser's word.
That's not enough to build a case.
You don't have time to build a case.
You want the nerve gas,
Cummings is your connection.
Cummings is the President's Chief Advisor.
How exactly do you suggest we get to him?
I can secretly meet with Mike Novick
enlist his help.
How do we know Novick's not in this with Cummings?
Because I know him.
He'll listen to me.
And the President will listen to him.
With Novick's help, we can isolate Cummings.
Jack, as much as I appreciate you wanting to be involved
you don't work here anymore.
That's exactly the reason why I should do this.
If it backfires, there'll be no fallout on you.
I think it's worth a try.
I agree.
It's your call.
All right, Jack.
But just so we're clear,
this is about finding the nerve gas,
not getting revenge for David Palmer.
Understood.
Work out your protocols with Ms. Raines.
We'll keep looking through Cummings' background
for anything that supports our case.
We're gonna need to set up a secure channel
for you to contact us on.
Can you bring up the satellite photo of the compound?
Jack, I'm sorry if I'm being a little distant.I just...
It's taking me a little while to get used to you being alive.
I understand.
I'll call Novick.
Jack.
When Cummings finds out that you're still alive,
he's gonna come after you again.
Yeah.
Yes?
Is Bauer dead?
I haven't received confirmation yet.
Your man should have taken care of this by now.
Perhaps he had to alter his strike window.
Has the nerve gas reached the port?
Not yet.
But they should be arriving any minute.
Good.
I have to go.
I'm late for a briefing.
You have all the shipping documents in order?
The canisters will arrive at port
in your country in eight days.
Ground transportation to your base camp will take another day.
Will you need my help getting them to your target?
No.
I've arranged transport to Moscow.
Have they found my wife yet?
No, sir,
but Secret Service is confident
she's still on the grounds.
If they're so damn confident,
why can't anyone find her?
What the hell are they doing?
I'm sure it's just a matter of time
Mr. President.
Sorry I'm late.
I was just setting up the video.
This was made by terrorists,
to document the effects of exposure to nerve gas.
It was recovered from a training camp two years ago.
Disorientation occurs moments after exposure.
Now the video jumps forward
no more than a couple of minutes, we estimate.
Within that time,
there's permanent damage to the central nervous system.
Violent seizures take over.
Bronchial membranes blister and peel away.
Death occurs within...
Stop.
Now, according to DOD,
the Sentox-Six nerve gas stolen from the airport
is far more lethal than the gas we just saw used.
If released in a town or city, for example,
the cloud will remain lethal for much longer.
Are we any closer to finding the canisters?
There haven't been any reports of progress, sir.
Excuse me, Mr. President.
I need to return a call to the State Department.
Do you have those updates, Walt?
Yes, here's one from CTU.
Also one from Homeland Security.
This is Bauer.
Jack. Mike Novick.
It's good to hear your voice.
Yours, too, Mike.
I'm so sorry about David Palmer.
I know how much he meant to you.
Yeah...
What's going on?
I have a lead on the stolen nerve gas.
Isn't CTU coordinating the search?
This is something I need to bring directly to you.
I don't understand.
I can't talk about it on the phone, Mike.
We need to meet.
No one can know about this, not even the President.
I'm not comfortable with all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me some idea what this is about.
It concerns Walt Cummings.
There's an area
a few hundred yards outside the southwest gate.
It's at the far side of the property from the main house.
Thanks, Mike.
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
Jack...
Hey.
They said we can leave soon.
I know, I heard.
What about you?
Are you coming home with us?
No, I need to stay here.
CTU still needs my help.
Derek, I'd like to speak with your mom for a moment
is that all right?
Yeah, of course.
Take him downstairs.
She'll be there soon.
You're not coming back to us at all, are you?
No.
I never thought I was going to be back here at CTU.
I would never have gotten you involved
in all of this, I promise you.
It's the woman who interviewed me, isn't it? Audrey Raines.
You were involved with her.
I could tell by the way you looked at each other.
I was with her before I had to disappear.
Are you still in love with her?
Yes.
Does she still love you?
I don't know.
Mr. Bauer.
Your transportation's standing by.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Thank you.
I'm not comfortable with all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me some idea what this is about.
It concerns Walt Cummings.
There's an area,
a few hundred yards outside the southwest gate.
It's at the far side of the property from the main house.
Your man didn't do his job.
Don't put that on me, Nathanson.
You were supposed to have Bauer killed hours ago.
I'm not going to warn you again.
Pull yourself together.
You heard the call, didn't you?
Bauer's coming here to expose my role in all this.
You're assuming he knows the extent of it.
Well, it's obvious he knows enough.
Now, what the hell am I supposed to do?
At this point
there's only one thing you can do.
Mrs. Logan,
please come out of there.
Mrs. Logan...
Aaron...
don't let them take me.
You've got to listen to me.
They're just trying to help you.
No.
They're trying to set me up.
They're trying to make it look like I had a breakdown
so they can cart me off to some psychiatric hospital.
Ma'am...
Aaron...
It's someone in my husband's administration.
They're trying to shut me up
because I know the truth.
What truth?
David Palmer.
I know...
Don't let him take me, Aaron. Please?
We have our orders, Mrs. Logan.
I'm sorry.
Aaron... please...
Aaron...
Audrey
did you check with the airports?
Yes. They've all been alerted on the missing canisters.
And CHP?
Same thing.
Trucks are being checked at all major interstates.
Make sure there's no mention of the Sentox nerve gas.
The White House is clear about that.
Yes, I know.
The bulletin only describes the missing canisters.
There's no mention of chemical weapons.
Good.
The last thing we need is for the public
to find out that nerve gas is out there.
Schaeffer...
...what were you doing in there?
Making sure the canisters were secured properly.
Don't want them knocking around
when this gets loaded onto a ship.
My men secured the canisters according to my instructions.
You don't need to be concerned.
All right.
Here are the customs documents you need
when the shipment arrives,
along with the remote trigger
and the arming codes.
I'll take the rest of my payment now.
Our arrangement was you'll get your final installment
when the ship left port.
There's not gonna be a problem.
They're loading out in less than an hour.
Then you won't have long to wait.
Fine.
Ms. Raines?
Yes.
We've been released.
Oh, good.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Do you still have feelings for Jack?
I'm sorry, but that's personal.
I know, but he's been living with my son and me for the last six months.
We started to become a family...
...and I care about him.
Do you know he still loves you?
If you don't love him, let him go.
Bauer.
Jack, it's Audrey.
What's going on?
Jack...
What?
Audrey, what?
When this is over,
are you coming back?
I don't know.
Are you going back to Diane?
No...
I don't know what I'm doing yet.
I haven't had any time to think about it.
Is it true what she said?
What'd she say?
That you still love me.
I never stopped loving you...
not for one second.
Then don't go away again, Jack, please.
It's more complicated than that.
I know.
It's time.
I gotta go.
Jack...
I have to go.
Yeah, I know, I know. Okay. Bye.
No, no!
Keep me out of this!
The last thing I want to do is comment to the press
about the roadblocks going up.
And we can't have any leaks about the nerve gas.
It would just cause a panic.
Come in.
Pardon me, sir.
We found Mrs. Logan.
Is she all right?
She's fine, sir.
She was hiding in the stables.
Stables? What the hell
did she think she was doing?
Mr. President...
I feel awkward mentioning this, but...
Mrs. Logan said some things...
About David Palmer.
Yes, sir.
I've heard her conspiracy theories, Aaron.
I've heard them all.
But thank you for your concern, Aaron.
They found my wife.
Good.
Mr. President...
we need to talk.
What is it, Walt?
I was hoping to spare you from this
but I'm afraid Jack Bauer is forcing my hand.
He's on his way here to meet with Mike Novick.
Bauer? Why?
He's going to accuse me
of helping the terrorists acquire the nerve gas.
That's ridiculous.
No, sir.
It's the truth.
What did you say?
Through a proxy, I leaked
information to the terrorists
about where the nerve gas was hidden.
You have to understand, sir,
this gas was never going
to pose a threat to American lives.
Never pose a threat?!
People died in the airport!
Hostages were killed!
We had hoped to limit the collateral damage.
"Collateral damage"?!
What are you thinking?
This is an unspeakable crime.
Walt... you have to answer for this.
Mr. President...
it's in your best interest to hear me out
before you make that phone call.
What do you mean
"my best interest"?
Sentox gas is being smuggled out of the country
by separatists who think they are going to use it
against the Russians.
However, that nerve gas will never reach Russian soil.
And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators on those
gas canisters.
As soon as they reach the terrorists' base,
we'll trigger the canisters by satellite
and release the gas.
So everything that happened today
was just to kill a some terrorists?
No, the goal is to produce a smoking gun,
proof of the existence
of weapons of mass destruction in Central Asia.
This is unbelievable.
It's necessary.
It will finally give us a pretext
to increase our military presence in the region,
guaranteeing the flow of oil for the next generation.
How dare you.
How dare you act without my consent.
How dare you put this administration
this entire country in jeopardy.
You're a traitor.
No, no,
Mr. President,
I am a patriot!
Doing what needs to be done
for the continued safety and well-being of this nation!
My God...
you gave the order to have David Palmer killed.
That was an unfortunate
but necessary intervention.
He found out too much and we had...
Walt!
You're rationalizing murder
the murder of a president.
You're going to contact these people
and recover the nerve gas before it leaves the country.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Why not?
I don't know where the nerve gas is.
And the man I have working inside
has gone dark-- he's unreachable.
Now, you'll let things play out as they are.
Otherwise, your administration will be implicated
and your presidency will be destroyed.
It's your choice Mr.President.
Jack.
Thanks for seeing me like this, Mike.
What is it?
Did you tell anyone we were meeting?
Of course not.
Son of a bitch!
Who did you tell?
Who did you tell?!
I didn't tell anybody, Jack!
Jack Bauer, stay right where you are.
Put down your weapons and put your hands up.
What's the meaning of this?!
Tell your men to stand down!
I'm sorry, sir, we can't do that.
He's here at my request!
We have orders to use force if necessary.
Orders? From who?
The President of the United States.
Get on your knees.
Thanks.
Novick and Bauer have been taken into custody.
So we're just gonna lock Mike Novick up?
For the time being.
Well, what good will it do?
Eventually, he's gonna get out,
and he's gonna talk to the press.
What can he say?
He doesn't know anything.
I thought you told me
he talked to Jack Bauer.
We stopped Bauer before he could give Mike any details.
What's he gonna think?
We're detaining him.
Bauer was about to divulge national security secrets
that Mike's not authorized to hear.
That's why Mike's being detained.
And what about Bauer?
He must have talked to other people at CTU
and told them what he knows.
As soon as this
nerve gas leaves U.S. soil,
it's gonna be very difficult to prove
that either of us is connected to this in any way.
And you're sure
that these-these-these detonators will work,
that the Sentox gas will be released before it can be used
against the Russians?
Yes.
Right now all you need to do
is authorize me to terminate CTU's involvement in this matter.
We'll tell them we've got the situation under control
and that we'll deal with Bauer.
Who, after all,
is not officially affiliated with them any longer.
All right.
Good.
Yes?
Mr. President, I have Mrs. Logan for you.
Not now.
Yes, sir.
Dunley.
What is Jack Bauer doing here,
why is he under arrest,
and why wasn't I told?
Orders of the president.
Directly?
No. It came through Walt Cummings' office.
Okay.
Thank you.
We're no longer running point on the search for the canisters.
We've been ordered off by Division.
Why?
The White House wants to use their own people to coordinate from now on.
That doesn't make sense
we'll waste hours
getting another agency up to speed.
Yeah, I know.
I tried calling the president.
He's not taking my calls.
What about Mike Novick?
Jack should be with him by now.
Novick's people say he's unreachable,
and Jack's cell goes right to voice-mail.
Something's wrong.
Yeah, I know,
but I don't know what we can do about it.
I do.
What?
We can disregard the order.
We're not disregarding a presidential order.
If we don't, we will not find this nerve gas.
Sending Jack Bauer
to have a conversation with Mike Novick
as a private citizen is one thing,
but I'm not about to start considering disobeying
a direct order from the White House.
That's because you don't have the experience
to know any better.
Mr. Buchanan,
will you step outside for a moment?
I can't have you talking to me like that
in front of these people.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Are we clear about who's in charge here?
Yeah, but my advice stands.
If this order jeopardizes
our chances of finding that nerve gas,
it's your responsibility to ignore it--
at least until we can make our case to the White House.
You also need to learn to make decisions faster.
Bill...
One more thing that comes with experience.
Lynn,
if we don't do everything in our power
to stop these terrorists,
we're not doing our job.
Okay,
disregard the order.
Thank you.
Is there anything else you'd like me to pack for you?
Maybe a few of your...
nicer dresses?
I'm being confined to a psychiatric ward, Evelyn.
I don't think there are
gonna be any black-tie events.
Sorry.
How'd this happen?
What's that, Mrs. Logan?
Charles and me.
I was his confidante.
All those years in Congress, my... opinion
was the one that mattered most to him.
And now I'm...
...less than an afterthought.
I'm sure the president would be here
if he could.
He's the President of the United States,
Evelyn.
He can do whatever he wants.
If he wanted to be here,
he would be.
Mr. Bauer,
you're being moved
per the president's orders.
Where?
To a class three detention facility.
On what charges?
I was invited here by Mike Novick.
Those are my orders, sir.
You're Pierce, right?
Aaron Pierce. You served under David Palmer.
Yes, I did.
I need to speak with you just for a moment, please.
That's not possible.
It concerns David Palmer's killer.
All right.
David Palmer was assassinated
because he was on the verge of discovering
that the terrorists that attacked us today
were being helped by someone
within Logan's administration.
Who?
Walt Cummings.
Why would Mr. Cummings be involved
with terrorists?
I couldn't tell you.
But I can tell you
that the terrorists are now in possession
of a weaponized nerve gas,
and Walt Cummings may be
the last chance we have to stop them in time.
Walt Cummings ordered the
assassination of David Palmer.
I know that's hard to believe,
but I can prove it, it's true.
Actually, it's not that hard to believe.
The First Lady also thinks
someone in the administration was involved.
Your primary responsibility as lead agent
is to protect the President
of the United States.
Someone in his administration
is undermining his authority.
That is equivalent to a coupd tat.
Agent Pierce, please...
please, I need your help.
Bauer's escaped.
When? I didn't get a code alert.
My comm's down.
Call it in, have agents cover the west gate--
that's where he was headed.
What about you?
I'll take your post.
Go.
Yes, sir.
That was NSA
CTU hasn't transferred
the search operation to their jurisdiction yet.
What's the problem?
I don't know.
But you need to call Lynn McGill,
make sure we're in charge of this.
I've been avoiding his calls because
he's just gonna ask me
why I'm pulling CTU off the search operation
and I don't know what to tell him!
You don't have to tell him anything.
You're the president.
Agent Pierce,
we're in the middle of a meeting
if you don't mind.
Mr. President
my name is Jack Bauer
and I'm sorry to have to confront you like this
but your chief of staff is withholding information
that is vital to this nation's security.
Stop this!
I'm the President of the United States--
get your hands off this man!
Agent Pierce, do something!
I am, Mr. President.
I'm upholding my oath to protect you.
That won't have any effect, sir.
I've overridden the distress line.
Mr. Cummings is guilty of conspiring with terrorists.
He facilitated the theft of a military-grade nerve gas,
and today is responsible for
the death of at least three people,
including David Palmer.
I know about that,
but there's an explanation.
What do you mean, you know about that?
Mr. Bauer, please,
I just found out a couple minutes ago.
It's very complicated.
I don't know what this man has told you,
but we need to find that nerve gas now,
and I mean immediately
before it is too late.
It's already too late.
What do you mean?
Apparently, it's on its way out of the country.
Where is it?!
He told me he doesn't know!
He's lying to you, sir!
The man I have inside has gone dark,
I don't know.
I'm done talking with you,
you understand me?
Now you read my file.
First thing I'm going to do,
I'm going to take out your right eye
then I'm going to move over
and I'm going to take our your left.
And then I'm going to cut you.
I'm going to keep cutting you
until I get the information that I need,
you understand me?
So for the last time, where is the nerve gas?
I don't know.
Stop!
Stop. Stop!
I'll tell you!
I'll tell you.
It's-it's on a freighter
leaving the port of Long Beach at 2:30.
How is it concealed?!
In a container carrying medical supplies.
What's the container number?
I don't know.
What's the number?!
I don't know!
I-I'd tell you, I swear.
Mr. Bauer!
I don't know.
Mr. Buchanan, I've got Jack Bauer on line three.
Jack, what's going on?
We've been trying to reach you.
Bill, hold on.
I'm going to put you on speakerphone.
Bill, I'm standing here with the president.
The nerve gas is at Long Beach Harbor
in a container full of medical supplies
on a freighter bound for Central Asia.
It's set to depart at 2:30 p.m.
How solid is the intel, Jack?
It came directly from Cummings.
Mr. President, we've been trying to reach you
about an order we received changing our jurisdiction.
Disregard the order.
Then you want CTU to maintain operational control of the retrieval?
Yes. Absolutely.
I'm alerting CBP.
Get hazmat teams in there and set up a perimeter.
Have medical teams standing by
in case the gas is released.
Got it.
Good work, Jack.
Are you heading back to CTU?
I don't know yet.
Jack, we'll let you know when we have
more information on the container.
Copy that.
Mr. President,
Agent Pierce and I are prepared
to hand ourselves over to the authorities now.
Aaron.
Yes, Mr. President?
Take back your shield
and get Walt Cummings out of my sight.
Yes, sir.
He told me it was too late, and I believed him.
You need to understand, I trusted Walt Cummings...
but he lied to me.
I was coerced.
There is, uh, one more thing that we need to discuss.
What is that, sir?
You.
The fact that you're alive
presents problems for both of us.
Yes, Mr. President.
I accomplished what I set out to do
which was to identify and locate David Palmer's killer.
I would like to stay on until
the nerve gas is retrieved.
After that, I give you my word
I will simply disappear again.
All right.
I think that would be best
for the good of the country.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Bauer.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Excuse me.
I'll see you soon.
Wait. Kevin. Hold up
What's happening?
- Martha. - Charles...
Come on. Get out of the car.
Be careful.
What?
You were right.
There was a conspiracy.
David was trying to
warn you and warn me.
I should have listened to you.
I-I...
Y-you... you believe me now?
It was Walt Cummings.
He lied to me.
He convinced me that you were out of control.
Walt?!
Sending you back to the... the clinic in Vermont was his idea.
And you went along with it.
I'm sorry, Martha.
Sending me away without a word...
like I was... some nuisance to be gotten rid of.
Excuse me, Mr. President,
but you wanted to know when a link with CTU
was established.
Yes, um... thank you, Wendy.
See that the First Lady's bags
get back to her room.
Of course.
I've got to go.
Chloe, do we have confirmation on the intel Jack gave us?
There's only one ship
scheduled to leave the port
of Long Beach at 2:30.
It's a freighter heading for Central Asia,
leaving from Pier F.
We don't have CTU teams in the vicinity,
but we've got a Customs and Border Protection
task force on site under our directive.
All right, make sure that CBP understands
the nerve gas is housed in 20 canisters
of gray metal that are unmarked.
They're going out in a shipment of medical supplies.
Yeah, yeah, they know all that already.
But there's going to be
about a thousand cargo containers on that ship
and we don't know which one the nerve gas is in.
It's container 539146,
box seven.
I was able to hack into the ship's manifest.
It's the only container stocking medical supplies.
That's great.
Make sure all the strike force units have that.
Right.
Lynn, the White House is requesting
a live feed from the assault.
We'll have Chloe patch them in once the TAC teams
reach the staging area.
All right, got it. Yeah.
That's him.
His name is Ivan Erwich.
He's a chemical engineer
trained at the University of St. Petersburg.
Joined his country's separatist movement six years ago.
Do we have any clearer images any file photos?
No, which is why we need you to I.D. him
when the strike force has a visual.
Okay, just make sure that CPB knows
that we need to take Erwich alive.
They know. Stand by.
What's the situation?
The strike team is in place, Mr. President.
We're just waiting for the video feed to come up.
Feed's up.
CTU, we've located the target container.
No hostiles present.
You have the green light, Agent Finn.
Remember,
do not discharge your weapons
unless absolutely necessary.
If a bullet breaches one of those canisters,
we'll have a massive casualty situation.
Copy that.
Masks on.
Go!
Don't move!
Put your hands in the air now!
He's dead.
Open 'em up.
Let's go! Open 'em all up.
This one.
Empty. Next.
Moving on, moving on.
Come on, get it open.
Empty. Next. Come on, move it.
Open it open it.Next.Open it
come on, come on.
What do we got?
What do we got?!
Nothing?!
There are no gas canisters here, CTU.
Repeat, the nerve gas is not here.
Get Walt Cummings in here now!
Yes, sir.
Damn it!
The nerve gas isn't there.
It has to be.
Where are the canisters?!
I don't know.
I-I've told you everything.
They have to be there.
- Oh, God... - What is it?
That's Schaeffer, the man we had inside.
They must've found out
we reprogrammed the detonators.
It's his cell phone, sir.
Who's calling you?
That's Schaeffer's number.
Bill?
I want you to monitor and record this call.
We're on it.
Answer it now.
Yes?
We know you've altered the arming codes, Mr. Cummings.
Who is this?
I think you know my name...
as I now know yours.
Your man Schaeffer confessed everything.
Is President Logan with you?
The President had nothing to do with this...
nor did anyone else in the government.
I was acting alone.
Do you really expect me to believe that?
It's the truth.
Erwich, listen.
We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country is about to pay a very steep price.