We release the sentox here
and 200 000 people die.
We need access to the control room.
Jack bierko will be ready to deploy any minute.
If we could ignite that gas before it leaves the plant
the sentox will be incinerated.
Bierko!
Give me a hand.
Organize an escort team.
You get him back to CTU alive.
You got it.
I just word from the faa about a hiJacking aboard a diplomatic flight.
So what?
Jack Bauer is the Hijacker.
What was he doing on that flight?
Looking for the recording that implicates me in David Palmer's death.
Order the plane down and grab Bauer before he can hurt us.
We need to take him down now
dead or alive.
Mr. President?
I don't care if Bauer's making threats or not
that plane has to land immediately.
And when it lands
I want my secret service detail to take him into custody.
Sit down!
He has a gun!
Everybody just stay in your seats!
Do what I tell you
and no one will get hurt!
Captain
this I Jack Bauer.
I'm speaking to you on a discreet channel.
The person that I'm looking for
the man with the evidence that I need
is sitting next to you.
He's your copilot Scott Evans.
You need to open the door.
Could you
take the stick for a second?
I'm the only one who can fly this plane now!
Give me the recording.
Advise CTU I have the recording.
I'll be on the ground in less than 15 minutes.
Bauer's got the evidence.
He is in control of the plane.
What do we do?
You are going to have to shoot down that plane Mr. President.
Otherwise
you'll go to prison for treason and murder.
The following takes place between 3Am and 4Am.
Sierra tango cleared to flight level 2-2-0 report reaching.
5-2-0 sierra tango descend to flight level 2-2-0.
We can expect the approach to van nuys.
Good.
This is Jack Bauer.
Can you patch me through to Karen Hayes?
Hold please.
I'm bleeding.
I think you broke my nose.
You'll get medical attention as soon as we're on the ground.
Right now your only concern should be flying this plane.
Miss Hayes I've got Jack Bauer on line one.
Put him through.
You are connected.
I've got the recording.
It was on the copilot.
The copilot?
he was working for henderson.
The captain's unconscious
but I've secured the copilot.
We're en route back to van nuys airfield.
What's our eta?
21 minutes.
We're going to be on the ground in 21 minutes.
Karen listen to me.
This recording proves that president Logan
was complicit in David Palmer's assassination.
It'simperative that we do not let it fall into the hands
of anyone that is loyal to the president.
As soon as we're on the ground
I'm going to need you to provide me with a safe corridor back to CTU.
Jack it's Bill.
I'm back here with Karen.
I'll explain everything later.
We can dispatch a team to meet you at the airfield.
They can head off any law enforcement
take you into protective custody.
Okay good.
Bill how is Audrey?
Curtis just brought her in.
She's in medical getting treated
but it looks like she's going to be okay.
Thank god.
Okay I'll get back to you as soon as we're on final approach.
All right.
Audrey.
I just got off the phone with county general.
I have some great news.
Your father survived the crash.
He's alive?
one of our teams picked him up about 30 minutes ago at the accident site.
He's still in icu
but they expect him to pull through.
Oh my god.
We have a team stationed at the hospital.
He'll be well-protected.
Thank you.
I have to take this.
Curtis?
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
This is manning.
Is henderson secured?
He's in holding room three.
Good.
I need you to take a team to pick up Jack.
Where is he?
He's on a plane heading towards the van nuys airport.
Eta is 20 minutes.
Why is he on a plane?
He had to commandeer the plane
in order to secure the evidence against president Logan.
I'll brief you with the details en route.
Curtis I cannot emphasize strongly enough
the explosive nature of the evidence that Jack is carrying.
I need you to put him into protective custody
and bring him back here to CTU.
Understood.
President Logan will probably send his men to retrieve it.
You've got to get to Jack first.
We will.
I'm heading out.
yes?
We have a solution that will allow you to order the plane shot down.
I sure as hell hope so.
I may be the president
but there are protocols in place that I can't just ignore.
What we're proposing will circumvent your protocols.
What is it?
We're going to simulate a vci distress signal.
It'll be broadcast on the airplane's transponder code
and it will appear to come from Bauer's flight.
Hold on.
What is a vci distress signal?
It's an emergency signal indicating that there's a hiJacking in progress
All you need to do is appear to struggle with the ethics
and then give the order.
Mr. President?
Fine.
All right.
You sound reluctant.
I can't believe it's come to this.
I'm going to shoot down a plane full of innocent people.
None of us is happy about this Mr. President
but you don't really have a choice.
Bauer has evidence implicating you in this conspiracy
and I don't have to tell you what the consequences will be for all of us
if it's released.
We should contact chloe and bring her in.
We're going to want her help bringing Jack back to CTU.
Fine.
Send an escort.
Karen
I appreciate this.
I know you're putting everything on the line to help us.
All I can say is this recording better be everything Jack claims it is.
I know Jack.
I don't always agree with his methods
but I trust his judgment.
I'll go make that call.
What's going on?
What's Buchanan doing out of holding?
The situation has changed Miles.
There's some new intel.
I haven't seen anything.
What new intel?
I don't have time to explain it right now.
What does that mean?
It means that I'll brief you when I've got the chance.
Have you compiled the orders for bierko's transfer?
I'm still working on them.
Let me know when you've got them.
What is it Mike?
A situation has come up regarding the hiJacked plane.
Tell me what's happening.
The faa just picked up a vci distress code.
It originated from flight st-520.
What's a vci distress code?
The vci is a coding system that was recently installed on all commercial airliners.
This particular code indicates that a hiJacking is underway
and that the plane is going to be used to target installations on the ground.
Oh my god.
Admiral Kirkland is standing by on video-conference from point mugu.
He's ready to brief you with the details.
Admiral Kirkland
I'm Mike novick.
I have the president here.
Mr. President.
Admiral.
Mike's told me about this vci signal.
How could it have been sent without Bauer's knowledge?
Most likely one of the pilots under duress secretly activated the transponder code.
Let me get this straight.
At last report Bauer was in the passenger cabin.
Does this mean that he's now in the cockpit
and that he's in control of the plane?
It appears that way sir.
what do we do admiral?
Sir the protocols for this scenario are clearly specified.
We're compelled to take preemptive action.
What action?
The aircraft must be shot down.
We've already scrambled an f-18 out of point mugu.
We just need your approval to engage.
There are over 50 people on that plane admiral.
We have to think of the people on the ground Mr. President.
Over 20 million citizens live in los angeles county
each one of them is now a potential target.
I don't believe this.
Mr. President if I can interject.
Admiral it's hard for me to accept that
Bauer intends to use the aircraft as a weapon against civilians.
From my briefing document
Jack Bauer is a distraught individual with a history of erratic behavior.
Jack Bauer has spent his entire career protecting american lives.
I think there's a reason he's doing what he's doing.
What would that be?
I don't have the answer
but we should at least try to find out.
We don't have the time.
Mr. President
we could have the f-18 shadow the aircraft.
We could issue a standing order to fire
only if the target deviates from its present course.
That's not a viable option Mr. President.
Why not?
Right now that plane is over the desert.
In another 15 minutes
it'll be above los angeles.
If we're forced to shoot it down then
there'll be facing massive casualties on the ground.
And Mr. President
we must also consider the possibility that
Bauer intends to attack the presidential retreat.
The retreat?
You're inside the target zone
and Bauer's already been accused of killing one president today.
The simple fact is sir
we don't know what his intentions are.
Mr. President...
Mike. Stop.
I've made my decision.
Admiral I'm authorizing you to shoot down that plane.
Yes sir.
Mr. President...
Mike please.
Don't make this any more difficult for me than it already is.
Miss Hayes.
This just came in over the interagency sub-net.
What is it?
We have to alert Jack.
This is Bauer.
Jack
air traffic control just received a vci distress signal from your aircraft.
That effectively authorizes president Logan to shoot you down.
Shoot us down?
And f-18's been scrambled out of point mugu Jack.
You have eight to ten minutes at best.
Can you patch me through to the pilot of the f-18?
No chance.
They're on a coded frequency.
We can try to get in touch with the white house.
And tell them what?
They don't want to hear anything I have to say.
Hold on.
We need to land this plane now.
We're 100 Miles from the nearest airport.
They just scrambled an f-18 to shoot us out of the sky.
We need to get on the ground now!
You didn't hear me.
There's nowhere to land.
How much runway do you need?
At least 5 000 feet.
Bill do you hear me?
Jack.
I need you to look for a stretch of freeway 5 000 feet long
straight enough for us to land on.
I'll pull up maps in the area Jack.
It'll take a few seconds.
Get back to me as soon as you've got something.
We can't land on the freeway.
Yes we can.
It's late there's a curfew.
There won't be any cars on the freeway.
Cuff your right hand to the flight control now.
All the way.
Start taking us down.
Do it now.
What's chloe o'brian doing here?
I don't know.
You can go.
What's going on?
An f-18's been scrambled to shoot down Jack's plane.
Can you open up a socket with the atc radar tracking plot?
Yeah I think so.
Do it chloe.
We need to know the exact amount of time
Jack has before the fighter plane reaches him.
Okay.
Karen look at this.
Two possible landing sites.
I think this one's the best shot.
I agree.
Let's get Jack on the phone.
I need to speak with you.
We need to make an emergency landing.
Talk to your passengers and get them ready.
What's happening?
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just get them ready.
Okay.
Listen up everybody.
We're going to prepare for an emergency landing.
The proper procedure...
it's Bauer.
Jack it's Bill
I think we found something.
Bill hold on one second.
I want to put you on speakerphone.
Go ahead.
It's a stretch of the 118 freeway between mile marker 91 and 92.
There's about 4 000 feet
then there's an overpass.
That's not long enough.
It's the best we can do.
Copy that Bill.
Hold on give me a second.
You can either try and land this plane on the freeway or I will.
Give me the coordinates.
3-4-5-0.2 north by 1-1-0-3-0.4 west.
We need to know where that f-18 is.
Jack it's chloe.
I'm working on it.
Manning.
We have the exact location where Jack's putting down.
Go ahead.
It's the 118 freeway between mile markers 91 and 92.
He should be on the ground within minutes.
Copy.
We're redirecting.
118 freeway.
Mr. President we're five minutes away.
I'm patching us in directly with the pilot of the f-18.
Go ahead.
Bravo one
this is admiral Kirkland.
You're on with the president and myself.
Report status.
My radar is locked onto the target.
Okay I've got the atc radar plot.
Put it on the main screen.
Jack the f-18 is within 15 Miles.
They're not gonna make it.
He's gonna be within the missile range in two minutes.
You're not descending fast enough.
If we increase the descent rate
we won't be able to pull out of the dive.
If we don't get on the ground before that f-18 reaches us
it's not gonna matter. Descend now!
Put the oxygen masks on!
Target has increased angle and rate of descent.
One minute from missile lock.
Jack they're almost within weapons range.
The aircraft can't take this.
I have to pull up.
Not yet!
I can see the freeway!
Come on.
Okay level up now!
Now!
We can't pull out of the dive!
I need your help!
Pull!
ground proximity alert.
20 seconds to missile lock.
Target's at 1 000 feet and leveling.
Leveling?
Affirmative sir.
What does that mean?
Target may be preparing to land.
The objective seems to be the 118 freeway.
Lower the landing gear!
We're going too fast!
Lower it!
He's lowering his landing gear.
The f-18's in range.
I have missile lock.
The aircraft is in a landing profile sir.
I recommend we abort.
What?
The parameters have changed sir.
I want that plane shot down!
Sir...
order your man to fire now!
Mr. President!
Admiral Kirkland is right.
The aircraft's not a threat.
There's no reason to do this.
I implore you to reconsider.
Sir we have a lock,what are your orders.
Abort.
Yes sir.
But if they don't land
I want you to shoot that plane down immediately!
Yes Mr. President.
Bravo one hold fire.
I repeat hold fire.
Copy base.
Bravo one holding fire.
We have marine units deployed in the area.
I want them to cordon off the landing site
and apprehend Jack Bauer.
Yes sir.
500 feet!
We're not gonna make it.
Come on.
CTU.
CTU We've spotted the plane.
They're coming in for a landing.
We're heading towards them now.
I'm handing the controls back to you!
Touch it down!
We're still going too fast!
target has touched down.
I'm clear.
Returning to base.
Bill we made it.
We're down on the ground.
Jack we've redirected Curtis to your location.
He should be there in a few minutes.
I'm just east of the balboa overpass.
Have him meet me there.
Send a secondary team to pick up the copilot
Got it.
Get out of there Jack!
Everyone keep moving to the rear of the plane!
Exit from the rear now!
You should have followed through Mr. President.
You should have orderehould have ordered that pilot to fire.
They were landing on a freeway.
I had no pretext to shoot them down.
I had to abort.
It's going to be much harder to contain now
if not impossible.
Bauer's on the ground.
He won't get far.
Even before the plane touched down
I ordered two battalions of marines into the area.
They're cordoning off the landing site  even as we speak.
Bauer...
has nowhere to run.
I hope you're right Mr. President.
This is our last chance.
If Bauer gets through...
I know.
I know what's at stake Graham.
I'll get back to you as soon as I have any news.
Curtis it's Jack!
Go ahead.
The marines are moving in.
They're setting up a perimeter.
Where are you?
We're approaching your position from the north.
Okay I got you.
I'll meet you on the north side of the freeway.
they know I'm still in the area. We got to get out of here.
Head south on variel. Move.
Damn it. You're gonna have to try and talk your way through the roadblock.
Get your hands up!
Hands where we can see them.
We're federal agents.
Los angeles counter terrorist unit.
We've been given orders to detain everybody inside this perimeter.
We're all on the same team here commander.
We're trying to apprehend the suspect who hiJacked that plane.
-Jack Bauer? -That's right.Now let us do our job.
I need to see individual id'S. I'm gonna call this in.
We don't have time for this commander.
The longer we sit here the better chance Bauer has of slipping through the net.
-This will only take a few minutes. -A few minutes is all Bauer needs to escape.
We're not prepared to let that happen.
Now we're moving out.If you really want to fire on federal agents that's your call.
Stand down.
Move out.
Stand down!
Head east for a while  then turn south.
Yes sir.
-Buchanan. -It's Curtis.
-We've got Jack and we're headed back in. -Okay Curtis.
Marines are all over the place. Barely got past one of the patrols.
They must be taking direct orders from Logan. There's no other explanation.
We can't take the chance of running into any more of these patrols.
-We'll stick to the back streets. -Understood.
Hayes.
I want to know what's going on.
Miles I told you I would tell you when I felt the time was right.
I'm sitting here watching you work with two people
under arrest for aiding and abetting a federal fugitive.
If you don't talk to me  I'll have to get my answers somewhere else.
I'll be right there.
-You can't tell him. -I can't hold him off any longer.
You really think that's a good idea?
I have to trust him.
He's been nothing but loyal.
I probably shouldn't have kept him in the dark this long.
I'll be right back.
I don't appreciate being threatened Miles.
And I don't appreciate being shut out.
We've worked a lot of years together Karen
and I have never wavered in my allegiance.
I don't deserve this.
No you don't.
Come with me.
Jack Bauer's acquired evidence implicating president Logan in David Palmer's death.
-Have you seen this evidence? -No but Bauer's bringing it here now.
What is it?
It's a recording of a conversation between the president and an accomplice.
-But you haven't heard it? -No.
And that's what you're doing with Buchanan and o'brian?
Covertly helping Bauer?
Yes.
For the past three hours president Logan has
done everything in his power to keep Jack from getting back here alive.
You're working against the most powerful man in the world
and you haven't actually heard the evidence.
This is why I didn't talk to you Miles.
Because you knew I'd talk you out of it.
Yes I know what I'm doing is risky.
If I am wrong  my career is over.I could be brought up on charges.
Not just your career Karen.
I am doing this because I believe that Bauer is telling the truth.
But you don't know.
Okay okay.
Let's say he is.
Let's say that recording implicates Logan.
Then what are you going to do?
Are you going to arrest the president of the United States?
That will be up to the attorney general.
-You're depending on... -I'm sorry to interrupt.
-Yes. -They're ready to move bierko.
Thank you. I'll be right out.
Look I have to go over the transfer protocols.
I know that what I'm asking from you is difficult.
Everything rests with what's on that recording.
Tell me what you need.
Bauer will be here any minute.
The best way for you to help me is to go back
out there and keep things running smoothly.
-All right. -Miles?
-It's imperative this stay between us. -Of course.
Thank you.
We have a full tactical complement  enhanced ordinance package two vehicle escort.
Vladimir bierko you're being transferred
to a primary holding facility at our district headquarters.
-Let me know the second he arrives. -Understood.
Let's move out.
Let's go.
-Where the hell is Mike novick? -He's moments away sir.
You told me that three minutes ago.
Yes sir.
I'm sorry Mr. President. I was on the phone with colonel Owens.
He's the marine field commander on the site.
-Is Bauer in custody? -No sir.
What happened?
As ordered the marines sealed off a one-mile radius around the landing site.
They've completed a sweep of the area.
And?
And it's colonel Owens' estimation that
Bauer is no longer inside the perimeter.
-He got away. -It appears so sir.
I can't believe this.
Uh Mr. President it's only a matter of time before Bauer's apprehended.
Sir are you all right?
Thank you Mike.I need some time alone now.
Jack the attorney general's on his way to his office right now.
He'll be ready for a video conference in ten minutes.
Okay good.Chloe I want you to prepare the recording for playback.
I want you to clean it up and apply a digital signature
so that we can establish a chain of evidence.
-Okay. -You need to work alone.
I don't want anyone else near that recording.
You don't ever let it out of your sight.
-I won't. -You said I had ten minutes.
-I'd like to see Audrey. -Of course.She's in medical.
Thank you.
No,ma'am he is still in ICU.
Well when will I be able to speak with him?
-Sorry I don't know. -All right I understand.
Well just let him know...
can you please tell him that his daughter called and that...
she loves him very much.
Thank you.
It looks like my dad's gonna be all right.
Yeah I know I heard.
Oh god I'm so glad to see you.
Me too.
We did it.
The attorney general's going to hear it.
-So it's over? -Yeah.
President Logan's going to pay for David Palmer's assassination.
Thank you.
Close your eyes.
I'm going to sit with you for a minute.
-Yes. -Graham.
-I've been trying to reach you. -I know.
-Bauer slipped through the cordon didn't he? -Yes.
I've just been told that
the attorney general's office received a phone call from the director of CTU.
I think it's fairly obvious they're in possession of the recording.
I think that phone call was about you.
I didn't expect it would to happen so soon.
I am sorry Charles.
You don't deserve this.
Listen Graham despite how things turned out...
...I still believe that we were in the right.
I still believe that we acted in the best interest of the country.
And we have to keep putting the country's well-being ahead of our own.
The spectacle of a sitting president on trial for murder would be devastating.
Yes. Yes it would.
Aside from the psychological damage to the country
a trial would expose certain realities that should never see the light of day.
If only we could keep such a trial from taking place.
That thought occurred to me  as well.
I'm glad we agree.
I want you to know I've taken steps to ensure
that you and your associates won't be implicated in any of this.
I appreciate that Charles.
We all do.
There's nothing more to say.
I'm going to hang up now.There are uh
a few things I'd like to take care of before...
Good-bye Charles.
Good-bye Graham.
Martha may I come in?
Now you want to talk?
Marti please?
What do you want?
Is there something else you want to confess?
No.
I want to tell you how sorry I am...
for everything.
When you forget to give me something for my birthday
that's when you say you're sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.It was horribly wrong and unforgivable.I know that.
But what I can't live with is the fact that I hurt you.
That's the last thing I wanted to do.
Marti?
Marti please.
That's the truth.
The truth.
You know what really gets me Charles?
What?
That you had me going for so long.
If I wasn't so horrified by the fact that
I'm married to you I might actually be impressed.
Yes.
I have an urgent call for you sir.
He says his name is Miles Papazian from CTU.
I don't want to talk to anyone from CTU.
He insists that you'll want to speak to him.
He says it's about Jack Bauer.
-Put him through. -Yes sir.
Go ahead You're on with the president.
Mr. President?
Yes go ahead.
You don't know me  my name is Miles Papazian. I work under Karen Hayes.
What is this about?
It's about a recording sir
that Jack Bauer has just delivered here to CTU.
Sir my understanding is it's a recording of a conversation of yours
that if leaked could significantly compromise national security.
Go on.
My superior Ms. Hayes  is working with Bauer and Bill Buchanan.
Their intention is to play the recording for the attorney general.
-Why are you telling me this? -Because sir...
I feel compelled to intervene.
And I just I wanted to make sure that you would approve.
I do Mr. Papazian  I do approve.
Listen I'm going to text you...
my private number.
Let me know how it goes.
And Miles...
...I promise you  I won't forget this.
Thank you sir. That's all I wanted to hear.
Mr. President I look forward to speaking with you again soon.
Karen wants to know how long before the teleconference starts?
Five minutes get out of here Miles.
-We'll be ready? -Not if you keep interrupting me.
I'm just doing my job chloe.
Well if your job is to slow things down  then you're doing really good work.
I'll tell Karen you'll be ready.
Thanks.