The terrorists are controlling the main terminal at Ontario Airport.
Today, your president and the president of Russia
have come together to sign an anti-terrorism alliance.
I have hostages.
Unless President Logan and President Suvarov
make a joint statement repudiating this accord,
I will order their execution.
I want this handled!
Do you understand?
I don't care how you do it.
I don't care what it takes.
Fix it!
David Palmer called me last night.
He said it was a matter of national security.
Those were his exact words.
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter of national security.
- That's not what he said. - Yes, it is.
No, that is a trick.
I know that all phone conversations are recorded.
Where do they store those transcripts?
Archive room, down the hall.
This is Bill Buchanan.
I'm hoping we can resolve this peacefully.
I don't think you understand just how serious we are.
You make any efforts to enter the terminal,
you will spend the rest of the day collecting body parts.
Jack, I'm going to need you to quarterback this thing from inside.
I'm staring straight down on the main concourse.
We've got 6 hostiles wearing explosive vests.
We have to assume their orders
are to detonate if we try to make a move.
Hey, I got a woman, Diane Huxley,
says she has info for CTU.
Diane, what's going on? What's wrong?
Derek is inside the terminal.
You!
No...
Curtis, they're moving another one of the hostages.
Oh, my God, it's Derek.
You have a problem at the terminal.
Jack Bauer is inside providing recon for CTU's rescue operation.
Mr. Bauer,Derek has 5 seconds left to live.
4...
Beresch!
The following takes place between 10Am and 11Am
We've been trying from here,
but we still can't make contact with Jack.
Can you make a visual, Curtis?
Negative.
Maybe Jack went dark intentionally.
Unlikely. He was talking to us when his transmission cut off.
We have to assume he's been captured or killed.
Which means we need to mount this assault without his help.
Without Jack directing our teams,
success probability falls to less than 20%.
President Logan is going to sign this treaty in less than 1 hour.
If the terrorists are still in control, they'll kill all the hostages.
What do you want me to do, Bill?
Work up an assault plan that doesn't include Jack.
All right, I'm going back to the staging area.
We'll coordinate from there.
Back to your stations.
Prepare to reconfigure.
All teams, stand down.
We're working up a new mission profile.
Mr. Bauer,
what is CTU's assault plan?
The boy means something to you, otherwise
you wouldn't have given yourself up so easily.
Tell me the plan.
They're going to storm the north concourse doors on my command.
I'm coordinating the operation from in here.
Is there anyone else inside?
No.
Get me the plans to the terminal.
You've been a great help.
We'll keep the boy alive from now.
Bring me another hostage.
Anything you do in here today
will not stop that treaty from being signed.
The United States Government does not negotiate with
terrorists, you know that.
Your President is a weak man.
He'll back down once more blood is spilled.
Not him.
You! Get up!
Move! Move!
I'm not your enemy...
Please... Please, you don't have to do this.
- Vlad.I can help you buy more time, - Please!
No! You don't have to do this now.
CTU was supposed to have raided the terminal by now.
Why haven't we heard from them?
Bill Buchanan said they had a setback.
What kind of setback?
They lost contact with Jack Bauer.
Why? What happened to him?
They're not sure what happened to him,
but they need to reconfigure their assault plan.
Yeah.
I'll tell the President.
Beresch is transmitting from the terminal.
He's got another hostage.
We have waited patiently for you to renounce this unholy pact
with our oppressors, but we have heard nothing.
This is the cost of that silence.
What happens next is your choice, Mr. President.
If you choose to sign this corrupt document,
understand that you will also be staining it with the blood
of the remaining hostages.
If CTU can't pull this off in time,
that's upwards of 60 people, Mike.
You know, I've never done anything in my presidency
that I didn't feel was right for the country.
Of course not, Sir.
Nobody thinks otherwise.
I know I'm ambitious,
that I want this treaty to be the hallmark of my presidency,
but I never thought I would sacrifice innocent life.
Mr. President
you are not responsible for the actions of these murderers.
I could postpone this.
Sir?!
I give them what they want, maybe nobody else has to die.
Do you think these people would actually release the hostages?
We both know that would never happen.
You're doing the only thing you can do.
Mrs. Logan, if someone altered the recording
of your conversation with David Palmer,
the President needs to know.
No. Not now. Not yet.
What are you waiting for?
Charles is much too preoccupied.
Between the Summit and the hostage situation,
he's not in the frame of mind to deal with this.
Besides, he thinks I'm unstable.
Which means I have to show it to him in just the right way.
So, until the treaty is signed,
I'm not letting this out of my sight.
What's happening?
I'm sorry, I don't have time to explain.
You said you were going in to get the hostages.
We lost contact with Jack.
What does that mean?
We're not sure what happened.
But we need to change our assault plan.
- Is Jack okay? - We don't know.
What about Derek?
As soon as we get more information, I'll make sure you're told.
- Please, I... - Ms. Huxley...
I need to go.
The situation continues to grow more tragic.
We've just received a video feed
confirming that another hostage has been executed
inside the main terminal at Ontario Airport.
Jack...
Don't say anything.
We're going to get through this. Just don't say anything right now.
You're going to call CTU and tell them you've revised your assault profile.
Tell them to come to the emergency door south of gate 12.
They won't just do that because I ask them to.
They'll need an explanation.
That's your concern, Mr. Bauer.
Overwrite volume four with the approach vectors,
and re-key with the airport grid.
Okay, hold on, just for one second.
We don't have one second.
We're running out of time to save the hostages.
Want some help, Spenser?
He doesn't need any help.
Just keep managing the two-ways or else we're gonna have dropout.
Excuse me.
You're Ms. O'Brian, right?
- Who are you? - Lynn McGill. I'm from District.
I met you when you came out for that memory management lecture.
If you say so. What do you need?
- I need to talk to Bill Buchanan. - Is he around?
He's in the Situation Room.He's kind of busy right now.
I see him. Thanks.
I look forward to working with you today.
You don't know who Lynn McGill is, do you?
No, and I don't care.
Get back to work.
Once Curtis and his teams go in there,
I want an update on deployment of HRT.
Mr. Buchanan, I assume they told you I was coming.
Lynn, please... call me Bill.
If we were having a beer or something, but at work,
it's better if we maintain a more formal mode of address.
Whatever makes you feel comfortable.
Look, we're in the middle of final prep here...
I know, I understand President Logan
wants us to go into the terminal as soon as possible.
Yes, before the treaty is signed.
Is Curtis Manning ready to send his teams in?
He is, but we're flying blind.
My briefing sheet says that we have Jack Bauer on the inside.
And we haven't heard from him for close to 20 minutes now.
Well, that's interesting.
Lynn, I read the bulletin from Division,
but I still don't know why you're here.
District was getting heat from the White House.
Heat about what?
Jack Bauer.
They just want to know things are running smoothly.
- We're on track, Lynn. - Well, I'm sure you are...
but that's my assignment.
Is your tactical wired through to all the servers?
Yes, it is, you can go ahead and plug into Station Four.
I'd prefer to work from your office, Mr. Buchanan.
I hate to displace you, but I think I should have a central vantage point,
and I just want to make sure
that you're okay working from another station.
Fine.
Good.
And, uh, it's not a big deal,
but just so that everyone's clear on the chain of command,
I think you should address me as
Mr. McGill in front of the others.
You know, Lynn, I'd rather not.
Just a suggestion.
Anyway, I need your office.
And that's not a suggestion.
Fine.
Mr. Buchanan, it's Jack Bauer on line 1.
Is Curtis plugged into this call?
I'm on, Bill.
Go ahead, put Jack through.
You're both on with Jack Bauer.
Jack, what happened?
One of the hostiles got too close,
I had to end the transmission.
All right, we'll restart the countdown.
Negative, Curtis.
We need to scrap the existing plan,
find a new breach point.
My men are already in position.
They moved the hostages within the kill zone.
They'll be taken out with the crossfire.
There's an emergency door just south of gate 12.
It's unguarded.
You should be able to punch through with no opposition.
I see it, but I'm not comfortable with this entry point.
It's the only shot we've got.
Are you there now?
Yes. It's clear.
I'm in a flank two position.
I repeat, I am in flank two position.
Curtis, how long before your teams can redeploy?
About 20 minutes.
The President's going to sign that treaty within 30 minutes.
I'll go as fast as I can.
Jack, I'll call you when my men are in position.
You can call us in.
Copy that. I'll be standing by.
Ivan and Ishmael, stay with the hostages.
The rest of you come here.
Vlad, guard them.
You are doing great.
Manning.
It's Buchanan.
How long until your people are ready to move on the terrorists?
About 15 minutes.
- Why so long?  - When Jack called and changed the breach point,
I had to modify everything, including the explosives.
They have to be repositioned precisely.
Maybe it's a mistake to write down Jack's new information.
It might take too long.
Jack's aware of our deadline.
If he didn't think it was worth the delay
he wouldn't have made the call.
I trust him.
All right, Curtis, 15 minutes.
You have to make this happen.
- I will. -Call when you're in position.
Mr. Buchanan? Mr. McGill needs to see you in his office.
It'll have to wait. Tell him I'm busy.
He said it had to be now.
Fine.
No, I'm settled in fine.
If I need anything, I'll call. Thanks, Donna.
What is it, Lynn?
I'm up to my ears trying to coordinate this hostage situation.
Sit down, Mr. Buchanan.
Would you stop with the "Mr. Buchanan"?
We need to get this assault in motion now.
Sit down, Bill.
I informed the White House
that the rescue operation is back on track.
Thank you.
I must admit, though, I felt a little inappropriate
talking about an operation that I didn't personally review, so
before you send your men into the terminal.
I'd like to see the Playbook.
Look, I can't have you micro-managing my work here, Lynn.
If you want to do my job, just let me know. I'll go home.
Please don't be defensive. I'm not challenging you.
I'm just trying to do my job.
I'll have Chloe send it to your laptop.
Anything else?
That's all for now.
Bill?
Fighting me isn't going to increase our chances
of saving those people's lives.
Lynn wants to look at the revised assault plan.
Send it to him.
Does that mean he's running point, instead of you?
It just means he wants to see the plan, Chloe.
Bill, Curtis just confirmed
that his team will be ready in ten minutes
based on Jack new intel.
As of this time, there is no word as to whether
or not the president is going to call off the signing
of the historic treaty agreement between the United States
and Russia scheduled for just under an hour.
There been any response from the White House
since we killed the last hostage?
They released their statement confirming the signing
of the treaty is going ahead as planned.
They won't capitulate,as long as they think
their rescue attempt will succeed.
Once we kill them, then they'll realize their options have run out.
The only chance these people had of being rescued is gone because of me.
People were going to die here today, Derek.
That was their plan.
This is not your fault.
I'm the reason you went along with them.
If I wasn't here...
Stop it.
This is not over.
While there has been no official rebuke of the terrorists' demands
statements from the White House
appear to confirm the president's position
is unchanged, and that the treaty will be signed within the hour,
as scheduled.
That puts the lives of the approximately 60 men,
women and children being held as hostage in question.
Were the terrorists to carry out their intentions...
Good news, Sir.
CTU has reestablished contact with Jack Bauer.
The rescue operation is back on track.
But that's still no guarantee.
- Excuse me, Sir? - The hostages may be killed when we go in there.
Let's be honest.
That's more likely than not.
We don't know that, Sir.
President Suvarov is waiting for you outside.
You're walking outside together onto the stage.
We all agreed to the protocol.
It's time already?
Yes, Sir.
Mr. President.
Shall we?
My people have just informed me that the assault has been delayed.
It's happening now.
It will happen before the treaty is signed.
Don't worry.
Mr. President, like you,
I have staked much of my political future
on the success of this treaty.
If this rescue attempt fails
it will not only be rendered meaningless,
it will become a mockery.
And so will we.
I'm here to escort Mrs. Logan.
The ceremony's beginning any minute.
- She'll be out in a moment. - Oh, may I...
have a word?
You're aware Mrs. Logan was found in one of the archive rooms?
Uh... I don't know anything about that.
Aaron Pierce said you lied to him.
You told him Mrs. Logan was in her room, when
she was actually going through classified documents.
I don't think you understand
just how grave this situation is.
What do you mean?
Mrs. Logan removed a document from the archive
that contains highly-sensitive intelligence protocols.
That's not what she said it was.
What exactly did she say she took?
I think that you should talk to her about this.
Evelyn, this is important.
What did she tell you?
She said it was a transcript of a call she had with David Palmer.
And I'm sure when she said that, she believed it.
You're aware if this document finds its way into the wrong hands,
that you'll be held responsible.
I'm not the one who took it.
No, you aided and abetted.
You'll not only lose your job,
you'll be prosecuted.
That's not fair.
I tried to talk her out of this.
All I'm asking is that you tell me where did she put it.
She has it with her. It's in her blouse.
She said she wouldn't let it out of her sight
until she talked to the president about it.
Walt?
Sorry to keep you waiting. I'm ready now.
Presidents Logan and Suvarov will each make statements,
which will be followed by the signing of the treaty.
How much time will there be between the moment
I step out on stage and when I sign the document?
Not long.
Does CTU know that's how long
they have to launch the rescue attempt?
Yes, Sir.
They're completely synchronized with what's going on here.
I hope so.
The lives of those hostages depend on it.
Today was supposed to be
the crowning achievement of my presidency.
Instead, everybody's waiting to hear
what's going to happen at the airport.
- So, how are you feeling? - I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
How come you just keep getting better looking as you get older,
and I just keep getting older?
What are you talking about? You're the most beautiful first lady
Pennsylvania Avenue has ever seen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
President Logan and President Suvarov.
The treaty signing is a minute and a half ahead of schedule.
Should you call Curtis and let him know
he might need to speed up the assault prep?
No. Curtis is moving as fast as he can.
A call from me isn't gonna make him move any faster.
I just thought he might like to...
I said no, Chloe.
The only way to make sure the assault happens in time to save the hostages
is to try to slow down the signing.
- What's wrong with Buchanan? - Nothing.
I think he just realizes we're not gonna be able to save the hostages.
Before we begin the treaty signing
I would like to address
what's happening just a few miles away from here.
As you know, terrorists have already taken innocent life
in an attempt to stop this historic treaty from being signed.
President Suvarov will not let this happen.
I will not let this happen!
Yes, Mike?
Bill I should have heard from you by now.
Have your men gone in yet?
We're not quite ready.
You have to go in now.
- The president's about to sign that treaty. - I understand.
We're pushing as hard as we can.
In the meantime, is there anything you can do on your end?
Like what?
Can you stall things?
Can you slowdown the ceremony?
Bill, the entire world is watching this on live television.
The presidents of the United States and Russia are on stage now.
This process has been set in motion.
No, I can't stall.
Okay, I'll call you back.
No. You stay on the phone with me.
I need to know the moment your people go in.
Yes, Sir.
This barbaric lawlessness
that's taking place at Ontario airport,
only underscores the need the necessity for this accord
and for our continued vigilance and commitment
to fighting terrorism around the world.
It looks like President Logan is going through with the signing.
He said he's not going to give in to your demands.
Are you sure this is going to work?
It will work.
And the reason the president is so confident is that
he thinks his rescue attempt will save the day.
Are you sure can end up that assault?
As soon as the CTU agents come through the entry point
that Jack Bauer fed to them,they'll all be killed.
One of the president's aides will then walk up to the podium
and whisper into his hear that there'll be no rescue
that his signature on the treaty
will be the death warrant of the hostages.
That will stop him, I assure you.
Well, just in case you're wrong and he signs the treaty,
you'll be ready to carry out your threat?
Every one of my men is committed to doing what needs to be done today.
We've upgraded our estimate of how many wounded there'll be.
I need ten more ambulances at the airport before we launch.
The rescue operation you're about to execute
is radically changed from your initial approach.
It was revised based on new intelligence from Jack Bauer.
Which he phoned in after being dark for nearly 20 minutes I was there
- Right. - I need to call you back.
Well, I can't say that his explanation
for being out of touch is entirely satisfactory.
Jack said he was trying to avoid detection.
Wh... What are you suggesting?
There's too many unusual circumstances at work here...
I want to try to understand it better
before we send our people in.
I'll need the entire transcripts of your communications
with Mr. Bauer since he's been inside.
To what end?
Thouroughness.
I don't need a sorting run on the calls
just raw transcripts will be fine.
Fine, I'll send them to you.
Thank you.
Curtis in on line 3.
Curtis, what is your situation?
My men are in place, and we're setting the entry charges.
Any complications?
No
We're also jamming the trigger frequency
so Beresch can't detonate the vests remotely.
We should be able to make our entry on target.
Good.
Stay on the line with me untill we get the go.
O'Brian.
Uh, Miss O'Brian,
I'm trying to understand the transcript of
Jack's last call to CTU,
and there a few items I...
Mr. McGill, I'm really busytrying
to help keep revised assault on schedule...
What do you need?
I understand, and don't want to slow you down,
but I'd appreciate it if you unlock me volume five
there are a few things
- that I'd like to see. - I don't need to know what you'd like to see.
Okay, it's unlocked.
Good.
This Lynn McGill person's really slowing things down.
Yeah, that's his style.
I worked whith him before.
He usualy loses about 20% of his staff in the first
couple of days after taking control of the new office.
That many people quit?
No.
Mostly were fired.
In the volatile climate of twenty 1st century,
the sharing of detering technologies by
responsible powers is the surest guarantee of global peace.
But let this accord be proof that
our two great nation stand together
in their comitment to fight
the enemies of peace and freedom.
Akhmed found Chevensky.
He's dead. He killed himself...
we found him in the baggage room.
What about the key card?
Chevensky had it hidden right where he said he would.
The rest of you will work cleanup on whoever makes it through that line of fire.
Assume CTU is in body armor so go for the head shot.
You... and you,
guard the hostages.
Kill anyone who tries to break away.
Head down!
It is time, the black night is broken
by the dawning of the light of global peace.
Curtis.
Jack, my men are in place.
Okay.
Now, remember, I am in a flank two position...
make sure your men don't hit me when they come in.
Roger that.
Ready to start the countdown on your word.
Jack?
Move in at your discretion.
All teams, we have a green light.
Counting down from 60 seconds on my mark.
Now.
Jack, we'll see you inside.
Everyone, 60 seconds.
Stop the assault!
Put Curtis on the phone.
What are you talking about?
They're walking into a trap.
Look at the transcript.
When Jack issued the command directive
he used the term "Flank two."
Yes, he was trying to give us his position inside the terminal.
No, he wasn't.
"Flank two" is a duress code used to
indicatethe agent is communicating under duress.
We ran Jack's calls through a protocol filter
if there'd been a duress signal in there we would've found it.
You filtered through the current codes.
When Jack was active,
"Flank two" was a duress code.
Chloe, confirm that.
Jack is trying to tell us
he's being used to send misinformation.
If Curtis Manning's teams go in now
they'll be ambushed.
He's right.
Curtis, abort the countdown. Repeat, abort, abort.
Stand down. All teams stand down.
We're aborting entry. Repeat, we're aborting entry.
Confirm that we're standing down. What's wrong Bill?
We detected a duress code in Jack's call.
We have to assume that terrorists are
feeding him the information he gave us.
Redeploy your men according to the original assault plan
and do not contact Jack.
If Jack contacts you, buy time.
Copy that. We're moving.
You're gonna outflank the terrorists?
Yes.
That should work.
All teams, reposition for entry through the east and north gates
plan Bravo repeat plan Bravo
through the east and north gates. Go!
Acknowledged.
Redeploy protocol one.
What's happening?
Ma'am, I need you to step back to the vehicle.
Now.
He said 60 seconds three two ago.
What is CTU waiting for?!
I don't know.
You heard what I heard.
It's Jack.
Jack.
What's happening?
There was a malfunction on the entry charges.
What's the time frame?
Any minute.
They're resetting the detonators.
Stand by.
Copy that.
They're in position.
Stay ready!
Yeah.
Is it done?
No. CTU hasn't attacked yet.
You said it would happen before the signing.
And you told me the president would never let it go this far.
He's signing it.
You have no choice.
Kill them all.
No!
You okay?
Yeah.
We secure the terminal besides the hostiles
there appears to be no further casualties.
Repeat remaining hostages are unharmed.
Good work, Curtis.
You get that, Mike?
Got it. Thanks for the good work.
Mr. President, I have some good news.
I have just received word that the crisis at the Ontario Airport is over.
The rescue operation that I authorized was successful.
The terrorists have been captured or killed.
And, best of all
this has all been accomplished with no further loss of innocent life.
Excuse me agent!
My name is Jack Bauer.
I know who you are, Sir.
Can I use your pick?
This is Derek Huxley.
His mother is waiting for him at the command post.
- Can you please take him there? - Of course.
What about you?
Come here.
I have to finish this.
Go take care of your mother.
- Yeah. - Okay.
Go.
I'm missing one.
Everybody, I need your attention.
We're looking for a man who was being held here with you.
He's a white male, mid-30s.
He was wearing a bright yellow tie.
Did anyone see him leave?
Anyone?
Keep the hostages here until I get back.
Mom!
Derek!
They were going to kill me.
Jack saved my life.
He saves everyone's life.
Mrs. Huxley,
I need you and your son to follow me.
Can I see Jack Bauer?
I'm sorry, I have instructions to transport you to CTU.
This way, please.
Mister President.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
- Charles? - Oh, watch your step honey.
I need to talk to you.
Sweetheart...smile, it's over.
Charles, I just need a few minutes alone with you.
- Yes soon. - No! Not soon, right now... this is very important.
Martha, when I am done with this, I'll call for you.
- I promise. - All right this ends now.
I have played my role without interfering.
Now it is time for you to attend to me.
- And I will. - Charles, do not patronize me!
Something is going on.
- I am not crying wolf again. - Martha...
Please do not ruin this moment for me.
We'll talk later.
Martha. Everything all right?
No, it's not all right.
I have to talk to my husband.
The situation is more dangerous than he realizes.
Whoa, and what situation is that?
I'm sorry, Walt.
I can only talk to Charles about this.
Curtis just confirmed the area's been contained and
they're reporting only minor injuries among the hostages.
Good, thank you.
You should probably route all field updates through Mr. McGill
for the time being.
Okay.
Bill, if you have a moment.
Lynn, uh.I owe you an apology.
For what?
Well, if you hadn't recognized the duress code
that Jack transmitted, well...
Bill, you're the reason I figured out what he was doing.
What do you mean?
Well, I admit, I was suspicious of Mr. Bauer
but you were so adamant about his integrity that I just...
looked for a way to reconcile the contradiction, so...
thank you.
I assume Mr. Bauer's been taken into custody?
Well, I plan to debrief him here
but not as a suspect.
Well, he hasn't been officially cleared in the deaths
of David Palmer or Michelle Dessler.
Well, based on mitigating evidence in Chloe O'Brian's testimony
we're confident that Jack was framed for those murders.
I appreciate that,
but it still doesn't change a very tangled situation.
I mean, we have surveillance footage that places
Jack Bauer at the site of David Palmer's assassination.
Well, clearly, it was doctored.
Not according to preliminary tests.
If we're gonna get to the bottom of this,
Jack Bauer has a lot to answer for.
Bring him in now.
The rest of the terminal's clear.
Jack.
It's good to see you again.
It's good to see you.
We've got a problem
one of the hostages is missing.
He was working with the terrorists.
Give me a description, I'll take care of it.
I'll help you now... let's go.
Jack, you need to go back to CTU.
Buchanan just gave orders to take you into custody.
I watched Beresch give this guy a key card.
Something else is going down here.
- We've got to find this guy now. - And I'll get right on it,
but I need you to go with these men, please.
He's a white male,
mid-30s, wearing a dark suit and a yellow tie.
He's about five-eight.
We'll find him.
Okay. Thanks.
These are my weapons.
Altieri, Hutchinson
we have a possible sleeper among the hostages.
We're looking for a Caucasian male
We're looking for a Caucasian male five-eight, dark suit, yellow tie.
Where have you been?
We had a problem with Chevensky.
Where is he?
Dead.
You have the key?
Masks.
All right, now.
One, two, three.
Push it, push it.
Do you have the merchandise?
Yes, we're moving the canisters out now.
Good.
Transportation's been arranged.
Call me when you're out.
I will.
Evelyn, did you get a chance to speak to my husband?