Now, why would David Palmer call my wife
about a national security threat?
Can't risk having Mrs. Logan
obsess about this phone call.
David Palmer called her yesterday.
Our communications office
will have a recording of their conversation.
Get that for me.
You don't need to be concerned that
there's any connection between David's death
and the phone call he made to you.
He said it was a matter of national security.
Those were his exact words.
Martha, it's David Palmer.
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter of national security...
No, that's not what he said.
That is not what he said!
Yes, it is.
I have dealt with the Martha Logan situation.
I was able to alter the tape of the phone call
before the president heard it.
There's no longer any evidence on my end
that Palmer was trying to warn her about the attack.
Sir, it's Edgar. I think we can find Chloe.
She's accessing our system through a laptop.
I'm running a locate now.
What'd you get for me on Chevensky?
He's a baggage supervisor at the airport.
Jack Bauer! Agent O'Brian!
We know you're down here!
Don't fire!
Do not fire!
Chloe, what the hell's going on?
Jack didn't kill anybody.
He's being framed to cover up the
real reason Palmer was assassinated.
Where is he?
I can't tell you.
Where can I find the baggage claim supervisor?
- Down that hall to the left. - Thank you.
Chevensky!
Why was President Palmer killed?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You are going to tell me what I want to know.
It's just a question of how much you want it to hurt.
Mom, do you see those men?
I have to warn Jack.
Derek, where are you going?
Come back here!
No!
Quiet!
You will not be harmed as long as
your president complies with our wishes!
The following takes between 9Am and 10 Am
We have a critical incident in progress!
I want a facility lock down and a code five evac, right now!
- Clear the area! Ma'am... - Officer...
Officer, my son is in there.
I'm sorry, ma'am. We're evacuating the area.
Follow these people.Ma'am!
Grab her!
I have to get my son!
Derek!
I have information for CTU!
Please.
My son.
Everyone, quiet!
Stay down.
If you cooperate, you have a chance of leaving this building alive.
If not, you will die.
Do you understand?
Take out all cell phones and pagers and drop them on the floor.
We're going to be okay...
Bring them in.
Everyone up.
Move it.
Chevensky?
- Yeah. - Well?
Chevensky's not here.
We have to find him. Keep searching.
Let's search the other rooms.
Come on.
Let's go.
McClaren.
Listen very carefully.
We have hostages.
If you wish to keep them alive,
you'll make no attempt to re-enter the terminal.
We are wearing explosive vests.
We are prepared to detonate ourselves along with our captives.
If you make any efforts to enter the terminal,
you will spend the rest of the day collecting body parts.
Hello?
Set up a security perimeter.
We'll operate from the northwest apron behind hangar 12
and get those fire trucks out of here!
Everybody out!
Claremont, grab that woman in the yellow next to Bailey.
Bring her up here. Quick!
All right.
Yeah. Thank you.
Bill, I just spoke to the director of Secret Service.
Now that Suvarov has arrived safely,
they're lowering their security level by one.
I think we should do the same.
I'll take our Tac Teams off standby.
Have we heard back from our unit that was sent out to the refinery?
Yeah. At least that part of Chloe's story checked out.
So it's possible that Jack was set up in Palmer's assassination.
We can't assume too much.
Jack still has a lot to answer for.
Buchanan.
Mr. Buchanan, I've got Jack Bauer on the line.
- Put it through. - Yes, sir.
Bill, put it on speaker phone.
Please.
Jack, it's Bill.
Bill, I'm inside Ontario Airport.
Gunman have just attacked and taken over Terminal One.
They are carrying automatic weapons and they have hostages.
We haven't received any alerts.
Trust me. You will.
What are you doing at the airport, Jack?
I was following up a lead.
President Palmer knew of the planned attack.
I believe that's why he was assassinated.
We just received an interagency flash.
There's been an attack on Ontario Airport.
First reports are of several men carrying automatic weapons
and they've taken control of Terminal One.
Go to alert level four.
Launch all available Tac Teams.
Curtis is in the air.
Redirect him to the airport.
Have him maintain operational control the moment he's on site.
Right.
Jack, we just received confirmation of the situation.
I want you out of there now, Jack.
Turn yourself in.
Let our people handle this.
Understand this, Bill.
I don't work for you.
I'm staying inside.
You want my intel, fine.
But I'm doing this my way.
How many hostiles are there?
Approximately 10 to 12.
Gunmen have locked down the terminal.
I'm going to be sending you photos of the hostiles.
They should be clear enough that you can identify them.
Hold on.
Okay, they're transmitting.
All right, Jack.
We'll pull a schematic of the airport and forward it to your cell.
Bill, hold on. One more thing.
A woman is going to contact you.
Her name is Diane Huxley.
I sent her and her son to CTU for protection.
Who are they?
I don't have time to explain, but I'm responsible for them.
Just make sure they're safe, okay?
We'll take care of them, Jack.
Thank you.
I'll be standing by.
We have to alert the president.
Right.
I'd like to personally extend my condolences
on the loss your country has suffered today.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I hope that what you and I accomplish here today
will serve as a fitting tribute to David Palmer's legacy.
I can't imagine anything more appropriate than
the two of us establishing a comprehensive
antiterrorism alliance between our nations.
If you would excuse me for a moment, Mr. President.
Of course.
What's up, Mike?
Terrorists are controlling the main terminal
of Ontario Airport in L.A.
Terrorists?!
Yes, sir.
There are eyewitness reports of two casualties
and they've taken hostages.
Who are they?
Unclear.
CTU Los Angeles is prepping a briefing.
Mr. President.
I suggest we move to the Situation Room.
Now?!
CTU thinks this may be related to the summit.
Related in what way?
I don't know, sir,
but we'll find out during the briefing.
Sir?
We should go.
Of course.
Mr. President, as you've probably been made aware,
a situation has developed that
requires my immediate attention.
I have just been informed.
This is terrible news, indeed.
Please let me know if there is anything I can do.
I will. Thank you, sir.
That's all for now, ladies and gentlemen.
Spencer?
Pulling the ground plan of the terminal off the NTSB server
and sending it to Jack Bauer now.
Good. Edgar.
Were you able to identify the terrorists
from the photos Jack sent?
Still no matches on the watch list.
I tried three different encoding arrays.
Did you try widening the parameters?
If it was any wider, we could use the phone book.
Wait, wait, wait, hold on a second.
Try using NP-safe adaptive search.
You okay?
Thanks for asking, Edgar.
Chloe...
you managed to rack up four protocol violations.
Well, it's a lot worse than that if you count agency doc codes.
It's more like 26 violations.
Do you want me to figure out whose face that is?
Or I could just go wait in holding.
See what you can do.
- Did it work? - We got something.
It's off an archive from the Bureau of Consular Affairs.
Anton Beresch,
a former army officer in one of the Russian breakaway republics.
Which means this definitely has something to do with the summit.
I'll data-mine the interagency servers,
see what I can come up with.
DOD is receiving a localized broadcast from the airport.
The networks are also picking it up.
Spenser, put it on screen.
...citizens of the United States,
today your president and the president of Russia
have come together to sign what
they have called an "historical accord",
an "antiterrorism alliance".
Your leaders claim it will bring peace
and security to their respective countries.
As you'll soon learn, it'll accomplish exactly the opposite.
We are acting on behold of the oppressed people of our region.
A people whose desire to be free is every bit as strong as your own.
We are prepared to use every means
at our disposal to achieve our goal.
I have hostages.
Unless President Logan and President Suvarov
make a joint statement repudiating this accord,
I will order their execution.
You have exactly 90 minutes.
We have to get this lunatic off the air.
Sir, we can contact the networks,
but they're under no legal obligation to comply.
We take these actions with the full knowledge
that we will be called butchers,
but we are only responding to the violence
that has been inflicted upon our own sons and daughters.
Until we as a people achieve our own
due-- national sovereignty--
terror will be met with terror.
That was a live feed from the
Ontario Airport in Southern California.
As we just heard,
the terrorists are demanding that President Logan
repudiate the antiterrorism accord.
This is insane.
How did these people get control of an entire airport?!
We've been preparing for this summit for 16 months!
Every news agency in the world is here!
I've staked my entire administration on this day,
and now these people are demanding that I go on
national television and publicly repudiate everything we've done?
Mr. President, perhaps you should take a few moments...
Mike! I want this handled!
Do you understand?
I don't care how you do it,
I don't care what it takes-- fix it!
All right.
Go ahead.
Curtis, this is Jack.
I'm staring straight down on the main concourse.
I've got six hostiles wearing explosive vests.
Four of them are staying near the hostages.
I expect their orders are to detonate
if we try and make a move,the other two are roaming.
I've got two security doors on the northeast side of the concourse
both are chained, but currently unguarded.
All right, get a recon unit over to the northeast wall.
All right, Jack, I'm gonna need you to quarterback this thing from inside.
Copy that.
Hey, I got a woman, Diane Huxley,
says she has info for CTU.
Diane Huxley. Who is she?
- Curtis, did you just say Diane Huxley? - Yes, I did.
- Is she there? - Yeah.
Let me speak to her.
I'll bring her over.
Hello?
Diane, what's going on?
What's wrong?
Derek is inside the terminal.
What are you talking about? I left him with you.
He saw some men,he wanted to warn you.
I tried to go after him. There was an explosion.
Are you sure he made it all the way inside?
I don't know.
Hold on.
Damn it!
I see him.He's with the other hostages.
But he's not hurt.
Please don't let anything happen to him.
Jack, I can't lose my son.
Diane, listen to me.
I promise you on my life,
I am gonna get Derek back to you.
Do you understand me?
Okay.
Let me speak to Curtis.
Jack.
Hey, Curtis, I need to ask you a favor.
I want you to let Ms. Huxley
stay with you at the command post.
You got it.
I need you to let me know if
the hostiles adjust their profile in any way.
Copy that.
I'll get back to you.
Son of a bitch!
His name is Anton Beresch.
He's a member of the Dawn Brigade,a separatist movement
blamed for numerous terrorist bombings in Russia.
Precisely the kind of terrorist organization
today's accord was designed to combat.
Bill, I have no intention of calling off this signing,
much less making a public statement to that effect.
So that gives you less than 90 minutes to rescue the hostages.
We're already operating under that timetable
Sir.We have a unit on the ground,
and we're making an on-site assessment.
Spare the agency patter
just get it done.
Sir, you need to be aware,
we should be prepared to accept
additional civilian casualties.
More casualties?
It's a possibility we have to face, sir.
I'm not prepared to accept any such thing.
Bill, it's your job to make sure those people get out of there alive.
Mr. President, the terrorists are wearing explosive vests.
They've threatened to detonate themselves and the hostages
if any attempt is made to retake the terminal.
I'm aware of the situation.
Bill, have you tried initiating a dialogue with the terrorists?
Yes, what about talking to them? Have you tried that?
Beresch placed a call to an Airport Police sergeant
it was a blocked number,
but we're in the process of back-tracing it.
Look, whatever you do,
just make sure it's done by the deadline.
When I put my name on that accord,
I do not want to be signing the
death warrant of innocent American citizens.
Yes, Mr. President.
Do you have that number?
Yes, sir. We just completed the back-trace
Try it.
We're all gonna die.
It's gonna be okay.
Yes?
This is Bill Buchanan,
a director of the Los Angeles Counter-Terrorist Unit.
I am listening.
The president has authorized me to speak on his behalf.
I'm hoping we can resolve this peacefully.
I've told you how to resolve this peacefully.
Your president
must make a public statement.
I know he's considering that option.
Then we have nothing more to speak about.
There must be some other way we can address your demands.
I don't think you understand just how serious we are.
I know ,the president...
Data-mine the call.
Yes, sir.
Get up!
- Up! -What?
Bring him.
Curtis, they're moving one of the hostages.
On your knees!
Oh, my God.
Please...
I have a wife.
So do I.
No.
You!
Curtis, they're moving another one of the hostages.
I can't see where. I'm changing position.
- Derek? - Ma'am, please, ma'am
That's my son.
- Ma'am, please. - They're gonna kill my son!
That's my son!
Derek
No, let me go!
In 15 minutes,
your president will get another
demonstration of our commitment.
15 minutes.
I'm in position.
How much longer till
- you're ready to move in? - At least a half hour.
We're still transferring personnel from the summit.
Negative. That's too long.
You need to advance your attack.
We can't. We're just not ready.
Curtis, they're gonna kill that kid.
Jack...
I heard that woman Diane's side of the conversation...
This has nothing to do with her.
These people are gonna continue to
kill hostages until the summit deadline.
We can't risk the lives of all
those hostages for this one kid.
You know that.
I not gonna jeopardize the mission.
- Just tell your men to hurry. - They will.
It's all connected.
Maybe that's enough, Mrs. Logan.
The doctor said you really shouldn't be watching this...
Evelyn...
David Palmer called me last night.
He said he had something to tell me.
It was "a matter of national security."
I think it has something to do with this.
The terrorists?
Yes. I tried to tell my husband and Walt Cummings
but they think I imagined the call.
So we checked the phone recordings.
The conversations don't match.
Someone altered the conversation, Evelyn.
Who would do something like that?
I don't know.
Now listen to me.
You have got to cover for me.
No one can know that I am gone.
Do you understand me?
Where are you going?
O'Brian.
- Chloe, is that you? - Jack?
What's going on? Why are you answering the phone?
Mr. Buchanan needed my help with the airport crisis.
- Are you alone? - Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to send a picture of one of
the hostiles over to your screen. Hold on.
Okay, I got it.
I want you to enlarge the upper right corner of his vest.
Looks like a secondary detonator
cell phone activated.
Yeah, so the leader can set off the charges individually
in case anybody gets cold feet.
I need the detonation frequency.
Okay, I'll have to I.D. the detonator.
It could take some time.
Just get started.
Did you clear this with Buchanan?
No.
Chloe,
can you see the live feed?
Oh, my God. It's Derek.
I need your help.
Okay. I'll get back to you.
Spenser...
I was really worried about you.
Not now.
I need you to reconfigure Jack's phone
to emit an alternate signal.
What for?
Could you just work up a procedure?
This is off protocol, isn't it?
Yes.
Spenser, you have more knowledge about
bandwidth processing than anyone here.
I need you.
Got it?
Yeah.
It's Agent Pierce.
I'm here to escort Mrs. Logan to the Garden Room.
She's still not ready.
President Logan is expecting her
15 minutes before the ceremony.
Could I speak with her?
What's going on?
She's in one of her moods.
If you push her, it'll make it worse.
I'll wait out here.
Thanks.
It's Mr. Burk, isn't it?
Uh, Mrs. Logan...
You work in the communications office, don't you?
Yes, Ma'am.
I know that all phone conversations are recorded.
Where do they keep those recordings?
Uh, well, the calls are recorded onto a hard drive.
It's part of the central server.
Is there, by any chance, any hard copies?
Actually, the President insists
on written transcripts as backups.
He...he's kind of old-fashioned that way.
I know. Where do they store those transcripts?
Archive room down the hall.
Can you show me?
Access is restricted.
I'm the First Lady.
I understand, Mrs. Logan,
uh, but there are security requirements.
You...you have to have an entry card.
Do you have one?
Well, yes, I do...
Can I borrow it?
It's extremely important.
Mrs. Logan, I'm sorry.
Um... there's nothing I can do.
Mr. Burk...
we can continue this little dance if you really want to
but you and I both know
I am going to get into that room
so you can save us both the trouble
and just give me your entry card.
Mrs. Logan, you wouldn't...
You know, in three seconds, Mr. Burk
I am going to scream louder than
any woman you've ever heard in your life.
One... two...
Here's the card. Here.
Thank you.
I'll return it very soon.
O'Brian.
Chloe, they're going to kill Derek
in less than three minutes
I need that frequency.
We're still trying to find the manufacturer of the detonator.
Hurry. We're running out of time.
I know, but if we don't get the frequency right
we could accidentally detonate all the vests.
Okay, there's no match on any of the Czech military components.
That leaves the German manufacturers.
Jack, we're trying to narrow it down.
Now, the first team will enterthrough the southeast door
and split into two flanks.
The primary kill shots will take out the hostiles wearing bomb vests.
Second team enters through the southeast door
forms a protective ring around the hostages.
We'll only have a few seconds to neutralize the hostiles,
so find your targets fast.
Go.
What's your time frame?
We're on target to launch the assault in 15 minutes.
Understood.
How old are you?
Fifteen.
Try to control your breathing.
Slow down.
See?
Better.
Please don't kill me.
That's up to your president.
Bill Buchanan.
Beresch is calling from the airport, sir.
This is Bill Buchanan.
The boy hasn't long to live.
We haven't heard from the president yet.
We need more time.
No.
The president must announce the summit is canceled,
or I kill the boy.
We're doing our best to get
an answer from the president.
I implore you to resolve this without further killing.
This boy's blood
will be on his hands.
Come on, Chloe.
Jack, we just got a match on the manufacturer.
We're trying to figure out the frequency.
There's no match on the 2004 series.
It's got to be one of these three.
Hold him!
Agent Manning!
I got it.
Here it is.
We've got the trigger frequency for the detonator.
Go to submenu three on your phone.
I'm at submenu.
Enter this code: 6-3-3-9.
- Now what?  - The phone needs to reboot.
When it does, it'll give you a ready message.
Then you press the star key,
and it should send the signal to set off the detonator.
Your president has abandoned you.
I'm not getting a ready message signal.
It takes time to re-flash the ROM.
Son of a bitch, come on!
I'm sorry.
I got it. I got it!
Curtis, what was that?
There was an explosion in the terminal.
We can't tell what it is from here.
Patch me through to Jack.
Stay in position! Keep the hostages together!
Check the exits, make sure the perimeter's secure!
It was Ibrim's vest.
It must have detonated by accident.
Jack, what's going on?
One of the terrorists' vests blew up.
But none of the hostages were hurt.
Were you responsible for that, Jack?
Jack, answer me.
Bill, they were going to kill another hostage.
I didn't have a choice.
I didn't compromise my position.
Now you tell me this.
Are Curtis and his team
on schedule?
Yes. The backup units are in position.
- Go time is ten minutes. - Okay.
Everyone.
Fall into formation "B"
and run circuit checks on your vests.
The terrorists are revising their formation.
I'll contact Curtis in the next few minutes with final positions.
Thanks, Jack.
Mr. Buchanan, President Logan's on the line for you.
Mr. President.
The news is saying there was some kind of explosion inside the terminal
Everything is under control, sir.
Our tactical units are in position.
Go time is ten minutes.
Then what caused the explosion?
Well, we're not entirely certain, sir.
We believe that our man inside may have been
trying to stall the execution of a hostage.
He triggered the bomb vest of a hostile.
Did you authorize this action?
No, sir, he acted independently.
You should know, Mr. President,
the man we're talking about is Jack Bauer.
Jack Bauer?
He was in the terminal when the terrorists attacked.
He's been helping us coordinate our operation from inside, sir.
I thought that Jack Bauer
assassinated David Palmer.
There's mitigating evidence to suggest that
Bauer may have been framed,
Mr. President.
What evidence? What are you talking about?
It's complicated, Mr. President.
Why am I only hearing about this now?
I didn't distract you with details that could wait
until after we'd resolved this hostage situation,
sir.
You tell me everything
and I will decide which details are relevant.
With respect, Mr. President,
we don't have time.
Then talk faster.
Mrs. Logan is due in the Garden Room right now.
Open the door, please.
Just a few more minutes!
Ma'am, it's my job to make sure she's there.
If you don't open the door,
I will open it myself.
Mrs. Logan.
How dare you barge in here.
This is a private residence...
Evelyn, if something happens to Mrs. Logan,
the blame will fall on you.
We both know that.
So I am urging you in the strongest possible
terms to tell me where she is.
We're moving to entry positions.
Davies, Matthews, are your teams in place?
All teams in place and ready to go, Agent Manning.
All right. Copy.
Go.
- Oh my God... - It's okay.
- Listen, listen. - Derek's alive.
He's okay.
Are you sure?
I can't go into details, but he's okay.
I have to go.
We're mounting our rescue operation.
Thank you.
Keep an eye on her. Let's go.
They're waiting for you in the Garden Room, Mrs. Logan.
I can get up myself.
All right.
But you still need to come with me.
Whatever you say, Aaron. Whatever you say.
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Logan...
It's all right.
I'm really sorry.
Evelyn, will you stop apologizing?
It's annoying.
Besides, I got what I came for.
Yes.
You have a problem at the terminal.
Explain.
Jack Bauer is inside providing
recon for CTU's rescue operation
which will launch shortly.
Are you sure?
This came straight from the Director of CTU.
And Bauer was responsible for detonating
the vest of one of Beresch's men.
Can you tell me Bauer's precise location?
No.
But I know he has a connection to one of the hostages
a 15-year-old boy named Derek Huxley.
I have to go.
Tell them that's being handled out of the press office.
Thank you.
Yes?
Mrs. Logan is back in her room, getting ready.
Why the delay?
She was in one of the archive rooms.
Archive rooms...
What was she doing there?
The First Lady is safe and accounted for.
You'll need to ask her about anything beyond that.
Thank you, Aaron.
C.T.
Go to the ticket counters.
Go to the west exit.
Manning.
Curtis, this is Jack.
Beresch's redeployed six men.
Are you ready for final positions?
Go ahead.
Four men were deployed to the east side of
the terminal in front of the ticket counter,
the other two to the west side of the terminal
in front of the emergency exits.
- Do you copy? - Copy.
Okay, once you deploy,
I'll give you real-time updates on their positions.
All right, Jack. I'm starting the countdown.
All teams stand by to execute.
This is it.
He's in the terminal now.
Okay.
Hostages up!
Hold on one second.
Hold on.
Hold on, Beresch is changing something.
Jack? Jack!
Curtis, what happened?
I lost Jack.
What do you mean, you lost him?
The connection's broken.
Can you reconnect?
I'm trying.
Jack Bauer.
Derek is a very brave young man.
I will shoot him in the head
if you don't show yourself immediately.
- Curtis! - It's not going through, Bill.
Can you move in without him?
The last thing Jack said was
that Beresch was moving something.
He could be moving the hostages into the kill zone.
Abort.
All teams, abort the operation.
Repeat: This is an abort.
Bauer, if you want to save the boy,
present yourself now.
Mr. Bauer!
Derek has five seconds left to live.
Four
Three...
Beresch!
I'm lowering my weapon.
Secure him.