Has Bauer arrived at CTU?
No, not yet.
I need you to clear an entrance.
Why are you tracking Jack Bauer?
What the hell's going on here,
- Spenser? - I was following orders.
I'm sure if they're tracking Jack Bauer, they have a reason.
This man is a professional assassin.
He just killed Dr.Paulson.
He tried to kill me.
Did you let him into CTU?!
They told me he was here
to place a tap on one of the servers.
- That's all I knew. - Who told you?
The White House.
Mr.Cummings.
David Palmer was murdered because he was about to expose
Walt Cummings' connection to the terrorists.
You want the nerve gas? Cummings is your connection.
Cummings is the President's chief adviser.
How exactly do you suggest
we get to him?
I could secretly meet with Mike Novick.
Who did you tell?
Who did you tell?!
I didn't tell anybody, Jack!
Tell your men to stand down!
I'm sorry, sir.We can't do that.
Put your hands in the air!
Sentox gas is being smuggled out of the country
by separatists who think they're going to use it
against the Russians.
However, that nerve gas
will never reach Russian soil.
And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators on those gas canisters.
As soon as they've reached the terrorist base,
we'll trigger the canisters by satellite
and release the gas.
You're a traitor.
You'll let things play out as they are.
Otherwise, your administration will be implicated,
and your presidency will be destroyed.
Mr.President,
my name is Jack Bauer
and I'm sorry to have to confront you like this.
But your Chief of Staff is withholding information
that is vital to this nation's security.
Stop this!
I'm done talking with you.You understand me?
So for the last time, where is the nerve gas?
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop! I'll tell you! I'll tell you!
It's on a freighter
leaving the port of Long Beach at 2:30.
CTU, we've located the target container.
No hostiles present.
You have a green light.
Take possession of the canister.
Open 'em up.Let's go.Open 'em all up.
Empty.Next.Moving on.
What do we got, nothing?!
There are no gas canisters here, CTU.
The nerve gas is not here.
Where are the canisters?
I've told you everything.
We know you've altered the arming codes, Mr.Cummings.
Erwich, listen.
We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country is about to pay
a very steep price for betraying us.
The following takes place between 1Pm and 2Pm.
I was approached six months ago by a man named James Nathanson.
He was my contact.
Who is he?
Former CIA.
Said he was recruiting like-minded individuals
for this initiative.
"Initiative."
Is that what you call this?
You helped terrorists acquire weaponized nerve gas!
I told you we were gonna trigger the canisters
once the separatists reached their base in Central Asia.
This was not supposed to happen.
But it happened!
You got into bed with these people, and now they're
threatening to use the gas on American citizens!
Oh, you make it sound like our goal was to kill Americans!
What the hell was your goal, Walt?
Explain that to me.
We're patriots, Mr.President.
We were acting in the best interests of this country.
How is any of this in our best interest?
Shoring up a strategic partner
in the war on terror,
ensuring a stable flow of oil.
How is any of that not in our national interest?
I have Chloe O'Brian's on the line for Jack Bauer.
Chloe, are you set up for the trace?
All set, Jack.
We're ready to call Nathanson.
How long do I have to keep him on the line?
Until I give you a signal.
Chloe, dial the number.
The line's been disconnected, Jack.
There's nothing to grab onto.
They must know something went wrong.
He's gone dark.
- Damn it, Walt! - I don't want
this weapon deployed on US soil any more than you do,
but Nathanson cannot help you now and neither can I.
These terrorists are operating on their own.
Mr.President, I think he's telling the truth.
He can't help us, not anymore.
Aaron
get him out of here.
Yes, sir.
Jack.
What do we do now?
I need to be debriefed.
After that, I'm leaving, sir.
Given the current situation,
things have become more complicated.
CTU is gonna have to be responsible
for the retrieval of the canisters.
Why are you leaving?
Sir, I have a daughter
that doesn't know that I'm still alive.
If I have to disappear again, in all fairness to her,
I don't think she should know.
Jack, terrorists just threatened
to deploy chemical weapons on US soil.
They have the ability to kill millions of people.
I understand that, Mr.President,
and I believe that CTU can handle this.
Jack, your experience can make
a crucial difference in stopping them.
Look...you and I have a complicated history.
I realize that.
And I'm not naive enough to expect
any special personal allegiance from you.
But I know your respect for this office
and your concern for this country
is just as strong as it was when you served
under David Palmer.
I'm asking for your help,
just until this crisis is over.
I will reinstate you.
I will give you
all the support you need.
Mr.President, you and I...
Jack, please!
For God's sake, we need to recover this nerve gas
before it's too late.
Micro-circuitry on this remote has been tampered with.
As far as I can tell, unless we can repair it,
we can't arm the canisters.
Rossler will have a way.
He should have called by now.
Our real enemy is Russia.
We should be figuring out another way to get back home,
not wasting time trying to use the gas against the Americans.
Question my orders again, and I will kill you.
Do you understand?
They've closed the ports.
They will hunt us until they find us.
So if we cannot use the gas against Russia,
we will use it against America.
Get up.
Hello?
Lynn?
Jenny, now is a really bad time.
Yeah, I know you're busy,
but I need to see you, please.
What is it?
I need some help.
You mean money.
Lynn, I'm clean.
I'm working two jobs and busting my ass
to put my life back together.
How much?
$500.
Can I, can I come over there?
Absolutely not.
Why?
Are you afraid I'll embarrass you?
Yeah, I am.
Lynn, I got nobody else to turn to.
You know, I can't go back on the street again.
If you don't help me,
I swear I'm going to hurt myself.
For God's sakes, Lynn, I'm your sister.
All right, listen.
Jenny, listen.
There's a parking lot across the street from CTU.
I'll meet you there in 20 minutes.
Okay.
Thank you, Lynn.
Sorry I'm late.
I was just explaining that
Cummings provided us with a schematic
of one of the canisters.
Triggering mechanisms
on the canisters can only be activated via satellite relay.
Cummings says the terrorists have been given
invalid detonation codes.
Then these canisters are useless to them.
Unless they can find a way
to control the triggering mechanism.
Are we running evacuation scenarios?
Evacuation isn't feasible,
not without a time frame or a target.
Erwich's threat was intentionally vague.
What are we doing to track these canisters?
Chloe?
I pulled a voice print
from Erwich's call to Cummings
and I'm doing a scan of all satcom chatter.
If Erwich is in contact with anyone on that bandwidth,
we should be able to intercept and trace the call.
We better get lucky
cause we just got a new assessment from Civil Defense.
They're estimating that the nerve gas from each canister
will create kill zones between one and three square miles.
The terrorists are in possession of 20 canisters.
We're talking about potential casualties
in the hundreds of thousands, perhaps over a million.
Yeah?
Ivan Erwich?
Go ahead.
Jacob Rossler.
I was asked to call you by a friend in Moscow.
You've been briefed on our situation?
You need to reconfigure
the remote trigger for an Aatox chemical delivery system, right?
Yes.
You have the canisters with you?
You'll need to start by cutting into them.
Listen carefully to my instructions.
O'Brian.
We just got a pattern match.
Send me the hit.
All interagency search protocols are being run through CTU.
Ken, no one is going around you.
All right, I'll make sure
that you're apprised in real time.
Audrey, I thought you should know.
Logan has asked Jack
to be reinstated on a provisional basis.
He's been given full autonomy and access.
We got a possible intercept on Erwich.
This just happened.
On the inner casing,
you will find a display window with a seven-digit readout.
I'll need them.
And then what?
I will program a new chip for your remote trigger.
Put me through to Jack Bauer.
Voice print is a 95% match.It's Erwich.
He was on a sat-phone.
I can't trace it,
but the call originated from a landline downtown.
This is Bauer.
Jack, we may have a lead on Erwich.
I'm listening.
We intercepted a call between Erwich
and an unknown associate.
We weren't able to trace Erwich,
but we may have a location
for the associate.
22 North Figueroa, a penthouse.
Chloe, bring up the building manifest.
- See who's in there. - On it.
From what we heard, Erwich is trying to acquire
some kind of activation code.
Yeah, he's trying to reconfigure the trigger mechanism
so he can disperse the Sentox.
Bill, we're running out of time.
Okay, the penthouse is leased
to a man named Jacob Rossler.
Cross-checking.
He's a software programmer
indicted for high security code infiltration,
identity theft.
Never convicted.
Okay, I'm gonna need schematics on the building
and vectors for every entrance.
We'll have it for you by the time you get there.
Bill, we're going to need to go in covertly.
Have Curtis meet me at the location
with a small team of four.
But tell them to stay out of sight until I get there.
Right.
We'll be in touch.
This is our new destination.
They'll clear a landing zone for you.
Mr.Buchanan, this building's security system
uses proprietary technology.
It's a high-end platform.
It's a bitch to hack into,
especially with the time constraints we're under.
So, get Edgar to help you.
Spenser is better.
Chloe, absolutely out of the question.
Spenser can do this faster
than Edgar and I put together.
He wrote an infiltration code
that took us four months to hack.
- That's a bad idea. - Stay out of this, Edgar.
He didn't know Cummings was dirty.
His polygraph proved that.
He's was spying on us.
He was spying on you.
He lied to you.
Sir, if you don't let Spenser help us do this,
we're not going to get it done in time.
He has to wear a security wristband
and be under constant supervision.
Fine.
Audrey Raines.
Audrey, it's Jack.
Hey.
Listen, I wanted to tell you myself,
the president asked me to stay on
until the canisters were retrieved.
I heard that you were reinstated.
Jack, you know what this means.
You'll be exposed.
CTU can handle the crisis.
Audrey. The President thinks that I can help.
Jack, you don't owe them this.
Listen, Audrey, the reason why I called:
I need to ask you to do me a favor.
What?
Kim doesn't know I'm alive yet.
I don't want her to find out the wrong way.
Do you want me to tell her?
No, I just want you to call her
and bring her in to CTU.
I'll see her when I get back.
All right.
Are you sure you're comfortable doing this for me?
Of course.
Thank you.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, your swing arm needs to be replaced.
With parts you're looking at $475.
Yeah.We're open till 5:00.
Okeydoke.
Can I help you?
Do you have some kind of
precision tool for cutting metal?
Sure.
Where is everyone else?
Lunch.Why?
I need you to do some work for us.
And we need it done fast.
If you do it, you'll live.
Do you understand?
Yeah, yeah.
Just take it easy.
Why haven't I gotten an update?
Bauer left here on some sort of lead.
Find out if CTU is any closer
to recovering the nerve gas.
Yes, sir.
How are you feeling?
Remarkably well...
for someone whose husband tried to have her committed
without so much as a good-bye.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come here to fight with you.
You have every right to.
The two of us used to be a pretty good team.
Do you remember?
I was the one you would always come to first for advice.
I remember.
We've got to get back to that relationship, Charles.
You're right, things are going to get rough for you.
And you are going to need me
and everything that I can give you.
I don't know what to say, Martha.
Don't you ever do that to me again.
Mike, please, come in.
Mr.President.
Mrs.Logan.
Mike.
Mike, I owe you a profound apology.
You were in an impossible situation, sir.
I understand why you did what you did...
No.
I panicked, Mike, that's it.
Plain and simple.
I'm not proud of how I handled myself.
I intend to make it right
from this point on.
I'd like you to resume your duties.
Thank you, Mike.
CTU is in the process of tracking down
the canisters,
but we still have to deal
with the issue of Walt Cummings.
It's all right, Mike.
I would like Martha's input on this.
So what do we do about Walt?
We can't detain him indefinitely.
Maybe not, but we can keep him out of sight long enough
for us to construct a credible narrative.
Mike...
are you talking about a cover-up?
I mean, exercising discretion
to spare this country unnecessary humiliation.
Walt Cummings was complicit in David Palmer's assassination.
He has allowed these terrorists
to get their hands on weaponized nerve gas
- that is at this point  - With respect...
- a very real and present threat - With respect...
Mrs.Logan,
if we go public with Cummings,
the president's reputation won't be the only casualty.
The credibility of this office will be destroyed.
Charles, you are going to take a hit on this.
But you won't be destroyed.
You did nothing wrong except to trust someone
who betrayed you.
You are human.
You might be overestimating
the public's capacity for forgiveness.
No.I'm not.
The only thing they won't forgive
is being lied to.
I think you should issue a statement to the press,
and the sooner the better.
I agree.
Why don't you and I work on it together,
see what we come up with.
Great.
Chloe.
Go to Station 3.We don't have much time.
Thanks for getting me reinstated.
I only did it because I need your help
getting Jack through the high-security building,
not because I forgive you because I don't.
Have a seat.
We need to gain access to the security server
at 22 North Figueroa.
It's a proprietary network, so get to work.
Chloe?
I swear, I thought I was falling...
I don't care, Spencer.
CTU, they've got eyes and ears on building security.
We have two units,
one east, one west of the building.
Chloe, do you copy?
We're here, Jack.
Spenser's countervailing
the building's security protocols.
What are you talking about?
Spenser's under arrest.
Buchanan released him from holding.
Fine, just give me Rossler's position.
I've hacked into the building's motion sensors.
According to them, Rossler is still
in the penthouse.
I have two guards on the penthouse level.
What about the ground level entrance?
There's one guard, three surveillance cameras.
Okay.Stand by to take out all security cameras
that are covering the front desk and the elevators.
I can only shut them down for 60 seconds.
After that, they will reboot automatically.
That's as long as you have to subdue the lobby guard.
Copy that.
Teams A and B, you will remain in a holding position
till you get a "go" code.
We are three minutes out.
We have to cross the street
to get to Rossler's building.
Yes?
We're ready to cut
into the canisters.
You have to cut precisely ten centimeters
from the bottom of the casing
to reveal the trigger.
How thick is the outer casing?
Five millimeters.
Call me with the identification numbers when you're done.
We're in position.
We're set.We're ready to go.
Give me a few seconds to access control.
Okay.Here we go, Jack.
On my mark.
Camera's dark.
Federal agent.Let me see your hands!
Let me see your hands!
Elevator code, let's have it.
Uh...four, zero, seven, three, pound.
Unit one, status check.
Just lost cameras A and C.
Tell him you don't know why the cameras went down,
but everything is okay.
Everything is okay.
Status check: blue.
Don't know why the cameras are out.
Everything's fine down here.
Turn around.
Back up to me.Back up to me.
Where are the elevators?
The elevator's almost there.
You have two floors to go.
The camera reboots in ten seconds,
then you'll be visible.
Move.Move!
Unit one, status check.
Where are you?
You tell him you had to use the men's room.
Base,headed to the men's room.
Something's wrong.
Yes?
Mr.Rossler?
We may have a situation.
What kind of situation?
I'm not sure.
Please remain in your office
until you get the all clear.
The guards look suspicious.
One of them has an automatic weapon.
Copy that.
Federal Agents.
You okay?
Yeah.Go ahead.Get my vest.
- Rossler's on the move. - Where is he?
9:00.
Federal agent.Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon!
Put your hands behind your head.
Do it!
Interlock your fingers.
Rossler is in custody.
I repeat: Rossler is in custody.
All backup teams move in.I need a medic.
We're patching you into the Situation Room.
Someone else is in the penthouse, Jack.
Where?
In the bedroom, to your right.North side.
Curtis, cover him.
I got him.
Let me see your hands.
Let me see your hands!
Don't shoot.
Who are you?
I'm Inessa.
Who did that to you?
You are the police?
Counterterrorist unit, Los Angeles.
He is holding me here.
I want to go home.
You need to cut
into the outer casing exactly ten centimeters from the bottom.
The casting is five millimeters thick.
You cannot puncture the inner lining.
What's in these things?
Don't worry.Just do what I say.
Just...Can't you tell me what this is all about?
Do you have a family, Cal?
A wife.
My wife is in prison.
She's been there for seven years.
Her only crime was to support me while I fought for my country.
My son lives in a state-run facility
He does not even remember what I look like.
You want to know what this is about?
Justice.It's about ending tyranny.
When you're finished,
we will leave.
You won't hurt me?
You're not my enemy.
The government is my enemy.
Hey.
You have my word.
Begin.
It's all right.
You're all right.
Just take a seat.
You're safe now.
Have a medic take a look at her.
I want CT to do a full background check.
I don't mind that they've dressed his wound,
but make sure they don't give him anything for the pain.
Yes, sir.
Curtis.Put him in a chair.
All right, let's go.Get him up.
Easy on my leg.
Just get him over there.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with CTU.
25 minutes ago you contacted a man named Ivan Erwich.
What did he want you to do for him?
I want my lawyer.
You'll get a lawyer as soon as I get what I need.
Mr.Erwich is in possession of 20 canisters
of Sentox-VX nerve gas, which he has
threatened to deploy here in the United States.
I guess you have a problem.
No, sir.You have a problem.
You've been conspiring with and aiding a known terrorist
which means I get to hold you for as long as I want.
Now, we know Mr.Erwich can't deploy the canisters
unless he reconfigures the trigger mechanism.
Is that what he wanted you to do?
Trust me.You don't want to go down this road with me.
Go to hell.
That's exactly where I'm going to send you
unless you start to cooperate.
You like hurting girls?
Curtis.
When I finish with you,
you're gonna wish you felt this good again.
Where is Erwich?!
I want full immunity.
Unfreezing of all my assets.
And transport
to a foreign country of my choosing.
No.
I need Inessa.
She comes with me.
That's the deal.
Maybe I'm not making myself clear.
We're not making a deal.
Curtis.
Jack, it's Lynn.
Go ahead.
We don't have the luxury to engage in brinkmanship.
He's gonna tell us what we want to know.
You may be right, but we're not gonna wait around to find out.
Accept the deal.
That's an order.
Fine.It's your call.
We're signing off.
Make sure he follows through.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I've been instructed to accept your proposal.
A certified agreement,
signed by the Attorney General.
When I see that, I'll tell you what you want.
But remember,
I want Inessa.
Your immunity agreement is being drawn up.
Now I want something.
Where's Erwich?
I have no idea.
I don't know the man.
Not even what he looks like.
I first spoke with him 30 minutes ago.
We were put in contact through a mutual associate in Russia.
Who?
Sergei Voronov.
He's a commander in the resistance movement.
What's Erwich want?
He wants to reprogram the chip
of the trigger.
He's calling me back
with the identification keys.
What's your time frame?
Within the hour.
How is he going to receive the package?
I was going to deliver it.
We haven't agreed on a meeting place.
I want that chip.
It's in a safe place.
Once I see some paperwork,
I'll show it to you.
I want you to be ready to fit that chip with a transponder
so we can track him.
Okay.
Buchanan.
Bill, it's Jack.
Where are we with Rossler's immunity agreement?
We have the Attorney General's sanction.
You should have the documents in a few minutes.
Okay, good.
Did we get any information on the girl?
There isn't much.
Inessa Kovalevsky.
Reported missing 19 months ago from Kiev.
The assumption is, she was kidnapped
by traffickers in the sex slave trade.
She's 15, Jack.
15?
Okay, thanks, Bill.
I'll get back to you.
You can't take the girl.
Then you don't have a deal.
You'll have your immunity, your freedom.
Leave the girl out of this.
No.
Inessa is all I care about.
She comes with me,
or you lose Erwich.
I've almost finished compiling those surveillance protocols.
Whatever you have, port it over to Edgar's station.
Why?
He'll be finishing that task.
Fine.
Chloe, don't you understand?
I know.
I'm glad you do.
You don't work here anymore, Spenser.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
What?
Your reinstatement was temporary.
Just until we got Rossler into custody.
But there's still a lot of stuff that has to be done here.
We pulled people from Division.
We don't need you anymore.
These men will escort you out.
I know that was hard, but you did the right thing.
Shut up, Edgar.
You're right.We don't need that part.
Okay, "I promise a full and open inquiry
into this matter."
"I will not rest until I've restored"
"the faith that you have placed in this office"
"and I can demonstrate to you, the American people"
"that I bear its mantle of responsibility"
"with respect and deep humility."
See, this way,
you're assuming responsibility for Walt's actions,
but you're also personally taking the initiative
to bring him to justice.
Well, I'd like to run it by Mike, but I think it works.
I think it's the right move, Charles.
Thank you for letting me help you.
I'm glad to have your help.
Been a long time since you and I have worked together like this.
Yes?
Mr.President.Mike.
What is it, Mike?
I think you should come here.I'm in the west hallway.
What's going on?
Just come here, sir.
I'm on my way.
Good.
Cut him down.
Thanks for meeting me.You got the money?
Jenny, I'm not here to bring you money.
Here's the name of a doctor.
He's a good man.I want you to call him.
I'll pay all the expenses.
It won't cost you a cent.
We'll call him together.
I can't.
Don't hurt him.Oh, my God.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Come on!
Rossler's been given a shot for the pain.
We have air and land pursuit units on standby.
As soon as he moves out, we'll be ready.
No one's going anywhere unless Erwich makes that call.
Stand by the phones.Excuse me.
Audrey Raines.
It's me.
Hey.Did you manage to get a hold of Kim?
No.I tried her, but she wasn't in.
I left a message.
Would you mind trying again for me, please?
Sure.
Okay, thanks.
I want to contact my family.
They must be so very worried about me.
I-I need to explain something to you first.
Please, sit down.
For now...
we need you to go with Mr.Rossler.
Just-Just for now.
Men like me, agents, are going to follow you.
And when we get what we need from Mr.Rossler,
they're going to move in
and they're gonna take you away from him.
You don't know what he does to me when we're alone.
I promise you, I won't let him be alone with you.
I don't believe you.
I won't do it.
Please, let...
Let me go.
I'm sorry.I can't.
Then you are no different than Rossler.
I am not Rossler.
Look at me.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I promise.
We need you to get dressed, please.
Thank you.
Good job.
That's it.
Load the canisters.Get rid of the body.
Pick it up.
Yes?
We have the identification keys.
I'm messaging them to you now.
I've got them.
How long will it take you to reprogram the chip
and deliver it back to us?
I'll be ready in ten minutes.
You and I need a place where we can meet.
You're coming personally?
Unless you have someone who can install
and program a coded binary chip.
I'll call you back in five minutes with the location.
I'll be here.
Get him set up for a wire.
I'll get the girl.
Yes, sir.
Mr.Rossler, in a minute,
we're going to be implanting a transmitter.
We're ready to go.
It's going to be fine.
What's happening?
Couldn't complete the trace.
We've narrowed it down to a ten-block radius.
Okay.Thanks.
No! Hold your fire!
Get a medic in here now!
Inessa, give me the gun.
I know you don't want to hurt anybody else.
Is he gonna make it?
No.He's dead.
Rossler was our only link to those canisters.
Erwich's gonna call here any minute.
He's gonna expect to talk to him.