go,go,go,go!
Clear. Clear.
We clear here .
Surveillance had them all
going inside 45 minutes ago.
Did anyone bail out
on the perimeter?
No,ma'am. All secure out here.
Boss,this isn't a meth lab.
So why an escape tunnel?
Need to take a look at this.
Hotchner.
When?
Did they raise the terror alert?
No,that's probably best.
All right,get everybody in now.
I'll be there in a minute.
What's going on?
Nothing. I just have
to go to the office.
It's 6:15,and you're talking
about a terror alert?
It's bad,isn't it?
I don't know yet.
Please don't lie to me.
It might be.
I may not be home tonight.
I mean,I might be home late.
I know.
Shoot. I forgot.
Tomorrow is the day we scheduled to
take jack to have his pictures taken.
Don't worry about it.
I'll reschedule.
No,no,no,no. Go
ahead and take him,
and I'll do my best
to be there,ok?
Just come back safely.
I will.
Bye.
Everybody,meet agent prentiss.
you had a date. I've been
filling her in on protocol.
- Derek morgan.
- Emily prentiss.
We can make nice later.
What do we know?
The dea raided what they thought was a hardened
meth lab right here in northern virginia,
but they found this instead.
That could be a dispersal
device for a chemical weapon.
Sophisticated.
Homeland security's thinking al qaeda.
They've developed devices that span
the spectrum of sophistication,
some as simple as soda
bottles and paint cans.
They're called al ikhteraa.
- Literally "the invention."
- They are.
Do we know what the biological
or chemical agent is yet?
No,not yet.
The cell members bailed
out through a tunnel.
The dea recovered a nextel 2-way
and managed to intercept a message.
That's not the transcript.
No,it's in arabic.
our friends surprised
us and eloped.
We can no longer wait for
the wedding as planned.
We can deliver our gift
at the next crescent.
I lived in several middle
eastern countries growing up.
Next crescent?
Muslims sometimes
use a lunar calendar.
- I'd have to look it up...
- next crescent moon is in 2 days.
So whatever they're attacking,it's
happening in less than 48 hours.
It sounds like it,sir.
Payment for the nextel
is linked to this man.
Jind allah.
Literally soldier of god.
That's pretty poor operational
security for a sophisticated plot.
2 months ago,jind allah was
captured leaving the U.S.
Using a forged pakistani passport
via richmond international airport.
He's been held as a ghost detainee
in guantanamo bay ever since.
So technically,he doesn't exist.
Soldier of god isn't a name.
No,it's most likely a name taken
on for the jihad,meaning struggle.
Extremists claim it's a holy war.
Yet the words "holy" and "war"
never appear together in the qu'ran.
Do we know his real name?
Cia interrogators have gotten
nothing out of the guy.
They need us to break him.
We do know from past intercepts
that he's a recruiter.
He came into this country
to assemble the omega cell,
a sleeper cell with
an unknown mission.
We have 48 hours to do what the cia
hasn't been able to manage in 2 months.
We could be looking at the first
attack on our soil since 9/11.
Hey. Car here? I told
reid 5 minutes.
I think you should take
prentiss with you to guantanamo.
Excuse me?
She could be of help.
I don't know enough
about her abilities.
There's plenty for
her to do back here.
I don't know what she's capable of either,
but we've got to find out sooner or later.
Well,it's an interrogation,
not a training exercise.
She's the only member of
the team fluent in arabic.
Well,there are other translators.
Yeah,but they haven't
studied behavior.
She ever have her ready bag yet?
My guess is there isn't much
this woman's unprepared for.
Car leaves in 4 minutes.
Yes,sir.
The old term used,
some of the best lessons are
learned from past mistakes.
The error of the past is
the wisdom of the future.
Excuse me,sir.
I just wanted to let you
know how much I appreciate--
do not thank me.
- Sir?
- It's not a favor.
Of course. I know that.
You're coming to do a job.
Do you think the interrogation
of jind allah will work in time?
Interrogation's the most
dynamic form of profiling.
That's not an answer.
Sir.
He's been locked away in gtmo.
He doesn't know we raided
the cell's safe house.
That's an advantage for us.
The main thing is to get
him talking about anything.
Then his language and body
movements will betray him.
It's like this-- you just focus on
the way your opponent holds his piece.
How quickly and firmly he places it.
Then you watch his face and body.
It'll telegraph a player's
strategy,his training,
maybe his motivations.
Is that what you need us to do?
No. I need you to listen.
You're fluent in arabic.
I won't know the
nuances like you.
Every word,every phrase.
Be on the lookout for
subtext,ulterior meanings.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to watch for tells.
Non-verbals,micro-expressions.
Watch him when he's
comfortable and relaxed,
then note the behavioral changes
when he's under stress.
If we can establish a baseline,we'll be able
to read him once I challenge his belief systems.
Before I can get him to give
up where or how they'll attack,
I'll first have to cause him
to reveal something of himself.
Game oveR.
What are you talking about?
Gtmo's runway is perpendicular
to cuban airspace,
so approaching aircraft have to negotiate a last
minute 90 degree right turn in order to land.
They call it the gtmo twist.
I was winning.
Actually,he would
have had you in 3.
- Bonnie ryan.
- Aaron hotchner.
Dea team. We ran this raid.
Derek morgan.
This must have slowed
you down some,huh?
Enough for them to get
out through the tunnel.
They must have done escape drills.
Hey,morgan.
Hey,kenny. Been a minute,man.
Yeah.
- We good in here?
- Yeah,
don't worry about it.
Everything's been rendered safe.
These guys weren't
messing around.
Hotch,these tubes surround what
would be the explosive charge.
And this cylinder right here?
It's gotta be where they put whatever
bio or chem agent they plan on dispersing.
That's happy thought.
Yeah. Tell me about it.
Looks like a 4 man cell.
They assimilated
into the community.
Just like any other suburban gangster
wannabes rolling at the mall.
Who do you think we're dealing with?
Most likely middle eastern males
in their early twenties.
And judging by that device out there,
they're looking at significant targets:
Military installations,
government buildings.
You must be the bau boys.
And gal. Pardon me.
- I'm jason gideon.
- Andy bingaman,fbi.
Agent prentiss,dr. Reid.
I'm the intelligence
supervisor here at gtmo.
You guys having a hard time
getting jind allah to talk?
Not only can't they get him
to budge,but 2 weeks ago,
word got out that one of the other
detainees was spilling secrets.
Jind allah managed to have a 3 minute
conversation with him in the shower line.
That night,the other
detainee committed suicide.
He's reciting the
qu'ran from memory.
He's most likely a hafez.
He must have done it a dozen times
since he's come to this facility.
Some muslim children are
able to do it since age 12.
2 months of interrogation,that's all the
cia's been able to get out of him.
There are cuts and bruises
under his right eye socket.
What kind of tactics are they using?
I control the actions
to the detainees,
but I can assure you,my protest
about their methods has been ignored.
Let the interrogation
proceed normally.
I'm gonna interrupt and
demand they stop harassing.
Maybe I should tell
them in advance.
No,it's better if
they don't expect it.
The reaction will be more
visceral,more believable.
- Go ahead with phase 2 as planned.
- Got you
You really gonna put a
show on for these guys?
No,no for them.
For jind allah.
He's needs to see me as a complete contrast
to what he's come to expect from his captors.
It's the best way to jump
start him into talking.
We have less than 36 hours.
Have at it.
You 2 ready?
- Yeah,this way.
- Thank you.
Do you understand?
Every day--
who the hell are you?
Supervisory special
agent jason gideon.
I'm an fbi behavioral analyst.
It's time to show this
man some respect.
You gotta be kidding me.
You have orders from
agent bingaman to leave
so I can speak with
this detainee alone.
I'm sorry for the
treatmentyou've suffered.
If you don't mind,I'd like to
spend some time with you.
He stopped his recitation.
He's sizing gideon up.
If I don't mind?
Like to get to know you as a person.
Your faith,your ideology.
To what end?
Studying human
behavior is what I do.
You know,if these guys
are fundamentalists,
you'd think they'd have
qu'rans,prayer mats.
No. We didn't find
any of that here.
They must have at least
one other location.
Ryan,
hotch.  what is it ?
That looks like a
list of chemicals.
I'm gonna check with garcia.
Go,doll.
Hey,I'm gonna read off a
list to you. it's criminals
I'd like to believe,with
greater understanding one day,
we can come to a peaceful
resolution of our differences.
Is that so?
Look,I don't know what you've done
or what you may have planned to do.
But unlike the other detainees here,
you have the education,intelligence
to convey the nuances of your culture.
That's what interests me.
Until I don't give you what you want.
Then you will resort to other tactics.
I swore an oath to uphold
the united states constitution,
no matter where I am,no
matter who I deal with.
You're sure?
All right.
What'd she say?
Garcia says this looks like a list of
additives needed to weaponize anthrax.
could they get enough anthrax?
The letter sent to senator tom daschle's office
in 2002 only contained 2 grams of purified spores,
enough to kill 25 million people
if effectively distributed.
Are you willing to have a chat with me?
Go ahead. Good.
Let's chat.
He's from egypt. Cairo.
You sure?
No,he could be yemeni,but
odds are he's egyptian.
What type of name is gideon?
American.
I often forget that in your country you
put your country first and your god last.
Sir,he was born and raised in egypt.
They pronouce "j" sounds as a "G."
You don't consider yourself
egyptian as well as muslim?
Egyptian.
In 2 minutes,you know more about me
than those thugs found out in 2 months.
They and I have very,very different
motives and methodologies.
And yet your country relies
on them to protect you from us.
Sometimes they're
their own worst enemy.
Yeah. Who is your worst
enemy,agent gideon?
It's not a who.
It's a what.
Ignorance.
You're a very honest man.
And you?
Must have become a hafez by what,age 10?
9.
Any person with the discipline and dedication
to memorize the entire qu'ran by age 9
must have a very serious reason
to choose a life of violence.
Perhaps.
We are through already?
No,not at all.
The sun is about to set.
Mecca's in that direction.
I'll have a prayer rug
and water bowl sent in.
What the heck is going on here?
The nsa is routing all messages
to us for language analysis.
You know,rumor has it,much to my chagrin,
that during national security emergencies,
our fair country turns all of its satellites homeward
and records all electronic traffic in the whole U.S.A
Is this even legal?
Yeah,I don't really want to
think about that right now.
Somewhere in this slew of chatter could be a shred
of something that could save a whole lot of lives.
All right,well,cross reference
gift with wedding allusions.
They'll be consistent with their code.
Here's something.
It rained all over the wedding,but
the gift is waiting in the barn.
When was that call made?
Looks like just
over 2 hours ago.
Let's run the words
"barn and "wedding" through.
The wedding will now be held at
vincent's barn off link and annandale.
Route the gift for delivery.
That's not a gift I wanna get.
I'll call hotch.
Yeah,jj.
We think we just found the
cell's backup location.
It looks like a construction
site in annandale,virginia.
Sounds like they may have
another device ready to arm.
I'll get agent ryan to organize another
raid. And notify gideon and reid.
Ok.
Can I offer you some water?
I offer you some first.
They only kept it there to
show me what I could not have.
I'd like you to explain something to me.
How can you ignore the fact
that muhammad preached
passivitywhile he was in mecca?
Do no violence.
His later message from
medina was perfectly clear.
When violence come upon you,
you must fight back with violence.
He's quoting from the
hadith,not from the qu'ran.
It's called the verse of the sword.
They argue that it cancels
out earlier teachings.
Verse of the sword.
Just someone's spin on
the words of the prophet.
It's not even part of the qu'ran.
But it does say in the qu'ran fight and
slay the infidels wherever you find them
and seize them in every stratagem of war.
Unless they repent.
Establish regular prayers
and practice regular charity.
Is it your intention,mr. Gideon,
to become a man of faith
and revert to islam?
I am a man of faith.
I have repented,I pray regularly,
and I practice charity.
I have never committed
violence against you,
so how is it that my faith would allow
you to live and worship as you please,
and yours would take my
life and snuff it out?
You are simply misguided
people of the book.
- But if you revert to islam...
- a billion muslims...
one billion muslims manage to
practice their faith in peace...
for allah is surely merciful.
You...
inquired about my childhood earlier.
I will tell you...
that it was a happy one until
one day a bomb fell out of the sky
and leveled the bazaar that
I was in with my family.
I was only 8.
Must have been horrifying
for such a young boy.
He's opening
up about himself.
Maybe.
We need to verify
what he's saying,though.
Speak.
Garcia,I need you to
check something for me.
I'm looking for a stray bombing in a bazaar
somewhere in egypt approximately 30 years ago.
Ok,greaT. That's not too obscure.
I don't need you to give me details.
We're just trying to set a baseline
for jind allah's truthfulness.
I just need to know if
it happened at all.
- When I know,you'll know.
- Thank you.
When the rubble was cleared...
half...
of my family was dead.
It was on that day that I swore
my life to vengeance for allah.
And for that very reason those holding
you here can never let you leave.
Your only hope is to tell me so I can hopefully
one day share your struggle with the world.
Your government won't
even admit that I exist.
How possibly can you tell
my side of the story?
Hey,guys,we want silence.
No conversation.
Let's be careful. We don't
know what to expect.
- Ready?
- Ready. Let's do it.
Clear!
This place is completely empty.
We missed them again.
You got gideon,prentiss,and me.
It's hotch. We're at
cell location number 2.
No cell members,no lab,no dispersal devices.
We're still looking for escape tunnels.
Call us.
We're running out of time. The attack's
supposed to take place in less than 24 hours.
So getting jind allah to talk is
our only chance of finding them.
Time I confronted him with the truth.
What are you going to do?
Show him my hand.
I'm going to give you the respect
of telling you what just happened.
A team of agents raided
an omega cell location.
Actually,both of them.
Our men are in place in
annandale as we speak.
You gain nothing by remaining silent.
Jihad is forever.
Something's wrong.
His hands.
Gideon,something's wrong.
This guy seemed relieved
by what you just told him.
Excuse me.
- What's the problem?
- Get everybody out of there.
Now! Now! Now!
Everybody out.
It's a trap. Now!
I said out! Go!
How did a terror cell get its hands on anthrax
without a single lab reporting a security breach?
Would we know if a foreign lab had a breach?
A foreign lab? Actually,no.
Garcia,isn't annandale where
morgan and hotch are?
That's not a gas main explosion.
Please pick up.
Please pick up. Please pick up.
Yeah,it's morgan.
Hello? Garcia,can you hear me?
We saw the explosion on tv.
Yeah,I know. We lost a swat agent.
Oh,god.
Don't worry. Don't think you're
gonna get rid of me that easy.
Do you need anything?
I know who to call if I
do. Thanks,baby doll.
That's ok.
Is he all right?
Yeah.
We lost a swat agent.
Son of a bitch.
Sorry about that.
Yeah,me,too.
The chatter was a set-up.
They knew we'd be listening.
They led us straight here.
Just tell me you know
where to look next.
Not yet.
They ok?
We were right about the trap.
It was rigged to explode.
A swat agent was killed.
- Was anthrax involved?
- No.
Then that's not the final target.
You look troubled,my friend.
You killed one of my men.
I was here with you.
The second location was a trap.
One of my agents was
killed in the explosion.
This is war.
We expect casualties.
Shouldn't you?
He was a good man.
Well... if he would convert,
there would be no reason
for him to fear death.
What do you say to his family?
I say...
where... were you to mourn...
when my son was murdered?
His son?
Did you see that?
When he told the story
about his childhood,
the bomb landing in the
bazaar,his behavior changed.
We know he was lying.
Garcia couldn't find any record of a
bombing during the time jind allah was a boy.
Exactly,but this time when he mentioned
his son,he looked at his hands,
like he had to concentrate
to control his anger.
That first story wasn't about him.
It was about his son.
Which means it must
have been more recent.
Garcia.
I need you to look for a
bombing again in egypt,
but this time anything
in the last 10 years.
On it.
We're looking for civilian
casualties,an 8-year-old boy.
Ok. I'm cross referencing
bombings and child victims.
7 years ago,in the heart of cairo,
egyptian government
blamed hezbollah,
but conspiracy theories on the
street claimed it was a joint U.S
Israli strike that went astray.
Your gross detainee's
name is jamal abaza.
How about his son's name?
Do you have that?
Amir abaza. 8. Killed in the blast.
All right. Find out everything you
can on that. I'll get back to you soon.
We know his real identity.
It appears that there will be no peaceful
resolution to our difficulties after all.
I haven't given up that hope.
It's time for your
salut-ul-isha prayers.
May we speak again tomorrow?
You are asking me?
Yes.
Tomorrow,then.
Jamal abaza's been in
the U.S. For a while.
He volunteered as the prison imam at the
dearfield correctional center 3 years ago.
How could the cia not know that?
They're focused overseas.
We're domestic.
Yeah. They probably sent a request
for a domestic information search,
and it's somewhere making
its way through channels.
If he was a prison imam,he must have
recruited militant islamic society members.
M.I.S. Is an atypical
prison organization.
They pick up an amalgam
of ethnicities.
The qu'ran says that my lord...
those that slip through the cracks are
the ones that traditional groups won't accept.
Outside these walls,you
need to understand...
it's made up largely of
american citizens.
American citizens with a reason
for hating the government.
We're looking at
home grown terrorists.
What the hell do you want?
The name jamal abaza. Does
it mean anything to you?
Abaza was an imam in cairo.
He preached jihad to his followers,
but he fell off the grid 7 years ago.
That's because when his son died,
he took the jihad name jind allah.
He came to america to
recruit sleeper cells.
You're telling us that that
detainee in there is jamal abaza?
Amazing what you learn
when you talk to people.
He was also a prison imam
in virginia 3 years ago.
Are you familiar with the
militant islamic society?
They're home grown?
We know the cell that abaza put
together has access to anthrax,
but we can't find any reports of
any going missing in the states.
We have protocols that
we have to follow.
You really going to allow
a terrorist attack on U.S.
Soil because of protocols?
I told you what I learned in
there because you and I,fbi,cia,
right now we have the ability to break
through all the protocol and share information.
Let me see what we have.
Coordinate with agent jareau
and penelope garcia at quantico.
Please.
Think it'll work?
I don't know.
Cia's tough. They play it
pretty close to the vest.
Well,if we don't all work
together,more people are gonna die.
A lot more.
How goes it with the cia?
I don't know what
gideon said to them,
but they are feeding me
information like crazy.
- They sure do generate intelligence.
- Yeah.
Hopefully not too
much to interpret.
Slept well?
For the first time
since I've been here.
Good.
Until yesterday,
I was not permitted
regular prayer.
We receive comfort
from our prayers.
- We?
- Human beings.
I say something wrong?
You placed us on the same level.
Aren't we?
Well,here I am thought
of as less than human.
And in your jihad,I am.
Gideon...
what do you really want from me?
I already told you.
I want to understand you.
And if that is not possible?
Then that would be my loss.
It's almost time for your midday
prayers. May I return later?
- I look forward to it.
- Thank you.
Most of these tips are so new they
haven't even been authenticated yet.
Yeah,but there's nothing in the established
information that's remotely helpful.
Wait a minute. Anthrax.
- What?
- Genimmune.
A dutch biotech firm reported that they may have
had a security breach involving anthrax last week.
May have?
They're still doing a
security and inventory sweep,
but they may be missing up to
20 grams of lab grade anthrax.
20 grams.
Could potentially kill a
quarter billion people.
He seems much calmer
than he was yesterday.
May make any reading of his
body language less accurate.
I know.
Is that what we want?
I hope so.
Well,isn't that the exact opposite of--
he hopes so?
We have less than 10 hours before
the new crescent moon rises.
9.
Aren't you worried?
I've been with him long
enough to trust him.
Cia is funneling you their
dutch terror watch list.
Ok,I can cross reference that with any port of
entry information we have as well as customs
and immigration enforcement.
You know,it would sure be a lot easier if there
was a centralization of all this information.
Oh,dream on,J.
No one wants the other kids
peeing in their sand box.
Tariq muhammad. Dutch
citizen,islamic convert.
Traveled here 4 days ago
under his original name.
Andre janssen.
And we have the address he
listed on his customs form.
Thank you.
- We just got a lead.
- Got a name?
And an address.
How does a terrorist cell
exist right here in mayberry?
Infrared scanning still
shows no one inside.
We're doing a soft entry in
case it's booby trapped.
Sir,get in here!
We have 5 deceased males and
what looks to be a crude lab,
all shot in the
head execution style.
Any anthrax on the scene?
Only residue.
There's also packing and
tags from 4 new backpacks.
All right,listen up.
- Backpacks?
- They're already on the move. We're too late.
have you finished?
As you said,the sun is set.
Yes.
I'd like you to meet a
colleague of mine. Dr.Reid.
- May we speak?
- Of course.
I have a little time.
That was a joke.
I have all the time. Please.
A joke.
Well,we're making progress.
Yes,progress. That is true.
Is there no way for this
thing to end? This jihad?
The jihad will end when
allah wills its end.
Then how will you know
that it is allah's will?
When the jihad ends.
I have been lying to you.
Of course you have.
My colleague has been outside
watching us as we talked on monitors.
Watching your body language,
trying to figure you out.
Were you successful?
Somewhat.
Your name is jamal abaza.
Your son amir was killed in 2003 in the
bombing at the mahfouz bazaar in cairo.
Since then,you've been recruiting M.I.S
Members in prison by convincing them
that U.S. Economic policies
are exploiting third word nations
and turned them into extreme fundamentalists
by promising a better existence with allah.
I would say that you were
more than somewhat successful.
But I did not learn
where your M.I.S. Cell was going
to make an anthrax attack in the U.S.
At the new crescent tonight.
I have no knowledge
of such a thing.
Yes,you do,mr.Abaza.
And there is still time.
What?
Are you sure?
something has happened?
How could you?
You choose to contort islam into
an excuse for a life of violence.
You have perverted your
faith to justify murder.
Now we are finally
chatting,gideon.
You accuse americans of being
puppeteers of the third world,
yet you used your own people's faith
tonight to make them dance for you.
Why?
Why is it always those who profess to
be the most fervent believers in this war,
they always manipulate other
people to die for them.
Does your president
go to battle?
Or does he send your children?
Tonight...
all those innocent people.
There is no such thing,
gideon. They were infidels.
And they were engaged in activities that
spread american policies over the entire world.
Your incessant need to own things,
material things.
Your capitalism rests on the
back of third world countries.
No one's hands are clean.
No one is innocent.
Those people tonight,
they were innocent.
They never hurt you.
They hurt me by existing.
Yes,the infidels shall fall
at the hands of the righteous.
And that is when the
jihad will end.
So you are ready to
murder 4 billion people.
America has learned
nothing from the past.
You harden targets
like your power plants,
but you leave the soft
root for our taking.
What has happened tonight will
affect your economy for years,
the way september 11th
affected air travel.
And maybe the next time a
giant shopping center opens,
people will think
twice before going.
And maybe next it
will be a school.Hey!
You can shut the video
feed down now,garcia.
Has the sun not set yet?
No.
No...
A shopping center.A mall.
It's a grand opening tonight
not long after sunset.
That gives you about an hour.
God help us if they don't make iT.
Let's just hope we
have somewhere to go.
Grand opening of the
usa mall today.
It's the third largest in the country,and it's
right smack in the middle of mclean,virginia.
Let's move.
What's going on with you?
You look like you've
seen a ghost back there.
Haley's supposed to take jack to the
new mall to have his portrait taken.
Well,go ahead and call her.
It's a breach of security.
You lose haley and jack,
screw this job.
You won't have a life.
I can't reach her.
Morgan,I'm going to find
the security office.
Morgan!
Looks like loading
dock security.
- Should we evacuate?
- No,no.
We'd have mass panic.Let's go.
Hello!
- Fbi.
- Fbi?
Are these all your security cameras?
Yes,sir.
What's this camera here?
That's the roof. East end.
Morgan,I've got 4 guys on
the east end of the roof.
What's on that
side of the roof?
Nothing.
No access doors to the mall?
Not unless you go
through the air vents.
Morgan,it's the air vents.
They're going for the air vents.
Don't move!
Put the devices down and put
your hands where I can see them!
Gun!
Police tonight foiled an apparent
robbery attempt at the new usa mall,
which presumably have marred an
otherwise successful grand opening.
Haley?
Hey,in here.
You're home.
Did you see that there was an
attempted robbery at the new mall?
I'm glad I cancelled
jack's photos.
I just decided I
wanted you to be there.
It's better if we
do it as a family.
Is everything ok?
Yeah,everything's perfect.
Ralph waldo emerson once said in order to
learn the most important lessons of life,
one must each day surmount a fear.
When did you know you were
gonna have to trick him?
The first time I talked to him.
You realized you couldn't break him?
Well,I realized he was too smart to have had
that nextel phone registered to him accidentally.
He drew us there.
He wanted our presence at gtmo
to confirm that he was successful.
And that's when you started
moving up the time of his prayers.
If I'd used an actual clock,
he might have caught on.
So it was all a chess game.
We won this round...
but you heard him.
Jihad never ends.
Mate.
I quit.
Yield.Surrender.
Capitulate.I'm
gonna take a nap.
Prentiss.
Sir?
You play?
Yes,sir. I play.