Previously
on criminal minds...
elle, 2 weeks
of pure heaven.
Do not call me
for anything.
Have a great time.
You all deserve a break.
Welcome to paradise.
Your resort
is beautiful.
A man said there had
been a murder
in room 19.
Get down!
Aah!
Who are you?!
Where is
the victim's head?
I'm here on vacation.
From jamaica.
Someone sent you a head?
Morgan and elle are
in jamaica right now.
Agent greenaway
wasn't even here
when this man was killed.
How did he know
where we were?
Jj: A man came to the door
with something
he said you would need
right away.
He came to the door?
Garcia: I was playing
a game yesterday.
The hacker
could have gotten
into my computer first.
I have far less protection
on my own laptop.
How could you be
that stupid?
I found him.
You what?
I know who he is,
the hacker,
his name's geist.
Unsub:
Now you're on a quest.
A young girl's life
depends
on the successful completion
of it.
Aah! Aah!
The one rule is,
only the members of your team
may participate
in the quest.
Reid: He's
given us all the clues
needed to complete
this quest,
including this book code.
Each one of these sets
of numbers represents
a particular word.
From what book?
Jj, get some reporters
here as soon as possible.
Morgan: Didn't he say
that we had to keep this
under the team?
We're looking
for this man...
no, no, no, no,
i said no outsiders.
I'm awake.
Anderson,
take greenaway home.
Yes, sir.
Get some sleep.
I told you,
it was one rule.
One rule!
www.1000fr.com Present
Sync:FRM@¹·ÐÜ&¾ÆÄÒ·¹´ü
Gideon: "the defects
and faults of the mind
"are like wounds
in the body.
"After all imaginable care
has been taken
"to heal them up,
still there will be
a scar left behind."
French writer
francois la rochefoucauld.
Sir, i thought
you'd want to know.
We identified
the girl in the video...
rebecca bryant.
Leave it on the desk.
Reid, how many books
do you think are
published in a year?
In the whole world?
Thousands.
Great, and all
we gotta do is find one.
You know,
i can see this unsub
gettin' our phone numbers
and addresses
from the bureau
personnel files,
but come on, man,
it really says in there
that gideon digs nellie fox?
Or that jj collects
butterflies?
I didn't even know
these things about us.
"Ever would it be night,
but always clear day
to any man's sight."
Reid, not again with the poem
from the music box, please.
There's something
familiar about it.
I think i've heard
it somewhere before.
Thought you had
a photographic memory.
Eidetic memory,
and that's
primarily related
to things i read.
Like i said,
this is something
i think i've heard.
Which leaves us...
nowhere, that's
where it leaves is.
Gideon: Not necessarily.
How would we proceed
if we didn't have
all these clues?
What's the first thing
we'd look at?
Victimology.
Why this particular victim
in this particular place
at this particular time?
We have a victim,
don't we?
Rebecca bryant.
Missin' out of
south boston, virginia.
You can get there
in a few hours
if you hurry.
Take jj. Find out
everything there is
to know about this girl.
Morgan: You go it.
Been lettin' him
lead us around
like he's somethin'
more than he is.
He's just
another unsub.
Let's start puttin'
together a profile.
What you want me
to do?
Just keep
workin' on this.
If anybody can
put it together, you can.
[Coughing]
Please help me.
Anderson?
Where's agent greenaway?
Sir?
I told you
to take her home.
I dropped her off
half an hour ago.
Take her home
does not mean
drop her off.
We're dealing
with an unsub
who has all of our
personal information,
including
our home addresses.
Get back
over there now.
But...
now.
[Airplane engines]
Agent greenaway?
Yes?
Case file, please.
How did i get here?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Without a case file,
you'll have to get off.
The rules are very...
clear!
[Telephone rings]
Female paramedic:
She's back.
Male paramedic: Get
a large bore going.
If we don't get
this pressure up,
we're gonna
lose her again...
permanently.
"possible book titles."
Thousands of books
published every year.
This is impossible.
Year... every year.
1963.
Agent hotchner?
Yes?
The delivery guy's
on the way up.
The one from
the press conference?
Thank you.
The book has to be
the right volume
and the right
publication date,
or the code
won't work, right?
Ok.
Now when you talk
about nellie fox,
it's in regards
to the 1959 white sox.
That's the year that's
important to you,
but for some reason,
this is a 1963 card.
Well, maybe
he couldn't find a '59.
You think a pale
clouded yellow butterfly
was easy to find,
or a music box
that specifically plays
the trout quintet?
So a book published
in 1963.
It has to be.
Maybe.
The guy who delivered
the puzzle to my house
just turned himself in.
You delivered a package
to my house yesterday.
Do i need
a lawyer here?
Late in the day
to my wife.
L... i guess i could
check my logs.
You know exactly
which delivery we mean.
Look, this guy comes
up to me on the street
with the package.
He says it only
needs to go a few miles,
and that a girl's life
depended on it.
And you didn't
find that suspicious?
He said a girl's life
depended on it, man.
I wasn't gonna
take no chances
with somethin' like that.
I see, so you're
a humanitarian here then.
Yeah, i guess
you could say that.
How much?
Thousand...
cash.
Seriously,
do i need a lawyer?
This guy is
infuriatingly good.
He routed
his ip through
major corporations,
crisscrossed
it through countries,
bounced it
off satellites.
I thought you
already tracked the hacker.
Did giles's apartment
have that?
He didn't have
a couch.
Exactly. Giles was
a smokescreen
i should
have seen through.
But now i have
this glorious program i wrote,
tracking the hacker
through his other identity...
sir kneighf.
"K-n-e-l-g-h-f."
That's an odd spelling.
Do you need something?
Yeah, is
there a database,
which lists
all the books published
in a given year?
Individual publishers
have lists,
but i don't think
there's anything
like a master one,
plus it would depend
upon the year,
because the further back
you go,
the less likely there'll
be any database at all.
1963.
Yeah, ok, that
would be an example
of extremely less likely.
Could you
do me a favor?
Type something
into a search engine
for me?
"Never
would it be night,
but always clear day
to any man's sight."
Ok, that's from a poem,
"the parliament of..."
"fowls!"
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Chaucer, my... my mom
use to read me that.
It's widely considered
as the first
valentine's poem.
Your mom read you
valentine's poems?
Hello, therapy.
Chaucer.
Chaucer,
"parliament of fowls."
Fowls,
"parliament of fowls,"
chaucer.
It has to be at least
283 pages long,
but the poem
has to be longer.
Something published
in 1963.
A butterfly indigenous
to great britain. Why?
Something born, something
from great britain.
Medieval.
Medieval, chaucer.
Chaucer was middle english.
Middle english spelling
of the word "fowls..."
there was
a contemporary british
author... fowles.
John fowles.
Will you type it
into a search engine?
Uh...
he wrote the magus,
he wrote the french
lieutenant's woman.
Anything in 1963
in great britain?
The collector.
Collector...
baseball cards,
skeleton keys,
music boxes.
These are things
that are collected.
Reid.
Hotchner:
What'd he look like?
I don't really know.
He had a big coat on
and a hat pulled down
over his face.
So you can't describe
him at all then?
Well, the part of his face
that i could see
was all messed up.
It was messed up?
Yeah... scarred,
all burned up.
[Line ringing]
Gideon: Burn scars.
Could explain
the trouble moving.
We know what the book is.
The collector
by john fowles.
You sure?
Not absolutely.
Not until we see
if the code works,
but i have
4 separate libraries
searching
for the 1963 edition
published in great britain.
Well done, reid.
Agent gideon, there's
a call for you on line 2,
says it's
extremely urgent.
Is there a name?
Sort of. He calls himself
the fisher king.
This could be
the unsub, guys.
Why?
In mythology,
the fisher king
is the grail king.
"Sir kneighf,"
it's an anagram...
for "fisher king."
Fisher king's
at the end
of all grail quests.
Line 2 trapped
and traced.
Gideon.
What i had to do
was not my fault.
Excuse me?
It was distasteful
and barbaric.
Who is this?
No one else
had to be hurt.
Call yourself
"the fisher king"?
I told you
there were rules.
I'm actually more interested
in exactly how you got
all those burns.
Remember this
next time you decide
to step outside
my instructions.
Agent greenaway did not
have to die like that.
Daddy?
Doctor: Notify the o.r.
She's bleeding out.
They're gonna need
4 units of "o"
on the rapid infuser.
Yes, ma'am.
Fight with me here.
Fight.
Fbi, one of my agents
was just brought in.
Agent hotchner,
i am sorry.
Anderson, where is she?
I got there just
as the ambulance
was leaving.
Where is she,
anderson?
They just took her
up to surgery.
Then she's alive.
What do we know?
The local p.d. Said
someone forced
her back door
and surprised her
in the living room.
They were probably laying
in wait for her.
After she was...
it appears
she dialed 911 herself
before she passed out.
Why weren't we
notified?
The offender apparently
took her i.d. And gun.
The uniform i talked to
didn't even know
she was in the bureau
until i arrived on scene.
Get back over there.
This is a federal
crime scene.
Nobody touched anything.
We process it.
Go.
Yes, sir.
[Beep]
Mrs. Valez,
are you there?
Woman, on speakerphone:
Yes, dr. Reid, i am.
I have a first edition
of the collector,
published in great britain
in 1963, doctor.
Wonderful.
Mrs. Valez, i'm gonna
read you a set
of 3 numbers.
The first is gonna be
a page number,
the second a line number
on that page,
and the third,
a word number
in that line.
Do you understand me?
Yes, i understand.
All right, the first
is page 222.
Mrs. Valez:
Page 222. got it.
Line 23.
Line 23. got it.
What is the 16th word
on that line, ms. Valez?
"The."
"The"?
Great.
Page 91,
line 11, word 13.
"Path."
Does that make sense?
"The path." yeah,
that absolutely
makes sense.
All right, please
go to page 31...
trap and trace
got nothin'.
Unsub used
a disposable cell.
We got our best
csu team.
If he left anything,
a print, a hair,
sweat, anything...
they'll find it.
I sent her home,
jason.
This wasn't you.
I should have been
clearer with anderson.
Try morgan
and jj again.
I tried 'em 3 times.
They're out of cell range.
Well, try 'em again.
I don't want 'em
to hear about this
on the news.
Woman, on p. A: Dr. Bender
to the mental ward, please.
Dr. Bender.
She was 16
when she was abducted.
She's 18 now.
Her birthday
was in august.
Help me!
Let me out!
2 years
in that little cell.
All right,
let's go over this
one more time.
She took off
for school,
but never got there,
correct?
Correct.
None of the neighbors
saw her that morning?
It doesn't even appear
that they canvassed at all.
Ok, jj, i need you
to see if the
originating detective
can meet us
at the house
'cause there's just
something really funky
about this whole
investigation.
Well, i will as soon
as we re-enter the world
of cell phone service.
"The path to the end
began at his start.
"To find her first calm
her long broken heart.
"She sits in a window
with secrets from her knight.
Is it adventure that keeps
him out of her sight?"
Another puzzle?
It's a riddle.
"Began at his start."
"The youngest
holds the key."
"Sits in a window.
Secrets, adventure."
Morgan's voice:
It really says in there
that gideon digs
nellie fox?
"Secrets
from her knight"?
"Sits in the window."
Woman's voice:
Tell some of your adventures.
"Ever would it be night,
but always clear day."
That'd be...
that'd be bright lights.
Jj: Someone delivered this
to the desk last night.
It's never night
in las vegas.
Excuse me?
I need to be connected
to the field office
closest to las vegas,
nevada, immediately.
Hi. This is
dr. Spencer reid
at the behavioral
analysis unit
at quantico.
Look, i need
my mother picked up
and brought to virginia
in protective custody
as soon as possible.
We're searching
for an unsub
who shot one
of our agents today,
and i think he might
know my mother,
and i believe
she may be in danger.
Yes.
She's at the bennington
sanitarium in las vegas.
Her name's diana reid.
She's a patient there.
Diana?
???
yes, sir.
If there's anything
we can do.
Yes, sir.
We will.
What's up?
Uh, that was hotch.
Don't tell me. Reid
already figured it out,
and we drove
all the way out here
for nothing, right?
Derek...
what?
What?
The... the unsub...
elle was shot
in her apartment
this morning.
[Slams on brakes]
What?
What are you doing?
I'm goin' back.
No, no, no.
Hotch said not to.
I don't give a damn
what hotch said.
But, derek, he's right.
There's nothing we can do
at the hospital, ok?
But maybe we can find
the unsub through...
through her,
through the victim's profile,
through rebecca.
How bad?
She's in surgery.
That's all they know.
[Heart monitor beeping]
[Heart monitor
beeping continuous tone]
Daddy, it was hard
growing up without you.
I'm sorry.
No, it wasn't your fault.
I just missed
you so much.
I'm always with you.
What's gonna happen
to me?
Happen?
That's up to you,
baby.
That's up to you.
Any word?
No.
I called jj.
I told her
that we'd call them
if anything changed.
What's all that?
This unsub's
extremely organized.
Sounded truly shocked
that we didn't
follow the rules.
Honestly believed
we would simply listen
to his directions.
He's delusional.
He thinks
he's a mythological king.
But delusion
and this level
of organization
are almost
mutually exclusive.
You don't meticulously
plan contacts
in the real world
if you're suffering
psychotic breaks
from reality.
How is she?
No word yet.
Is the scene processed?
They're finished.
We still have it
locked up tight, though.
You find anything?
Csu found
a partial print.
The shooter wrote
a message on the wall
in blood,
and in one
of the smudges, they
found a whirl pattern.
They made a lift.
They aren't sure
whether it's enough
to get a hit,
but they are
processing it now.
Rules.
She's ok... your mom.
Agents picked her up.
She's flying here
right now.
I forgot she
used to always
read me this poem.
It's funny, huh?
Funny?
Should have realized
sooner than that.
Nobody knows things
like the fact that jj
collects butterflies
except for me.
People tell me
their secrets
all the time.
Think it's
'cause they know
i don't have anyone
to betray them to...
except my mother.
I... i tell her
pretty much everything.
I don't think
anyone would mind.
Do you know that
i write her a letter
every day?
That's nice.
It depends on
why i write her.
What do you mean?
I write her letters
so i won't
feel so guilty
about not visiting her.
Did you know
that schizophrenia
is genetically passed?
All of her things
are still right here.
We kept it all.
Everything that
was in her room,
in case she ever...
you said there's
a videotape?
Yes, ma'am.
The man who abducted
your daughter
sent it to us.
You're sure
it's rebecca?
Yes, ma'am,
we're sure.
Ma'am i don't
mean to impose,
but we've had ourselves
a really long drive.
You got any coffee?
Excuse me?
I'll come with you,
ma'am.
Oh, certainly. Sure.
Detective...
i've seen kids missin'
for a decade,
and their rooms look
exactly the way they did
the day that they left.
Parents don't just
pack up their kid's stuff
and put 'em in boxes
in the garage.
Parents don't give up,
ever.
What the hell
is goin' on here?
This wasn't exactly
a cut and dried missing.
This rebecca
is no angel.
She was in trouble,
a lot of it
all the time.
What kind of trouble?
Name it.
Dope, vandalism,
theft, truancy.
Nobody even blinked
when she didn't show up
for school that day.
She was a part-time
attendee at best.
None of that
was in the report.
And why would it be?
Because it's relevant,
detective.
Look, uniforms filed
the initial report.
Missing persons never
did a supplemental
because the girl
had run away
5 or 6 times before.
She didn't run away
this time, did she?
Oh, yeah,
apparently not.
Nobody even bothered
to look for this girl
for 2 years?
No.
Why? Why was she
actin' out?
Was there
a problem at home?
Was there abuse?
Abuse?
From the moment
we treated rebecca
like an angel.
You just said
"brought her
into the house."
When she was
5 years old,
we took rebecca in
as a foster child.
And after
a couple of years,
we adopted her.
Where are
her birth parents?
Something happened
to the whole family.
Did she
ever talk about it?
I don't even think
she remembered it.
She was
just a little girl.
So her name hasn't
always been bryant.
No. It was...
garner.
Rebecca garner.
[Coughing]
Please.
I brought you dinner.
It's chicken.
I'm sick.
I need a doctor.
I knew
you liked chicken.
No, no.
Just take the chains
off me.
No, you'll
try to escape.
Please, no.
I won't.
I promise.
I'll be back
for your tray
in half an hour.
Why don't you
just kill me, you
son of a bitch?!
Because i love you
too much, rebecca.
Garcia.
Hey, it's morgan.
Derek, what do you need?
Garcia, i need
information
on an adoption.
Name?
Adopted name
is rebecca bryant,
birth name is garner.
Where?
Somewhere around
south boston, virginia,
13 years ago.
Nothing.
Nothing?
I'll try just the name
with a wider search.
Ok, there's
a rebecca garner
who was adopted by
a mr. And mrs. Joseph bryant
on december 4, 1993,
in clark county, nevada.
Wait. Nevada?
That's what it says.
The rest is sealed.
Morgan:
Garcia, unseal it.
I need to know
what happened
to that girl's family
to cause her
to need adopting.
Ok, i'll work on it.
[Telephone
beeps off]
Coffee?
No.
We don't have enough
for a profile yet,
not a good one.
No.
Some generalities.
Not enough
to catch him.
Press conference was
the thing to do, right?
Sorry?
Brought the unsub
out into the open,
he made a mistake,
left a partial print.
We wouldn't
have had that.
No.
It was really
the only way to go.
I did the right thing.
I did my job.
Elle will
understand that.
She'll understand.
Hopin'
she'll understand.
[Heart monitor beeping]
Greenaway: I'm afraid.
What if i don't
come out of it?
wake up?
You keep talkin'
like you don't have
any choice, peanut.
You can choose to fight,
to beat the odds.
It's up to you.
What if i want
to stay with you?
Well, that's
a choice, too.
That's why you're
so skinny, you know?
Too much coffee.
Thanks a lot, guys.
I've got her.
You know i'm
terrified of flying.
I know, mom.
I'm sorry.
Well, then why did you
have those fascists
arrest me?
Mom, they're
not fascists,
and you were not arrested.
I'm trying
to protect you.
By forcing me to do
the one thing
that frightens me
more than anything else?
I need to show
you something.
Follow me.
Whoa.
Morgan, on speakerphone:
Yeah, talk to me.
Not only did i find
her records,
i found some newspaper
articles about your girl.
Newspaper articles?
Yeah. Apparently most
of rebecca garner's family
died in a house fire
in 1992.
Faulty electrical wiring
in their tract house.
So when she was 4.
Yeah, mrs. Garner,
both garner boys,
one of the garner girls.
Rebecca was found
in the backyard crying,
but unharmed.
How'd she get there?
Her father probably.
He was a teacher
at a vegas public school,
and he tried to save
the rest of the family,
but he suffered
massive burns
to his entire body
and nearly died.
Spent years
in a burn icu,
and it was
during that time
that he gave up
his parental rights
to rebecca,
so that she could be
put up for adoption
because there
was no other family.
Could explain
her acting out.
You watch your whole family
die in front of you?
The father was awarded
a huge settlement
from the contractors
who built the development.
They were using
faulty materials.
Good work, garcia.
Print that up
for me, all right?
We'll be back
pretty soon.
Huh.
What?
Somethin' else?
No. It just says here
that, after the father left
the medical hospital,
he spent a few years
at a vegas sanitarium.
Bennington.
That mean somethin'
to you?
Yeah. That's where...
garcia?
I gotta go.
[Disconnects]
Could that be...?
Oh, my god.
This is
where you work?
This is where we meet.
Uh, my desk,
you can see it,
it's right out there
in the bullpen area.
The table's round.
Yeah, just like i wrote
you in my letters.
Yes, just like you wrote
in your letters.
Dr. Jessen gave me
the book you brought.
Marjorie kemp.
She's your favorite.
That particular book
is one of her minor works.
Mom, no!
Don't ta... don't.
You can't grab stuff
off the board.
This key is evidence.
Mom, the unsub that
we're looking for...
the... the bad guy
knows things
about my colleagues'
personal lives,
things that
only you would know.
Do you write about them
in you journals?
My journals are none
of the government's business!
I'm not
the government, mom.
Well, this certainly looks
like a government office.
Mother, do you write
about my colleagues'
personal lives?
Why did you
bring me here, spencer?
I need to ask
you some things
about a man
i think you might know.
A bad man.
He's killed some people,
and he's holding
a girl hostage.
You think i know
someone like that?
Will you just watch
the tape
and see if he sounds
familiar?
I had to make sure
i had your complete attention.
I assure you, you will
all understand in the end
why it must be this way.
You might
even thank me.
[Stops tape]
You do know him?
I'm sure it's...
randall garner.
Randall garner?
He was with me
at the hospital.
He's a very emotionally
disturbed man.
Reid, i got to the end
of the ip string.
Sir kneighf,
the fisher king,
his name is randall garner.
reid and garcia think
they've i.d.'d the unsub.
How?
I don't know,
but they want to know
how to proceed.
Well, one of us
should be there.
You go.
I want to be here
when she comes
out of surgery.
Call me immediately.
Immediately.
Hotch?
Yeah?
The only way for
the organization level
to be so high
is the unsub believes
it's all real.
He believes he's
the keeper of the grail,
needs us to find it.
We have to
make him understand
it isn't real.
right
I can't believe
she's real.
What do you mean?
Whenever he talked
about rebecca,
he never said
she was his daughter.
He said all his children
died in the fire.
He spoke of a rebecca,
more in the abstract.
I really thought
she was a metaphor,
not an actual human being.
An ideal.
A grail.
He thinks he's
the fisher king.
Who does?
Randall garner,
our unsub.
He believes you're
all modern-day knights
of the round table.
Uh, derek morgan,
this is my mother,
diana reid.
It's your mother?
Ma'am, it's a...
it's a pleasure
to meet you.
So where are we on finding
this son of a bitch?
I rechecked
all the clues.
There's nothing that points
to an address.
The adoption records
for rebecca
listed an address
of the fire,
so i made a call
to nevada,
and it's vacant.
No one ever rebuilt.
Nevada? So we don't even
know what state he's in?
I'll search
the tax records,
see if he owns
any property.
Excuse me.
Mom, we're...
just before the agents
got me from the hospital,
a man delivered
this to me.
It's a photo of a house
with an address
on the back.
Shiloh, virginia?
That's only 10 miles from here.
That's it, guys.
It's open.
Hotch?
Guys, listen up.
T wants us to know
we're in the right place,
so keep your eyes open.
[Dog barking outside]
Let's go.
It's morgan. We're clear.
[Floor creaks]
[Footsteps]
[Whispering]
There's someone
upstairs.
[Door squeaks]
Where?
I saw a shadow.
Randall garner?!
Fbi!
Garner?!
Come out, garner!
He's in there.
All right, cover me.
I'm gonna go in.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Mr. Garner?
My name's spencer reid.
You were in the hospital
with my mother.
I think... i think
she might have
confused you.
All we want to do
is help rebecca.
That's exactly what
you want, right?
That's why you sent us
the puzzles?
That's why you said
you hoped you'd be
seeing us soon?
Garner:
Ask the question.
There is
no magical question,
mr. Garner.
He believes
if i ask him
the right question,
it'll heal
all of his wounds.
Do you know the question?
I know what he wants.
I'm gonna move
to where he can see me.
Reid!
Reid, no!
Fall back.
Reid!
Reid, no!
Reid, reid!
Wait a minute.
Stay calm, mr. Garner.
Ask the question,
sir percival.
I told you,
i'm not percival.
My name
is dr. Spencer reid
from the fbi.
You were in the hospital
with my mother, diana?
Garner:
If you want the grail...
she's not a grail!
She's your daughter.
Her name's rebecca.
My daughters
died in a fire
and my son
and my wife.
Rebecca lived.
No. Your mother,
she explained
it all to me.
My mother's
a paranoid schizophrenic
who'd forget to eat
if she wasn't
properly medicated
and supervised.
She made me realize
none of it was real.
I didn't lose rebecca.
She... she never existed
in the first place.
She does exist,
mr. Garner,
and we're here
to help her.
Hotch, morgan?
I think maybe
it'd be better
if you guys
waited downstairs.
What?
Mr. Garner and i
are just gonna
talk alone up here.
Morgan:
Go ahead and talk, reid,
but we're not goin'
anywhere.
Ask the question.
I'll be healed,
and you may
take the grail.
Just ask the question,
sir knight.
I can't.
Heal me!
Mr. Garner,
a fisher king wound
cannot be healed
by somebody else.
It's not a wound
to the body.
It's a wound
to the memory.
Wound to the mind.
It's... it's a wound
that only you can find,
and a wound that
only you can heal.
Just ask the question.
There's only one question
that matters, mr. Garner.
There's only one
really important question.
Can you forgive yourself?
I couldn't
get to them.
If you tell me
where she is,
you can save rebecca now.
Tell me where rebecca is.
You already know.
I sent you
my other map.
What map?
Can i forgive myself?
No, i can't.
[Beeping]
Run!
[Shouting]
It's all right.
It's ok.
Let's go!
[Coughing]
What the hell
was that?
He had a bomb.
You didn't
think we needed
to know that?
I told you
to go downstairs.
Well, you didn't say bomb.
You left that part out.
Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop.
Stop? The house
is on fire, reid.
Let's go!
Just let me think,
let me think!
He's the fisher king,
this is his house,
so rebecca's
got to be here.
Reid, there
may not be time
for a search. Let's go.
Location's on the map
that he gave to my mom.
Reid, all she
told us about
was that photo.
Let's go!
Down... she's
in the basement downstairs!
Morgan: How do you
know that?!
Rebecca!
Is the house
on fire!?
Rebecca!
Unchain me!
Get us
out of here!
Hurry!
He called me
sir percival.
Rebecca: Hurry!
Reid, hurry.
The key. The key.
The youngest one
holds the key.
Tell me
you got the key.
Come on! Let's go!
Let's go!
We got no time!
Get it off!
You got her?
Come on.
Let's go.
Gideon: "it has been said
that time heals all wounds.
"I do not agree.
"The wounds remain.
"In time, the mind,
protecting its sanity,
"covers them
with scar tissue,
and the pain lessens,
but it is never gone."
Rose kennedy.
Dad, there's something...
it's ok.
No, i want to say it.
That day...
i was just mad
that day.
I wanted you to teach me
to ride my bike.
I knew that you
had to work.
I was just being
selfish and childish.
Baby, you were 8.
I said,
"i hate you, daddy."
Those are the last words
that i ever said to you.
Shh. It's ok, baby.
I've thought
so many times
that i wish...
i wish that i had said...
i love you, daddy.
I love you, too,
peanut,
very much.
I can't stay
with you.
That's all right.
Will i ever see you
again?
I'll be here
when it's time.
I love you.
Doctor:
There you are.
You can sleep.
You're
gonna be fine.
Elle's
out of surgery.
She's gonna be ok.
Good.
Is gideon still
at the hospital?
Yeah.
How's rebecca?
She's in the hospital,
but she should be all right.
Physically, maybe.
Thank you, everyone.
All of you.
Well, we could have
only gone so far
without mrs. Reid.
Mom, we found her.
Rebecca's safe.
You helped us
save her life.
Is it time
for lunch yet?
What?
I'm lecturing everyone
in tristan and iseult.
They're all gathering
in my room after lunch.
Can i attend
the lecture, too?
Have you read
any of the material?
I've had them
read to me.
Wonderful.
That's the best way,
isn't it?
Yes, ma'am.
By far.
Five for fighting:
* the batter swings
and the summer flies *
* as i look
into my angel's eyes*
* a song plays on
while the moon is high *
*over me,
something comes over me *
*i guess we're big,
and i guess we're small *
*if you think
about it, man *
* you know,
we got it all *
*'cause we're all we got
on this bouncin' ball *
* and i love ya free *
*i love you freely *
* and he said,
here's a riddle for ya *
* find the answer*
*there's a reason
for the world *
* you and i *
* there are secrets that we
still have left to find *
*there have been
mysteries *
* from the beginning
of time *
* there are answers *
* we're not wise enough
to see *
*he said,
you're lookin' for a clue *
*i love you free *
*here's a riddle for ya *
* find the answer *
* there's a reason
for the world *
* you and i *
captioning made possible by
touchstone television
productions, llc and cbs
captioned by the national
captioning institute
- www.ncicap.org...