[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.53,0:00:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,维吉尼亚州 弗雷德里克斯堡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.73,0:00:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都靠拢  就没人敢来惹我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.20,0:00:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都三个星期了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.20,0:00:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是最后一个和她说话的人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.56,0:00:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的觉得她被绑架了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.46,0:00:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这帮家伙真是疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.96,0:00:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Julie不会突然消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.16,0:00:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.36,0:00:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就这样人间蒸发了 和另一个女孩一样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.66,0:00:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她妈妈已经彻底崩溃了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.46,0:00:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.86,0:00:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿的每个人都疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.06,0:00:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只是吓坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.99,0:00:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 Julie肯定离开这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.69,0:00:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你保证 她现在肯定在华盛顿或者纽约
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.76,0:00:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.56,0:00:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny  哦  天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.26,0:00:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.16,0:01:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.56,0:01:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个贱人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.56,0:01:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真该找个镜子照照  伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞笑  看把你们吓得
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.76,0:01:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.12,0:01:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.36,0:01:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不好笑   傻B
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.86,0:01:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  各位
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.66,0:01:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想让我醉醺醺再脱光光 就直说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.86,0:01:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要这么费劲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.46,0:01:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.96,0:01:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.96,0:01:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一点都不知趣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.76,0:01:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.66,0:01:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他点颜色看看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.56,0:01:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.56,0:01:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点回来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.46,0:01:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.06,0:01:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.66,0:02:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.56,0:02:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证  一定会宰了你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.56,0:02:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到他
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.76,0:02:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.36,0:02:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.26,0:02:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Danny
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.06,0:02:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.96,0:02:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话  她和你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.16,0:02:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 拜托  说真的  Molly在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.86,0:02:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和你在一起啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.26,0:02:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.66,0:02:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.86,0:02:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.96,0:02:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.72,0:02:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.46,0:02:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI行为分析小组 维吉尼亚州 Quantico
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.36,0:02:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我正要把这个案子上报组里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.33,0:02:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.26,0:02:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信他们也有同感
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.06,0:02:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.26,0:02:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会尽快赶到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.26,0:02:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.05,0:03:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都到齐了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.62,0:03:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.02,0:03:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚 在弗雷德里克斯堡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.12,0:03:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20岁的女性 Molly McCarthy遭绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.82,0:03:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在过去六周内 她已经是第三个失踪者了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.92,0:03:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是在公共场所失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.02,0:03:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-之后再没有人见过她们 -直到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.72,0:03:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两天前 在国家公园被发现了 被烟烧过的部分尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.32,0:03:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里曾是钱瑟勒斯维尔战役的战场 (美国内战)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.92,0:03:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能确定身份吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.45,0:03:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是六周前的第一个受害人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.12,0:03:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸体腐烂程度表明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.02,0:03:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在一周前才被杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.42,0:03:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说他喜欢在她们身上花时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.01,0:03:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么这么个死状?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.42,0:03:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,验尸官在骨头上发现微小刀痕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.72,0:04:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得在Spotsylvania郡有过类似的案例
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骨头上也有类似的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.82,0:04:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在1980年冬 也发生在弗雷德里克斯堡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.11,0:04:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5名女性  16岁至24岁
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.42,0:04:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也被烧成碎片  有同样的标记
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.02,0:04:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样的内战战场
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.92,0:04:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一年中的同时间被杀 弃尸地点也相同
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.82,0:04:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像周年纪念
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.82,0:04:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个案子还没破
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.22,0:04:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时的受害者是吸毒者和出逃者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.32,0:04:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他在她们身上花这么多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.32,0:04:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能剩下的两个女人还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.62,0:04:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  大家觉得是同一个凶手干的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.42,0:04:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这冷静期可真够久的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.52,0:04:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BTK连环杀手直到25年后才再次露面 (1974年美国的一名连环杀人狂魔  逍遥法外31年)
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.82,0:04:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但他当时没有杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.02,0:04:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是奚落警方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.42,0:04:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骨头上的痕迹 以及弃尸地点…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是非常明显的特征
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.32,0:04:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连从未公布的细节都复制得丝毫不差 这恐怕不太可能
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.72,0:04:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 把犯罪手法和其他州的 失踪女孩做比对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.42,0:04:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许能找出间隔如此之久的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.52,0:04:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是同一不明疑犯所为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.02,0:04:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去27年他都做了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.52,0:05:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Julie
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.32,0:05:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.82,0:05:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持安静  就不会被烧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.02,0:05:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.82,0:05:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按他说的做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.72,0:05:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续  让她看看
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.42,0:05:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个派对
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.02,0:05:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.96,0:06:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国诗人Anne Sexton曾写道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.76,0:06:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我的父亲是谁不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.26,0:06:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是我记忆中的他是谁"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.36,0:06:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶手对女性有明显的轻视
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.66,0:06:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将她们视为可被任意蹂躏 且毫无价值
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.86,0:06:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  他需要大量的时间 和一个隐蔽处  以此折磨她们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.46,0:06:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐居  时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.46,0:06:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初认为凶手是个季节性的农场工人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.36,0:06:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是弃尸地点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.76,0:06:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有意思  不管有多大的风险 他总将尸体抛弃在战场
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.56,0:06:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是备受尊敬的地标
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.46,0:07:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在炫耀  这让他感觉自己很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.86,0:07:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都认为我跑了?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.86,0:07:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.36,0:07:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有我这么想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.66,0:07:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太傻了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.16,0:07:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.06,0:07:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.46,0:07:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个镇...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.76,0:07:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都在找你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.46,0:07:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.56,0:07:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从不相信你就这么走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.06,0:07:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这儿多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.26,0:07:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3个星期
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.56,0:07:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他每晚都那样做吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.46,0:08:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只需要去不同的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.86,0:08:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这样才能熬过去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.96,0:08:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ballantyne警长  我是Jennifer Jareau
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.46,0:08:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  感谢你们这么快就赶来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Aaron Hotchner 这是Spencer Reid博士
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.76,0:08:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  犯罪现场在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.86,0:08:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为这是同一凶手所为
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.46,0:08:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想浪费时间再做介绍了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.06,0:08:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的探员们去和John Caulfied碰面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.06,0:08:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他负责原来那个案子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.36,0:08:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.66,0:08:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.46,0:08:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 没见过面 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.66,0:08:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是听说过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.46,0:08:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.96,0:08:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的  人人都说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.56,0:08:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个正派的警长  是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.53,0:08:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.56,0:08:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上 我们这儿并没太多谋杀案
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.66,0:08:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这个案子毁了他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.86,0:08:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.06,0:08:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老一套了  你知道的  他开始酗酒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.76,0:08:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老婆也跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.56,0:08:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后被要求退休
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.66,0:08:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没走错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.06,0:08:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,David Rossi
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.36,0:08:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,John Caulfield
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Derek Morgan探员
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.16,0:08:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Emily Prentiss
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.46,0:09:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是翻查你的旧案子  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.96,0:09:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sharon Chroniger
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.16,0:09:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时她才只有16岁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.76,0:09:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现她被碎尸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.21,0:09:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向她父母保证  会将凶手绳之于法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.23,0:09:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来她父亲去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.17,0:09:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们说说1980年时 弗雷德里克斯堡的情况吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.51,0:09:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是个农村社区  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.20,0:09:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人人都彼此熟悉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.70,0:09:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以夜不闭户
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.41,0:09:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在到处都是城市屋和大型住宅社区
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以解释为什么受害者类型发生了变化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.96,0:09:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前是出逃者和妓女 如今却是大学学生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.69,0:09:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他选择现成的下手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.07,0:09:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个凶手突然停手27年之久 这不太正常  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.80,0:09:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不正常  但他可能坐牢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.97,0:09:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.20,0:09:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是搬走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.50,0:09:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定找到了其他满足自我需要的途径
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.04,0:09:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时大概有20个孩子在聚会
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.49,0:09:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,100码以外的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.25,0:09:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly McCarty被带到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.81,0:10:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里发现一条毯子 一件运动衫 一双鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.08,0:10:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道没人听见或看见吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.32,0:10:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有夜色作掩饰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.21,0:10:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Molly的男朋友是最后一个见到她的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.26,0:10:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据他说  Molly独处的时间不超过一分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.52,0:10:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很有耐心  出手相当快
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.08,0:10:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的犯罪手法炉火纯青啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.47,0:10:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不明疑犯年近60  那他肯定很强壮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.02,0:10:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能乖乖让她被拖动这么远的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.64,0:10:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这条没有标记的土路上 看到很多私人房产
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.82,0:10:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有明显的街道标志
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.32,0:10:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地图上也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.65,0:10:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  如果你不住这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.92,0:10:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定会迷路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.79,0:10:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定是当地人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.02,0:10:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉我们通往这里的各个入口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.55,0:10:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.47,0:10:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.92,0:10:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从有了Jack之后 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.76,0:10:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一有涉及孩子的案子 我总是提心吊胆的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.35,0:10:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么告诉我这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.95,0:10:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个案子  不管我们是否受理 都会经你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.59,0:10:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.43,0:10:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数的受害者都是女性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.93,0:10:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们大多数和你差不多大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.29,0:11:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔失控一下没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.11,0:11:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少让人们知道  我们还是正常人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.46,0:11:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你从不失控
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.60,0:11:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我也应该
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.53,0:11:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要保证...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.60,0:11:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我死了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.20,0:11:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝不能告诉我父母 他都对我们干了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.02,0:11:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.21,0:11:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.32,0:11:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保证
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.20,0:11:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会死在这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.93,0:11:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.28,0:11:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Julie 快起来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.33,0:11:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了 闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.13,0:11:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.70,0:11:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.98,0:11:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在努力 我发誓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.88,0:11:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Julie 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.89,0:11:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.64,0:11:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 求你了  我可以做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.04,0:12:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  Julie
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.52,0:12:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.53,0:12:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里有两对父母等待确认身份
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.69,0:12:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.21,0:12:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.95,0:12:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次他没有分开弃尸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.21,0:12:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我们眼皮底下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.25,0:12:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在嘲笑我们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.63,0:12:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他这是在说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.90,0:12:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我就这么干  你们束手无策"
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.68,0:12:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在大门口出示身份证才能进来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.43,0:12:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一份访客名单的复印件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.00,0:12:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有上百种进来的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.96,0:12:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些栅栏是保护个人房产的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.47,0:12:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和其他人一样  都清楚这里的地形
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.21,0:12:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可以跳过栅栏  将尸体抛弃在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.08,0:12:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再原路返回
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.39,0:12:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.28,0:12:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.60,0:12:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.50,0:12:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.14,0:12:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.54,0:13:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是来调查我的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.10,0:13:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.71,0:13:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿的人都传言说我疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.67,0:13:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对传言不感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.24,0:13:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不愿相信是这里的人干的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.04,0:13:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信你的辖区
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.98,0:13:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.07,0:13:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很平常的过错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.04,0:13:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你看点东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.47,0:13:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西我一直带在身上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.70,0:13:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的孩子?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.28,0:13:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,印第安纳波利斯 (美国印第安纳州的首府)
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.60,0:13:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平安夜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.24,0:13:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的第一个案子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.01,0:14:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3个孩子眼睁睁地看着父母被活活打死
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.72,0:14:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年我都打电话告诉他们  我不会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.33,0:14:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会追查到底
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.72,0:14:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.67,0:14:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都懒得回我的电话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.54,0:14:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.75,0:14:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别浪费时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.06,0:14:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿到了1980年谋杀案发前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.35,0:14:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个镇上的暴力罪名名单
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.66,0:14:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒后驾车  盗窃  强暴  袭击
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很少有惯犯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.11,0:14:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.24,0:14:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 这不会传染
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.94,0:14:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在全国范围内调查这家伙的犯罪手法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.66,0:14:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么有价值的发现
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.10,0:14:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我将目标缩小到案发地附近
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.91,0:14:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在旁边的一个镇找到了 Karen Foley的投诉档案
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.25,0:14:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,故事非常…恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发到你们的掌上电脑上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.21,0:14:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个儿童不宜的故事是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.98,0:15:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在1979年遭绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.28,0:15:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…她逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没听过这事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.99,0:15:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不在你的管辖区内
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.71,0:15:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会不会就是他的第一个受害人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.87,0:15:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是他的排练
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.51,0:15:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找出作案目标和作案地点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.75,0:15:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找出可行方案
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.18,0:15:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许谨慎计划也是他作案过程的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.07,0:15:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.21,0:15:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝女孩 施展你的魔力 找出地址吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.20,0:15:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.41,0:15:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foley女士?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.06,0:15:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Emily Prentisss 这位是Derek Morgan
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.45,0:15:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是FBI  请问你有时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.66,0:15:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.88,0:15:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在调查弗雷德里克斯堡的 两人被害案和三人绑架案
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.70,0:15:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你也听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.50,0:15:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  这太可怕了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.38,0:15:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 我们认为这也许与你1979年的遭遇有关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.67,0:15:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.87,0:15:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  你们找错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.98,0:15:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.17,0:15:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你语气这么肯定?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.23,0:15:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  那是我编的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.06,0:16:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们看过你的报告
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.39,0:16:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被下药 烧伤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.44,0:16:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭殴打 性侵犯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.91,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遭囚禁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.97,0:16:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时只有17岁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.22,0:16:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得为我的去向找些说法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.38,0:16:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去了哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.54,0:16:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在附近  我当时在吸毒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.89,0:16:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给家里打过电话 女士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.01,0:16:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的罪犯强迫受害者联系家人 解释他们的行踪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.30,0:16:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有罪犯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.85,0:16:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的报告中有大量细节 都和1980年受害的几名女性相符
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.00,0:16:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我在撒谎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.69,0:16:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白你不想回忆起那段日子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.05,0:16:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时现在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.81,0:16:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是唯一能帮助我们的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.20,0:16:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他女性不该承受痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.89,0:16:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生了什么  但你幸存了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.27,0:16:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.43,0:16:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你想好了告诉我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.19,0:16:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有线索
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.18,0:16:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.28,0:16:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们找出真凶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.57,0:17:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Karen Foley否认了她的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.77,0:17:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得她在撒谎吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.08,0:17:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定出过什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.94,0:17:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的眼光躲闪不定  自我保护 对我们戒心十足
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.23,0:17:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极力否认发生过的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.37,0:17:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不可能打开心理防线
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.59,0:17:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕一旦如此  就再也无法正常生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.17,0:17:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她现在唯一保护的只有罪犯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.65,0:17:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们告诉她  罪犯可能还逍遥法外
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.35,0:17:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她却无动于衷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.94,0:17:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.26,0:17:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.28,0:17:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许她根本没什么好怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.31,0:17:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们打算怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.52,0:17:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么有人将案子一查到底呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.61,0:17:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在你心里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.58,0:17:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这个混蛋还逍遥在外
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.97,0:17:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全正确
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.88,0:17:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她却毫不在意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.40,0:17:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她搬回来 因为她觉得很安全
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.41,0:17:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此对她下手的这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.65,0:17:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么搬走了  要么死翘翘了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.06,0:17:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这家伙是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.01,0:17:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是在这里土生土长的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.62,0:17:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当时20来岁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.43,0:18:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你发现了最后一个受害人之后 他从这里搬走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.69,0:18:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1980年12月13号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.86,0:18:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他坐牢了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.94,0:18:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许参军了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.32,0:18:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬走了 卖掉了房产
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.02,0:18:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个鲁莽的人  酗酒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.43,0:18:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许曾因为酒后驾车被捕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.05,0:18:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是这个 这就是你的案子 就在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.25,0:18:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他凡事都小心翼翼  一丝不苟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.98,0:18:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此他或许有两个可控制的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.79,0:18:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是私人地点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.89,0:18:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个用作折磨  一个用作囚禁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.83,0:18:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是个工场
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.82,0:18:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谷仓  车库
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.24,0:18:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1980年12月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.50,0:18:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人在这里  然后他走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.31,0:18:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他  John
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.11,0:18:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Robert Wilkinson
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.51,0:18:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三次酒后驾车
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.59,0:18:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐过几天牢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.68,0:18:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他死了啊   那时他28岁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.93,0:18:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他摔进了自己的联合收割机里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.62,0:18:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,﹣那是什么时候 ﹣1980年12月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.71,0:18:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在谋杀停止的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.20,0:18:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是Karen Foley在那之后就搬回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.27,0:18:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还有活着的亲人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.72,0:18:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个寡妇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.48,0:18:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Caulfield警长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.79,0:18:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 Mary
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.49,0:19:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能进去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.67,0:19:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.79,0:19:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你儿子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.85,0:19:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他结婚了  过得还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.91,0:19:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你今天来肯定有其他事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.50,0:19:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在调查一宗案件 线索查到Robert头上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.04,0:19:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经死了27年了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.06,0:19:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.22,0:19:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在1980年杀了5个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.69,0:19:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你肯定记得吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.85,0:19:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我已经很久没想过他了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.90,0:19:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时 你年纪轻轻就守寡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.10,0:19:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警长说你必须独立抚养你儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.03,0:19:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难相信你居然没有想过他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.65,0:19:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未为自己感到过遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.30,0:19:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数年轻守寡的妇女 都觉得自己是受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.61,0:19:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我继续生活
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.65,0:19:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再婚了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.99,0:19:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我的父母搬了回来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.46,0:20:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀孕的时候 曾在这里待过一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.55,0:20:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Robert一喝酒就变脸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.47,0:20:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他求我回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.26,0:20:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说他改过自新
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.86,0:20:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.05,0:20:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.63,0:20:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来那天他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她看上去很平静
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.55,0:20:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一点都不吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.04,0:20:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至都没问为什么我们会怀疑是他干的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.45,0:20:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怀疑他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.49,0:20:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他酗酒  她怀孕之后就离开他了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.85,0:20:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抛弃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.40,0:20:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他母亲也如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.29,0:20:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  他都无法处理
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.10,0:20:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他的刺激源 于是他开始杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.17,0:20:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣母/妓女情结
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.74,0:20:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不能碰他纯洁的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.72,0:20:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他要找可以任意蹂躏的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.56,0:20:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他死后杀戮就停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.29,0:20:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在的凶手又是谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.64,0:20:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Parker先生?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.48,0:20:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.70,0:20:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(5分钟后回来)
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.81,0:21:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.38,0:21:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有一宗绑架
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.78,0:21:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害人名字是Tara Ricker
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.11,0:21:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早家人报警
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.26,0:21:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚她没回家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.79,0:21:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还在搜寻她的车
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.81,0:21:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道 他抓了一个之后 就要杀另外一个了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.51,0:21:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们时间不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.51,0:21:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  目前都有哪些线索
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.64,0:21:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然是个模仿凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.07,0:21:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样的犯罪手法  同样的弃尸地点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.82,0:21:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你从未对媒体透漏过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.97,0:21:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.19,0:21:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是从家人或朋友那里得知的?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.85,0:21:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mary和Robert Wilkinson有个儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.80,0:21:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说杀人也会基因遗传吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.40,0:21:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是其中一个因素
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.16,0:22:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有心理和社会的因素
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.51,0:22:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有混合的基因
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.02,0:22:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而儿子又在没有父亲的情况下寻找自我身份 这也是个刺激源
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.35,0:22:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把猫放在口袋里  对着树猛摔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.02,0:22:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie Wilkinson多大了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.40,0:22:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mary在Robert死的时候怀孕
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.26,0:22:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是27年前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.26,0:22:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟Robert开始杀人的年纪差不多
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.50,0:22:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么消息  美女
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.67,0:22:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了Karen Foley说谎的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.97,0:22:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们又回来做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.24,0:22:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过了  我什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.93,0:22:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道他烧伤了你 Foley女士
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.56,0:22:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的受害人也是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.52,0:22:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道Robert Wilkinson强奸了你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.97,0:22:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还知道你因此有了个儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.09,0:22:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿还有其它的女孩?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.43,0:22:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.60,0:23:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的名字...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.70,0:23:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Julie Stanton
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.47,0:23:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应过她不告诉她父亲她的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.09,0:23:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.05,0:23:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.54,0:23:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他会先杀了我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.41,0:23:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stephen不知道真相
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.62,0:23:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...你从没跟他说起过他父亲的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.09,0:23:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他说成一个英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.82,0:23:35.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说他在一起摩托车事故中去世 所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.91,0:23:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你决定要这个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.54,0:23:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.33,0:23:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.12,0:23:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我孩子承担他父亲犯下的罪过
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.63,0:23:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stephen又喝酒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.25,0:23:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.01,0:23:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他因为酒后驾车坐牢  刚刚出来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.62,0:23:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是否心怀敌意
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.85,0:24:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或长时间消失?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.98,0:24:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么问我这样的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.09,0:24:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为了保护你的儿子 而隐瞒你的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.48,0:24:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很害怕他可能会伤害那些女人  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.95,0:24:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要和他谈谈 Foley女士
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.25,0:24:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车里没有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.75,0:24:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在取指纹
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.30,0:24:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车在这儿多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.38,0:24:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店主说昨晚就在这儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.42,0:24:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道没觉得可疑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.75,0:24:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在农场间来回
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.60,0:24:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到听说Tara Ricker失踪后才开始注意
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.71,0:24:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟顾客们谈过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.88,0:24:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人记得见过Tara
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.72,0:24:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有4个女孩失踪了 竟然没人留意遗弃车辆
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.59,0:24:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.32,0:24:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.57,0:24:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie Wilkins今天没有上班
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.73,0:24:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去看看他在不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.41,0:24:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Stephen
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.01,0:25:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.64,0:25:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.57,0:25:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,David Rossi和Emily Prentiss FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.50,0:25:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在调查该地区4名女性失踪案
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.38,0:25:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 Monroe农场那边的一个女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.44,0:25:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.59,0:25:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道些什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.45,0:25:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.93,0:25:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Robert Wilkinson这个名字 对你来说有什么意义吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.38,0:25:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.23,0:25:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.74,0:25:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于他对我妈妈做过的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.89,0:25:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.61,0:25:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为你可以保守秘密吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.74,0:25:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很早前就已经知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.19,0:25:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.50,0:25:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Robert Wilkinson强奸了你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.83,0:25:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.72,0:25:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没结过婚   从不约会
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.42,0:25:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天夜里都以泪洗面
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.16,0:25:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道有人伤害了你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.51,0:25:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被伤得很深
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.94,0:26:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天我打扫车库时
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.01,0:26:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现一篇文章…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.51,0:26:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于在农场事故中丧生的男人…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.31,0:26:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Robert Wilkinson
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.28,0:26:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面有他的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.44,0:26:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有篇关于失踪女人的尸体被发现的文章
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.04,0:26:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.21,0:26:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.54,0:26:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你走进来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.80,0:26:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我拿着那张照片
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.38,0:26:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着我的表情...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.67,0:26:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.96,0:26:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.44,0:26:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是十年前的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.08,0:26:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道都是我编的了?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.54,0:26:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道了?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.02,0:26:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些故事真的很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.65,0:26:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.93,0:26:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你相信他是个好人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.82,0:26:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是这件事中唯一美好的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.88,0:27:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们认为这些老案子和新案子有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.56,0:27:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的、
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.53,0:27:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可Wilkinson死了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.65,0:27:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我没死
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.63,0:27:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.92,0:27:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为是我干的?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.02,0:27:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你觉得我会变得和他一样
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.19,0:27:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…为什么你还要把我生下来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.49,0:27:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未后悔过当初的决定  从来没有
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.13,0:27:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 Stephen
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.25,0:27:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想怀疑你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.80,0:27:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.09,0:28:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Rossi
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.14,0:28:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.15,0:28:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan和Reid去 Charlie Wilkinson工作的地方找他  
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.20,0:28:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.14,0:28:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还不能排除Stephen Foley的嫌疑
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.87,0:28:08.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在正赶往Wilkinson的家
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.93,0:28:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一有发现就通知我们
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.10,0:28:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能告诉我们 他对你干了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.98,0:28:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.13,0:28:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得他第一次把我带进谷仓
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.39,0:28:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他盖住了我的头  所以我不知道身在何处
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.35,0:28:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这并不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.45,0:28:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把我灌得醉醺醺  我什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.60,0:28:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想让我为他跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.39,0:28:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把这叫做派对
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.07,0:28:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有天晚上他喝醉了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.59,0:29:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意识到谷仓的门没锁
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.53,0:29:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的手铐也松了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.02,0:29:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.49,0:29:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察不相信你的话?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.60,0:29:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们只当我是瘾君子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.84,0:29:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太…难以启齿了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.11,0:29:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那儿看到其他女孩了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.44,0:29:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是唯一的一个
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.87,0:29:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得被囚禁的地点的细节吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.03,0:29:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何细节都行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.69,0:29:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在墙上划了一个小小的和平符号
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.09,0:29:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每晚他来之前  我都会触摸它...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.87,0:29:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.68,0:29:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的守护天使
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.38,0:29:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chrissy Wilkinson?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.83,0:29:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.96,0:29:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jennifer Jareau 这位是Derek Morgan 我们是FBI的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.38,0:29:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.51,0:30:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在找Charles Wilkinson  他在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.83,0:30:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在工作
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.17,0:30:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他不在 -介意我们到处看看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.51,0:30:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白  出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.36,0:30:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在调查当地女性谋杀案
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.87,0:30:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在找Charlie?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.04,0:30:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人 有必要的话 我们可以申请搜查令
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.18,0:30:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.84,0:30:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.63,0:30:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.43,0:31:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然这里就是他折磨她们的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.63,0:31:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那囚禁的地方又在哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.75,0:31:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某个隔离的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.91,0:31:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不能冒险把她们囚禁在家附近
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.03,0:31:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这个地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.02,0:31:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…只在镇上跟Robert接触过
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.01,0:31:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wilkinson女士？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.55,0:31:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.56,0:31:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chrissy来电话了 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.35,0:31:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在找Charlie
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.23,0:31:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.49,0:31:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道Charlie是个易怒的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.06,0:31:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他杀了隔壁家的猫之后 还替他找借口
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.75,0:31:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着他走上这条堕落之路
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.33,0:31:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才从这儿搬走
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.36,0:32:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这里发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.40,0:32:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.38,0:32:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害怕他身体里遗传的因子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.57,0:32:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为只要带他远离父亲的家园
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.75,0:32:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守口如瓶  
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.58,0:32:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就相安无事了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.49,0:32:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保护了他
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.58,0:32:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是 像Charlie这样的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.37,0:32:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么易怒 那么多问题
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.57,0:32:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要知道他是从哪里来的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.70,0:32:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道实情他誓不罢休
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.60,0:32:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于有一天 他得知了一切
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.66,0:32:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这事结束了 John
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.61,0:32:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必担心其他的女孩子会受到伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.29,0:32:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想自己的儿子背负着 一个杀人犯的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.27,0:32:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie现在在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.61,0:32:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.78,0:32:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 真的 我真不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.47,0:32:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie一个人会去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.04,0:32:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 谷仓 - 其他地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.33,0:32:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 我不...我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.92,0:32:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 Hotch
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.33,0:32:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现了点东西
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.42,0:33:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是锁在壁橱里
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.59,0:33:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来在Charlie动过之前 这些都是Robert Wilkinson的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.11,0:33:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以Charlie寻找父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.61,0:33:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这就是他找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.07,0:33:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他曾经杀过动物
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.22,0:33:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然他已经具有谋杀冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.39,0:33:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且...找到这个 肯定让他觉得...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.10,0:33:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他与生俱来的权力
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.07,0:33:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"她们喜欢分享我的感觉"
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.10,0:33:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面有没有关于囚禁她们的地点的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.26,0:33:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,﹣还没找到 ﹣继续找
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.07,0:33:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有和平标记
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.02,0:33:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定在他囚禁她们的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.16,0:33:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Karen Foley说他迫她走出去
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.45,0:33:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得她能承受重返此地的压力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.90,0:33:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.18,0:33:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也看到她了  她在这事隐埋了27年
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.75,0:33:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有选择吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.39,0:33:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你能来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.02,0:33:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道这对你不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.76,0:33:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一路上一直在发抖
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.97,0:33:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾幸存 
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.11,0:33:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让你更加坚强
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.97,0:33:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能行的  妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.85,0:34:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.10,0:34:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.41,0:34:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那气息让我挥之不去
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.76,0:34:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.93,0:34:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是Mary Wilkinson
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.83,0:34:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妻子?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.66,0:34:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他每天晚上都折磨我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.17,0:34:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听不到我的尖叫?!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.28,0:34:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当他折磨完我之后 你会吻他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.08,0:34:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 求你了 别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.43,0:34:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她认为他每天晚上在谷仓做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.97,0:34:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.90,0:34:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问过他为什么想要离开你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.12,0:34:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.66,0:34:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.51,0:34:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你袖手旁观
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.15,0:34:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.10,0:34:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.60,0:34:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在Charlie出世前
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.88,0:34:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回到家
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.33,0:34:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.04,0:34:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他都干了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.07,0:35:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能让我无辜的孩子知道这些
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.68,0:35:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.23,0:35:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.95,0:35:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.11,0:35:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 警长?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.70,0:35:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.78,0:35:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当Charlie回家的时候 你会在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.82,0:35:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是的 别担心 休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.24,0:35:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.38,0:35:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他带我去了哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.01,0:35:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他总是用袋子盖着我的头
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.38,0:35:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的其他感觉可能更强烈
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.76,0:35:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会引导你再走一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.41,0:35:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地面有什么感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.63,0:35:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭上你的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.60,0:35:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走几步
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.21,0:36:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,树叶和树枝
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.13,0:36:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了很久
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.71,0:36:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个斜坡
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.46,0:36:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我摔倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.23,0:36:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么东西又软又冷
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.10,0:36:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但下面覆盖着硬邦邦的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.69,0:36:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如木头?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.43,0:36:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岩石
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.64,0:36:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我还高
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.78,0:36:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这块地的北边
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.13,0:36:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  有发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.70,0:36:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.97,0:36:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮上忙了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.66,0:36:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.78,0:36:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我看见了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.81,0:36:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心  Morgan
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.89,0:37:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.11,0:37:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.45,0:37:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-救救我们  我们在这里 救命 -安全
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.16,0:37:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 我的天
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.06,0:37:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 你还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.21,0:37:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是昏过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.96,0:37:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快叫救护车 医护人员
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.98,0:37:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士?  警长
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.45,0:37:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还有脉搏 但昏过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.97,0:37:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的Charile在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.22,0:37:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mary
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.18,0:37:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.44,0:37:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.65,0:37:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的丈夫会去哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.91,0:37:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战场上有个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.07,0:37:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在山脊那边 -你能带我们去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.10,0:38:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Charlie
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.72,0:38:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道最好别到这儿来烦我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.08,0:38:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI在农场
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.33,0:38:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们查了谷仓  发现很多血迹
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.80,0:38:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警长说你杀了那些失踪的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.78,0:38:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有照片 有书 所有一切
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.86,0:38:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才整晚待在谷仓?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.97,0:38:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都对她们干了什么 Charlie
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.29,0:38:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.83,0:38:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你强奸她们了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.48,0:38:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要有孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.92,0:38:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.25,0:38:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.93,0:38:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个贱人  跟你爸爸一个样
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.66,0:39:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.37,0:39:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他朝我扑过来
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.10,0:39:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我迫不得已
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.55,0:39:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.45,0:39:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不再关心  你会疲惫不堪
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.72,0:39:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你太过关心...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.09,0:39:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又会不堪重负
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.49,0:39:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要尽力就好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.74,0:39:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候我们能幸运破案
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.60,0:39:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而大多数情况却无法如此
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.74,0:39:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这就是工作  不可能尽善尽美
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.97,0:39:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还是关心好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.12,0:39:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的相信吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.12,0:39:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信不可能尽善尽美
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.57,0:40:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我会感觉好些
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.10,0:40:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道 最后的谋杀并不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.62,0:40:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.70,0:40:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没法破案
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.37,0:40:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要找的凶手已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.94,0:40:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来没死
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.10,0:40:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,27年啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.45,0:40:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个案子有多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.70,0:40:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,21年
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.96,0:40:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让它变成22年
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.95,0:40:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.37,0:41:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wordsworth曾写道
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.71,0:41:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"天真的孩子 轻浅的呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.83,0:41:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荡漾着生命的蓬勃朝气
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.35,0:41:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎会嗅到死亡的气息"
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.01,0:41:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要去喝一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.23,0:41:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要来5杯
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.51,0:41:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算我一个
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.19,0:41:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.00,0:41:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说“我不知道” 你也去 孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.42,0:41:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J.?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.19,0:41:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想去  但得改天了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.63,0:41:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 喝啤酒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.40,0:41:25.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.10,0:41:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- Hotchner探员? - 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.45,0:41:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.51,0:41:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Haley提出离婚
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.44,0:41:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被传唤出庭了
