[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.04,0:00:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-州际公路 -又是那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.44,0:00:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察只是执行公务
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.64,0:00:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他干嘛绕着我指挥交通
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.74,0:00:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那天可救了不少性命啊  宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.84,0:00:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.24,0:00:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.44,0:00:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,系好安全带  然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.64,0:00:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 不能打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.74,0:00:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐上车你就得信心十足	
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.34,0:00:40.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样才能觉察…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.84,0:00:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周围的情形
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.54,0:00:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.54,0:00:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.04,0:00:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别啊  今天可是星期天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.44,0:00:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应过的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.04,0:00:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让妈妈带你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.94,0:00:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  Andrea
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.24,0:00:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚饭时我就回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.14,0:01:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你上次也是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.84,0:01:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算以后再告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.24,0:01:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可现在我得看你笑一笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.34,0:01:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.04,0:01:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你拿到驾照
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.54,0:01:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的宝贝座驾了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.64,0:01:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.94,0:01:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在对爸爸没意见了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.54,0:01:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过成绩不能退步
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.54,0:01:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.24,0:01:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  Lisa
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.04,0:01:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lisa  猜猜看谁刚刚得了辆新车
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.14,0:01:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.44,0:01:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要拿到驾照就万事大吉了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.94,0:01:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有… -还有不能退步
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.24,0:01:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Harris先生  你也跟我爸爸说说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.64,0:01:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.84,0:01:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说了吗  又有女孩失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.14,0:01:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy Dewald?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.24,0:01:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识她?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.14,0:01:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是Bennett学校的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.54,0:01:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.64,0:01:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他几个都是大学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.34,0:01:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能不是同一人干的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.84,0:01:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是他轮流找黑人 白人女孩下手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.74,0:02:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没看报纸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.24,0:02:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是他找更年轻的下手  那我们就有麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.64,0:02:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Willam Harris
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.94,0:02:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.94,0:02:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Willam Harris
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.94,0:02:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你因涉嫌绑架Missy Dewald 以及谋杀三名女性被捕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.04,0:02:28.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有权保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.24,0:02:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有逮捕证吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.94,0:02:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去阁楼 车库 仓库看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.24,0:02:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定就在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.74,0:02:36.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的一切将成为呈堂证供
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.64,0:02:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在审讯期间  你有权请律师在场
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.14,0:02:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你请不起  我们会为你指派一名
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.54,0:02:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-明白你的权利了吗 -明白
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.34,0:02:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-William  究竟怎么了 -他们搞错了  我很快就能回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.34,0:02:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.74,0:02:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等够了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.94,0:03:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.44,0:03:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想找你就找个遍吧 Missy Dewald不在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.04,0:03:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个周来  你一直在说 他需要私密和时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.84,0:03:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说他不会把她关在家里 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.74,0:03:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我却听不进去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.14,0:03:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侦探  有证人看见他出现在诱拐地点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.84,0:03:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在亚特兰大他曾有过类型的行为 使用相同的作案手法
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.44,0:03:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他符合侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.64,0:03:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强壮  事业有成  有家室
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.14,0:03:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个地区工作居住
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.54,0:03:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有理由逮捕他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.14,0:03:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我们还没有足够的证据起诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.24,0:03:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一步怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.34,0:03:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到她的关键应该在他家中
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.34,0:03:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得挖掘他生活的方方面面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.64,0:03:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家庭 工作 朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.74,0:03:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探员Mogan和我负责审讯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.14,0:03:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.44,0:03:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在抓住受害者两天后将其杀害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.04,0:03:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy昨天失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.14,0:03:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以只要他被扣留 她活着的机会就很大
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.84,0:03:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在亚特兰大犯过强奸罪 找当时逮捕他的侦探谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.74,0:03:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看该如何下手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.84,0:03:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William是个优秀的诉讼律师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.54,0:04:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得占据优势
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.44,0:04:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他不设防
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.84,0:04:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如抓住他说话中的前后矛盾 这就足够让我们占上风
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.44,0:04:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去调查
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.44,0:04:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能扣留他到上庭为止
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.34,0:04:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12小时内让他开口的可能性有多大
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.94,0:04:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.84,0:05:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能保守秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.04,0:05:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使双唇紧闭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.74,0:05:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指尖也会说话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.14,0:05:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个毛孔都泄露着秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.54,0:05:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西格蒙德 弗洛伊德 (著名心理学家)
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.24,0:05:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他干的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.54,0:05:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些女孩真是被William Harris奸杀的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.14,0:05:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  无可奉告
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.64,0:05:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我女儿足球队的教练
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.84,0:05:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.84,0:05:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在都不敢让她出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.94,0:05:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.44,0:05:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一有消息  我们就会公之于众
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.94,0:05:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.34,0:05:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.34,0:05:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William Harris
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.04,0:05:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是特别探员Derek Morgan 这是特别探员David Rossi
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.84,0:05:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你回答问题之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.54,0:05:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得提醒你  你有权请律师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.94,0:06:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是律师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.34,0:06:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得眼熟吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.84,0:06:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.74,0:06:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.44,0:06:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不认识?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.24,0:06:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个女孩被强奸 扼死  然后被弃尸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.84,0:06:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.44,0:06:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的女人和她们同龄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.54,0:06:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy Dewald昨天失踪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.84,0:06:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么觉得是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.94,0:06:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她被诱拐时 有证人看见你就在商场
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.84,0:06:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有传言说你有过类型的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.84,0:06:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.84,0:06:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说亚特兰大的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.84,0:06:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚特兰大?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.34,0:06:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指控都被撤销了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.14,0:06:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一场误会而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.24,0:06:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为两个遭强奸的受害者不愿指证
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.24,0:06:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你杀人灭口  企图掩盖你的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.84,0:06:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.54,0:07:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 William  你结婚已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.04,0:07:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,18年了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.24,0:07:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得坠入爱河时的感觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.14,0:07:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是全新的体验
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.84,0:07:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳鬓厮磨   发香袭人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.44,0:07:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人兴奋不已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.04,0:07:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怀念那种感觉  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.14,0:07:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和同一个女人结婚18年
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.94,0:07:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像18年来点同一道菜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.34,0:07:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Rossi探员
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.34,0:07:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我多待一分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.34,0:07:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和真正的凶手就多待一分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.34,0:07:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说我们抓错人了?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.24,0:07:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.94,0:07:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像亚特兰大那次一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.64,0:07:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.24,0:07:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你们发现我说的全是实话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.74,0:07:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个可怜的女孩可能已经命丧黄泉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.54,0:07:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你女儿回避吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.74,0:07:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会对她造成困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.34,0:07:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我们之间没有秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.74,0:08:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能说明前24小时内William的行踪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.34,0:08:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸和我们一起待在家里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.64,0:08:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能出去了一个多小时 我不太记得了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.64,0:08:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个女孩被杀  Harris夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.74,0:08:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy Dewald至今下落不明
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.94,0:08:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间紧迫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.44,0:08:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.74,0:08:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果Andrea出了事  你是什么感受呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.04,0:08:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么6个月前搬来佛罗里达
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.94,0:08:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸找到一个待遇更好的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.34,0:08:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与亚特兰大的强奸罪名无关吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.64,0:08:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指控已经撤销了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.24,0:08:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丈夫两次成为嫌疑人 你真觉得这是巧合吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.64,0:08:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一场误会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.64,0:08:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.64,0:08:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William最近和你们疏远了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.94,0:08:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人躲在紧闭的屋里?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他工作繁忙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.24,0:08:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也犯法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.04,0:08:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你已经觉察出不对劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.04,0:08:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也很纳闷
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事只有你会知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.54,0:08:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Harris夫人  不管你家中发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.14,0:08:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能救Missy Dewald一命
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.14,0:09:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.94,0:09:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,询问到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.44,0:09:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有发现吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.54,0:09:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我点时间  会有发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.74,0:09:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  准备好搜查他的电脑了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.24,0:09:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生就准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.44,0:09:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来尽在你掌握啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.84,0:09:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪次能逃过我掌心呢  可爱的小屁屁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.84,0:09:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前为止 William Harris似乎很聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.64,0:09:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将痕迹掩饰得滴水不漏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.84,0:09:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  不过仅仅删除历史
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.74,0:09:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是能从硬盘里找到你那龌龊的网上记录
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.24,0:09:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菜鸟就是菜鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.94,0:09:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.04,0:09:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.74,0:09:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法警
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.44,0:09:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Harris可以和家人交谈几分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.44,0:09:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.54,0:09:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  只要你回家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.94,0:09:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在努力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.94,0:09:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.74,0:09:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  相信我  我全都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.84,0:10:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没法立案
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.94,0:10:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  保释金是500万 他们肯定有什么证据
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.44,0:10:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了亚特兰大的事情之后…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.74,0:10:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那我该怎么办 该拿退休基金里的钱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.34,0:10:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卖房子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.04,0:10:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房子?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.34,0:10:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一有什么事  没了房子我们该去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.14,0:10:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有事的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.74,0:10:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Harris先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.84,0:10:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.04,0:10:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-帮我照顾好妈妈  坚强起来 -我会的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.44,0:10:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我爱你们 -我也爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.64,0:10:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说卖掉房子时  你注意到Sharon的反应了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.94,0:10:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她开始怀疑他了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.34,0:10:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia在查找William的电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.84,0:10:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现了一个加密的网页链接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.34,0:10:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么网页
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.14,0:10:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法搜索  无法追踪的博客
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.44,0:10:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大堆的分类日志   有点像日记
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.04,0:10:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现什么可疑的了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.14,0:10:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了两种不同的语调  两个作者
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.14,0:10:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还发现各种各样特殊的词语 短句  标点符号  拼字法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.04,0:10:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明写日志的不是同一人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.14,0:10:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人叫做苏打水  有人叫做汽水
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.44,0:11:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人用长划线  有人用省略号
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.64,0:11:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这小子你们从哪儿找来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.44,0:11:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在FBI的台阶上发现一个篮子 他就躺在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.54,0:11:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交流的一方提到了恶魔带
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.64,0:11:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.64,0:11:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公路和人行道之间的小型绿化带
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.74,0:11:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今只有在俄亥俄州中部才用这个词
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.14,0:11:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William在亚特兰大住了20年 可他是在Columbus长大的  (俄亥俄州首府)
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.04,0:11:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个使用  "收费公路"   "加油"  这样的词语
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.14,0:11:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是福罗里达的特有方言
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.34,0:11:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  你肯定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.24,0:11:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么进展了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.44,0:11:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心伤了如此之久   早已忘了微笑的模样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.54,0:11:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉前所未有
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.94,0:11:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你在家里很无聊嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.94,0:11:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找小三了?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.34,0:11:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.84,0:11:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我婚姻幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.54,0:11:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妻子知道你的秘密日记吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.54,0:11:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定会对你万无一失的保密措施赞叹不已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.94,0:11:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你们自以为找到什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.04,0:11:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你们弄错了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.44,0:12:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大错特错了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.24,0:12:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有所隐瞒  William
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.44,0:12:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭有人看见我在那个商场 陪审团是不会定罪的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.84,0:12:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为我和其他女人勾搭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.84,0:12:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到Missy了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.04,0:12:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就说过了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.54,0:12:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.14,0:12:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侦探 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.74,0:12:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.44,0:12:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是Missy
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.94,0:12:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我盯着她父亲的眼睛 发誓平安把她带回去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.54,0:12:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她先是失踪  现在被杀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.54,0:12:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道他是在被捕前弃尸?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.14,0:12:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法医估计她的死亡时间是几小时之前
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.94,0:12:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是William Harris一直被扣留啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.04,0:12:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道真抓错人了?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.34,0:12:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想不是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.54,0:12:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他与他人交流联系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.34,0:12:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定他们不会背叛他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.44,0:12:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他没有外遇
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.14,0:12:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.24,0:12:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个同伙尽全力帮助Harris逃脱牢狱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.70,0:13:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.80,0:13:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚唯一的悬念… 虽然很难  但我想出了办法…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.90,0:13:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间简直完美… 我看着他们追着…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.90,0:13:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面几个小时是最美妙的…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.40,0:13:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不能打破信任
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.60,0:13:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到他的同伙了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.20,0:13:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.70,0:13:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太晦涩难懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.30,0:13:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一天过得真快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.80,0:13:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还真是依依不舍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.20,0:13:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一个受害者Kim Groves遇害之后 他们写了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.90,0:13:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得查出他们是如何认识的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.40,0:13:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了解他们的关系很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.50,0:13:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切如此绝望
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.50,0:13:47.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我最终重燃信心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.10,0:13:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎William承认自己的不完整
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.10,0:13:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.50,0:13:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到遇上他的知己  他才开始杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.90,0:13:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不能打破信任
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.10,0:13:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们逍遥法外越久 他们的关系就越牢固
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.10,0:14:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去这俩人不只对奸杀着迷 他们彼此深深吸引
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.10,0:14:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本可以救她的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.50,0:14:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前并没有迹象表现他有同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.70,0:14:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他才如此狂妄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.30,0:14:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的自大是支配型人格的典型表现
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.60,0:14:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他找到了一个愿意为他杀人的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.80,0:14:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的同伙咬人 在Missy Dewald身上发现了咬痕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.60,0:14:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是头一次
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.80,0:14:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William不在场  他就改变行为
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.00,0:14:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许同伙回到了以前习惯的状态
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.20,0:14:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以前曾经干过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.00,0:14:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经让Garcia在其他案件中查找牙医记录
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.70,0:14:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy遇害之前  地区检察官准备起诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.00,0:14:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在该如何继续扣留他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.60,0:14:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这些东西是写给一个男人的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.10,0:14:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来确实有特别之处啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.00,0:14:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们俩只是想爽一把
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.90,0:14:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这些女孩就不会死
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.40,0:14:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪儿认识的他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.00,0:14:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聊天室?  色情网站?  同性恋酒吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.40,0:14:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管这家伙是谁 他都在帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.40,0:15:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你收拾残局
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.30,0:15:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy Dewald死了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.80,0:15:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打电话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.30,0:15:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lee Jarvis
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.60,0:15:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地区检察官
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.00,0:15:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在逮捕证上看到他的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.30,0:15:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的定罪率是全福罗里达州最高的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.70,0:15:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.00,0:15:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的笔友原可以放任她自生自灭 为什么却又要杀了她
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.50,0:15:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jarvis可不喜欢输官司
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.00,0:15:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可不会因为这个案子坏了自己的记录
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的这位朋友实在是想讨你欢心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.50,0:15:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.20,0:15:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竭尽全力保证你不被判刑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.60,0:15:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀了Missy  这样你们又能相聚了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.20,0:15:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然才过了几个小时
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.80,0:15:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是他已经在想你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.10,0:15:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们从这里面究竟发现了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.20,0:15:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证据 证明有人和你一样病态
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.10,0:15:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来福罗里达中部的脑残还真不少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.30,0:15:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的牙医记录与William Harris不符
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.50,0:15:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却与今年早前Manatee郡的一起强奸案相符
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.20,0:15:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  找到相符的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.60,0:15:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  牙印属于同一人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.10,0:15:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他们从未被捕  无法交叉比对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.50,0:16:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那受害者呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.80,0:16:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Connie Mayers
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.30,0:16:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还住在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.10,0:16:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会问你们的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.70,0:16:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.90,0:16:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是买花的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.00,0:16:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些雏菊不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.00,0:16:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在警方记录里称  袭击你的人目的明确
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.30,0:16:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很自信
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.20,0:16:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更像一个控制狂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.10,0:16:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他戴着面具  但我能看出他是个白人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.10,0:16:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他掐住我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.50,0:16:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淤青很久才消散
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.00,0:16:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是光线好的话   我还能看到他掐住我的那双手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.80,0:16:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.10,0:16:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更糟的是咬痕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.80,0:16:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在结疤了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.40,0:16:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后我再没和人交往 所以我没什么可说的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.30,0:16:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我给你包起来 -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.80,0:16:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据Coonie Mayer描述  是个愤怒激发型的强奸犯  和William一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.70,0:16:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说两人都是支配型人格 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.70,0:17:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有道理  他们的文笔类型  都擅长写作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.00,0:17:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很重要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.10,0:17:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同伙犯罪中很少见
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.00,0:17:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们性格相同
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.70,0:17:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们的生活也很相似
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.60,0:17:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Harris去教堂  是家长会的委员
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.90,0:17:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他女儿足球队的教练  不喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.20,0:17:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像个圣人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.60,0:17:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有阴暗面的圣人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.60,0:17:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是他和同伙的共同之处
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.10,0:17:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Prentiss和我去找家人谈谈 看她们知不知道是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.10,0:17:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个强悍型男人可不好突破啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伙肯定关注调查
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.90,0:17:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就来说说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.30,0:17:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我公之于众吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.00,0:17:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有更好的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.70,0:17:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么会看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.70,0:17:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道不是William写的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.20,0:17:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩彼此深深吸引
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.90,0:17:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他需要一个方向 他们共有的文字正是他能依靠的全部
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.10,0:17:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的同伙写道  永远不能打破信任
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.60,0:17:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛对他可是沉重一击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.80,0:17:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需说  William很合作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.40,0:17:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就等着他上钩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.00,0:17:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现William对谁特别注意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.50,0:17:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.20,0:17:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是刻意绕开某人?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.60,0:17:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才搬来6个月
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.30,0:18:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连箱子都没完全打开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.80,0:18:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William哪儿有时间和某人打得火热
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.70,0:18:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们自以为了解所爱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.60,0:18:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是人人都有秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.70,0:18:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要找的人  就像你爸爸一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.00,0:18:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明 强壮  自信
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.40,0:18:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许也有家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.90,0:18:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算指控别人的爸爸也杀人了?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.50,0:18:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好极了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.40,0:18:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不愿意这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.60,0:18:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信这个同伙有过前科
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.00,0:18:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那名受害者说是个白人男子  40来岁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.40,0:18:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你也认识
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.40,0:18:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他有可能找你打听消息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.30,0:18:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.60,0:18:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很担心你爸爸  却无法和他取得联系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.80,0:18:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你妈妈就成了最佳人选
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.70,0:18:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在很不稳定  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.70,0:18:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表现得情绪多变
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.70,0:19:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚特兰大的事情过后  我们说好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.30,0:19:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都要说明白 不能再有误会
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.00,0:19:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.30,0:19:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢住的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.10,0:19:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢  华盛顿还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.00,0:19:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿也很好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可现在这儿和亚特兰大差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.50,0:19:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人人都觉得我爸爸有罪 事情越来越糟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.40,0:19:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.80,0:19:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写得怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.80,0:19:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然置身调查之中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了帮助William 你冒了很大的风险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.50,0:19:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy遇害  说明你们关系匪浅
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.80,0:19:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得知William在我们这边   肯定对你是沉重打击
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.50,0:19:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可不爱这话  看起来William和我们合作
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.70,0:19:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要让他相信 让他对他们的关系产生动摇
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.20,0:19:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数日志都是第一次谋杀后写的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.90,0:20:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  大多都是William所写
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.30,0:20:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想到是这样的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.70,0:20:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望时间不会带走这天的欢愉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.60,0:20:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来看看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.90,0:20:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻笑什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.20,0:20:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Sharon正提出保释 我在想去哪儿吃晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.90,0:20:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是我们错了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.30,0:20:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他们并非都是强悍型男人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.70,0:20:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可能去Salvatores
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.90,0:20:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始由同伙下手  然后他接手
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.30,0:20:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  也很冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.40,0:20:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.40,0:20:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你确实招供了呢 或至少你同伴以为你招供了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.60,0:20:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他别无选择  只有自首 那你就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.60,0:21:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.80,0:21:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都有输不起的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.80,0:21:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为你收拾烂摊子 只是因为他无法承担被捕的后果
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.00,0:21:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了我们写的日志 他会作何反应呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.70,0:21:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道我们读了你们的小情书
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.80,0:21:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们决定自己也写一封
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.80,0:21:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他明白  你在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.40,0:21:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我们合作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.60,0:21:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许此刻他正品尝背叛的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.50,0:21:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果真如此的话  你觉得他会怎么做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.80,0:21:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William  你写道 谢谢这个完美的游戏地点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.30,0:21:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你指的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.50,0:21:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高尔夫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.80,0:21:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高尔夫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.20,0:21:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高尔夫?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.60,0:21:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.10,0:21:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.50,0:21:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没让她们看过我的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.50,0:21:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.40,0:21:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说她会报警吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.00,0:21:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们都想过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.50,0:21:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过怕得要命
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.20,0:21:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.30,0:22:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点倔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.70,0:22:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别冒险了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.30,0:22:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀人…我可不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.50,0:22:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会太难办的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.60,0:22:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说像这样?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.30,0:22:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 就像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.00,0:22:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们这个样子  你可能都认不出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.30,0:22:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面带笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.90,0:22:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些所谓的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.80,0:22:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.50,0:22:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们都是父母的宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.90,0:22:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy Dewald  
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.10,0:22:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原打算和父母吃晚饭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.40,0:22:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才18岁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.30,0:22:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家中的独生女
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.10,0:22:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却夺走了她的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.90,0:22:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真为这些父母难过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.50,0:22:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:22:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见自己的话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.40,0:23:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全口是心非
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.90,0:23:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只说明你根本没有感同身受
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.00,0:23:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.10,0:23:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William  没有他你根本干不了这些
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.00,0:23:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你是不完整的  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.10,0:23:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.80,0:23:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  待在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.20,0:23:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈妈 -待在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.80,0:23:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<i>滚出去</i>
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.10,0:23:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.50,0:23:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 可恶的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.60,0:23:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心 Sharon
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.60,0:23:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会处理好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.50,0:23:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.10,0:24:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心痛了如此之久
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.90,0:24:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要很快再见那张脸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.00,0:24:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的感情确实真挚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.00,0:24:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可否认
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.70,0:24:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 William 
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.80,0:24:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你们不像两兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.60,0:24:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒像两个相爱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.70,0:24:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都不知道自己在胡说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.10,0:24:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.50,0:24:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实不知道爱上一个男人是什么感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.20,0:24:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执法部门的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.40,0:24:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有一种道德优越感
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.60,0:24:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘛  浑身都散发着这种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.20,0:24:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI里的黑人警察
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.30,0:24:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定满腹委屈  极力证明自己
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.60,0:24:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是谁在胡说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.90,0:24:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们其实没什么不同  你和我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.90,0:25:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们选择的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.90,0:25:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为这使我们感觉更强大
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.70,0:25:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.20,0:25:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么证据呢 特别探员Morgan
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.00,0:25:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了合理的怀疑   真有能证明我犯法的证据
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.70,0:25:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别坐在这儿  一脸自鸣得意
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.40,0:25:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我审判 小子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.30,0:25:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.50,0:25:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你的小子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.90,0:25:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脸上的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.60,0:25:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是鄙视你  因为你让我恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.00,0:25:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我一点都不像
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.70,0:25:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我们找到…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.30,0:25:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.00,0:25:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪审团可不会判你无罪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.80,0:25:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.60,0:25:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们互不相让
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.90,0:25:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在看表  等着被保释
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.80,0:25:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是感激不尽
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.70,0:25:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用谢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.00,0:26:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做得还不够好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.60,0:26:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.50,0:26:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven把外面收拾干净了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.40,0:26:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.40,0:26:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea  有点礼貌
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.70,0:26:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  Sharon
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.40,0:26:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为朋友帮忙  我乐意之至
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.40,0:26:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我爸爸什么时候成朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.70,0:26:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.40,0:26:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只需知道  你爸爸很快就会回家
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.10,0:26:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们会忘记这事
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.40,0:26:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会重回正轨  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.80,0:26:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你们愉快
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.00,0:26:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.90,0:26:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很怀疑
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.20,0:26:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.70,0:26:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么突然变得这么友好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.70,0:26:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是FBI探员说的要留意的人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.60,0:26:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸被捕后  他是唯一对我们友好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.30,0:26:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能将他拒之门外
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.20,0:26:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.20,0:26:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么发现
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.20,0:26:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有天 同伙写道
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.30,0:26:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉被冷落  是个局外人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.00,0:26:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人理解我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.10,0:27:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看着他们和孩子们玩闹
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.10,0:27:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复同样的谈话  乏味之极
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.80,0:27:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是有孩子的聚会
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.20,0:27:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  而且很不高兴参加
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.40,0:27:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我环顾四周  一切都变了 生命中唯一的生机
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.80,0:27:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个  藏在后来的日志里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.10,0:27:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他说的却是他们的初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.50,0:27:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我环顾四周  一切都变了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.90,0:27:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命中唯一的生机
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.90,0:27:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如此美好 如此自由  如此奇妙
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.60,0:27:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你6个月前搬来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.40,0:27:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后你遇见他  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.00,0:27:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.70,0:27:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哦 谢谢 -不用谢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.90,0:27:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- Will Harris - Steve Baleman
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.60,0:27:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见你上周搬来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.20,0:27:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-收拾好了吗 -差不多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.70,0:27:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我妻子 Sharon
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.80,0:27:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她人不错
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.20,0:27:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她管家 我管其他
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.20,0:27:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一看就是个好女人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.60,0:27:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我费了些劲
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.70,0:28:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好还是追到了Annie Tranied
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.90,0:28:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.60,0:28:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.20,0:28:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.80,0:28:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.10,0:28:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.30,0:28:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿很多人特别喜欢这种老式乏味的汉堡
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.60,0:28:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可确实没什么特别之处
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.50,0:28:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉再鲜嫩点就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.70,0:28:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还粘着骨头
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.80,0:28:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带着血丝  鲜嫩无比
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.20,0:28:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多种多样  生活才多姿多彩嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.20,0:28:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全同意
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.40,0:28:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.60,0:28:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得好笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.40,0:28:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想起了点事
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.80,0:28:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望是美好回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.20,0:28:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你进了监狱  你就指望着它活了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.00,0:29:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.70,0:29:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你输了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.30,0:29:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直在逃避自我 想要消失无踪
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.80,0:29:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了什么惹毛你的话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.10,0:29:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你会怎么做  伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.50,0:29:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开亚特兰大 这些小小的本能欲望就消失了?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.00,0:29:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此你找了一个自大的邻居
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.10,0:29:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这会让你感觉好些吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.50,0:29:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你感觉更加完整?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.00,0:29:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜效果不佳
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.00,0:29:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都无法让William开心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.00,0:29:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至漂亮的妻子和可爱的女儿都不行
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.80,0:29:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是有天你醒来 发现了他
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.20,0:29:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和你一样病态 一样可怜 于是你的世界全变了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.50,0:29:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是还击我对你的黑人评价吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.70,0:29:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为我们肤色相同 你真以为我们是同样的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.50,0:29:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相同的只有肤色
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.60,0:29:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你伤害无辜
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.60,0:29:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却没有
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.50,0:29:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不是个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.20,0:29:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-事实? -事实
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.00,0:29:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你真有什么证据  我早进监狱了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.40,0:29:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会进去的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.30,0:30:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别出门  Andrea
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.50,0:30:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不安全哦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.80,0:30:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.00,0:30:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸已经进监狱了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.40,0:30:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没什么可担心的了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.00,0:30:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出了什么问题
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.90,0:30:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的问题?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.00,0:30:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们家可没有变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.90,0:30:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.80,0:30:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸犯了强奸罪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.00,0:30:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们才离开亚特兰大 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.40,0:30:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没有
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.30,0:30:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报上可不是这么说的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.30,0:30:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和那些女孩差不多大
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.60,0:30:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定拿你先开刀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.90,0:30:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 嘿 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.80,0:30:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.40,0:30:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都回家去  快
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.30,0:30:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻逼
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.70,0:30:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.60,0:30:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  一群白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.80,0:30:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你妈妈出门了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.70,0:30:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要有人陪伴  尽管来找我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.20,0:30:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  真的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.40,0:31:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid  我们要找出聚会地点
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.50,0:31:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再来一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.60,0:31:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是连环杀手  和同伙通信
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.50,0:31:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要开一个秘密博客
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.20,0:31:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以安全地再现犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.30,0:31:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有人看见或听见
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.80,0:31:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.90,0:31:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎他们轮流给对方惊喜
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.80,0:31:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听这个  我喜欢挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.70,0:31:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间总是完美
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.60,0:31:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢今晚  虽然很难
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.20,0:31:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是想出办法了  我不可阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.90,0:31:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.60,0:31:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从没写时间
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.60,0:31:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他们怎么知道见面时间
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.10,0:31:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven  你在干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.60,0:31:39.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别走  我们得谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.90,0:31:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过  别烦我
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.20,0:31:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么发现
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.20,0:31:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4个受害者被诱拐的时间都不相同
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.30,0:32:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个甚至是在感恩节早上去超市的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.70,0:32:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了博客  神秘先生的电话和电脑都没有可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.60,0:32:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有文档 数字 文件都查过了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.90,0:32:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么联系
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.40,0:32:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们漏掉了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.10,0:32:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据这个地区的语言和信息
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.80,0:32:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伙很有可能是土生土长的佛罗里达人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.80,0:32:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  假设同伙就住在Sarasota
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.90,0:32:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不打电话  不写信
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.20,0:32:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能使用的是可视  或可听见的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.10,0:32:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是可视的   可能在房屋上挂一面旗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.70,0:32:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是可听见的  显然他们住得很近
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.60,0:32:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可视
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.50,0:32:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可听见
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.40,0:32:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是…
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.10,0:32:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们写的不是诗呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.20,0:32:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一是歌词呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.40,0:32:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如此美好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.20,0:32:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此自由  如此奇妙
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.70,0:32:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再念些
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.00,0:33:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切如此美妙  正是今晚我需要
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.70,0:33:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.60,0:33:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  就是这首歌 我们抓捕他时放的就是这首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.40,0:33:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一辆车里传出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.80,0:33:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是信号   所以他们知道回去杀了Missy Dewald
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.10,0:33:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伙就住在附近  他们就是在那儿认识的 社区聚会
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.60,0:33:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  找出是哪个邻居
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.00,0:33:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说些条件
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.40,0:33:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白人 男性
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.50,0:33:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已婚 有子女
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.50,0:33:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作稳定  或自己有公司
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.20,0:33:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直住在佛罗里达
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.40,0:33:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William附近的  一共有7个白人男子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.80,0:33:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5个已婚生子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.50,0:34:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2个土生土长
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.60,0:34:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人残疾
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.40,0:34:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人做房地产
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.80,0:34:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊   他就在隔壁
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.40,0:34:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven Baleman
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.30,0:34:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven Baleman
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.80,0:34:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟踪我?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.00,0:34:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.58,0:34:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怒气冲冲地走了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.18,0:34:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么生气
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.08,0:35:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他成天这样
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.58,0:35:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.78,0:35:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.88,0:35:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.78,0:35:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William被捕后  他变得坏脾气紧张  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.98,0:35:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven是好人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.58,0:35:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和你想的不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.38,0:35:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.18,0:35:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.68,0:35:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到Andrea了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.18,0:35:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.28,0:35:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Annie怎么哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.78,0:35:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认为Steven就是William的同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.08,0:35:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.28,0:35:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在找他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.58,0:35:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.08,0:35:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea说他突然对我们友好 这很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.28,0:35:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来看我们
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.48,0:35:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我没当回事  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.78,0:35:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他们都不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.78,0:35:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该去和Willam谈谈了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.48,0:35:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 Steven Baleman不只是你的邻居
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.98,0:35:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.38,0:35:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.28,0:35:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些什么都证明不了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.98,0:35:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们以为找出我邻居是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.38,0:35:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像取得了小小的胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.28,0:36:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven把Andrea带哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.28,0:36:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.38,0:36:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怀疑他
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.68,0:36:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在两人都不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.08,0:36:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能这样 她那么信任你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.08,0:36:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不见了?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.78,0:36:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不见踪影  我就知道你不是去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.28,0:36:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为或许 或许 
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.48,0:36:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你有了外遇
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.28,0:36:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法找你对质 我害怕一开口  一切就成真了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.88,0:36:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真该发现你谎言下的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.48,0:36:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长久以来 你一直在撒谎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.28,0:36:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个骗子 
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.98,0:36:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切太沉重了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.08,0:36:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人受得了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.28,0:36:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过就快结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.68,0:36:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有卖掉房子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.58,0:36:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有提出保释?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.58,0:36:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在亚特兰大的时候  我就不愿相信
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.18,0:36:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我不能再自欺欺人了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.88,0:36:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven把Andrea带哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.08,0:37:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.58,0:37:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.68,0:37:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何 William
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.48,0:37:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见你干的好事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.08,0:37:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kim Groves  你写道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.58,0:37:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最开始的几小时是最美妙的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.48,0:37:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精力充沛
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.38,0:37:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea失踪了两个小时
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.78,0:37:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻他在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.38,0:37:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在做什么  William
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.58,0:37:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抚摸她?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.48,0:37:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬她?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.08,0:37:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在场时  这就是他的所作所为
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.18,0:37:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的小男朋友失去理智了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.18,0:37:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些你的宝贝女儿在他手上
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.48,0:37:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我们更清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.28,0:37:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一直饱受痛苦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.88,0:37:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven带走了你的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.88,0:38:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无比信任的人背叛了你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.68,0:38:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说  没什么是神圣的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.18,0:38:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Steven Baleman有几处地产 不过目前为止  没有线索
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.58,0:38:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有他知道Steven把Andrea带去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.88,0:38:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为了保护同伙  竟然连女儿都不顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.08,0:38:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是在保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.28,0:38:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一开口  就难逃其罪
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.58,0:38:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Missy被绑架的时候 你是怎么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.08,0:38:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头看看我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.38,0:38:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每过一分钟  他就和她多待一分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.28,0:38:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在轮到Andrea了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.48,0:38:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟怎么回事 伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.78,0:38:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么直接冲出去  救你的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.68,0:38:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他不会伤害她吗  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.98,0:38:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有约定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.48,0:38:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不碰家人?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.98,0:38:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这儿越久 Steven的情况就越糟
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.88,0:38:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以为你背叛了他 现在轮到他了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.68,0:38:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打破了信任
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.18,0:38:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在和你的女儿在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.48,0:39:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能正哭喊着叫你
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.98,0:39:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 爸爸 你为什么不来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.38,0:39:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  因为你就站在这儿 一动不动
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.28,0:39:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.68,0:39:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你能阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.68,0:39:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个男人样  拿出做父亲的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.98,0:39:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.28,0:39:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.08,0:39:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.98,0:39:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Steven  是Steven 我不知道他去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.08,0:39:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你离开这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.48,0:39:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他伤害你了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.48,0:39:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会伤害她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.48,0:39:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我背叛你了?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.68,0:39:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你已背叛了我?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.58,0:39:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.68,0:40:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没告诉他们?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.08,0:40:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.58,0:40:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你怎么知道我在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.08,0:40:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea  亲爱的  相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.38,0:40:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都交给爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.58,0:40:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好了的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.58,0:40:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远不能打破信任
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.78,0:40:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带走了我的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.28,0:40:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她跟踪我
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.78,0:40:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她什么都不会说的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.28,0:40:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不会说?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.98,0:40:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.88,0:40:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Andrea  相信我  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.58,0:40:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.98,0:40:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,案子取消了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.48,0:40:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.78,0:40:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么简单?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.38,0:40:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被拘留时  你杀了Missy Dewald 他们证据不足
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.98,0:40:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说起了Missy  我们有证据了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.38,0:40:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀了Missy Dewald  还有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.18,0:40:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都是你杀的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.28,0:40:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.38,0:40:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.08,0:40:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.68,0:40:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直支持你
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.58,0:41:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我没出现 
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.88,0:41:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.68,0:41:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会杀了她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.68,0:41:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.18,0:41:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.38,0:41:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想逃
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.48,0:41:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你  我恨你
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.28,0:41:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 带我离开这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.28,0:41:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想离开 -好的  你会没事的  我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.88,0:42:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙只想再见他同伙一面
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.98,0:42:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们需要道别
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.68,0:42:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩算好了一切
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.38,0:42:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却猜错了结局
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.68,0:42:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英国历史学家C.Northcote Parkinson说过
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.68,0:42:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖延是最厉害的拒绝
