[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.07,0:00:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Hotchner先生? -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.47,0:00:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进  他正等你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.57,0:00:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.77,0:00:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只叫了你一个人 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.47,0:00:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们肯定是好朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.57,0:00:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我们只是大约十年前在一起工作过  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.87,0:00:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸运的话  他能撑过今晚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.47,0:00:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能缓解他的疼痛   对他也是一大幸事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.47,0:00:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<i>Tom Shaunessy侦探</i>
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.07,0:00:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<i>死神: 波士顿的连环杀手 FBI侧写员追踪</i>
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.87,0:00:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  Tom
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.37,0:00:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.67,0:00:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.17,0:00:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气  Tom
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.17,0:01:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你为什么叫我来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.57,0:01:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.27,0:01:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有抓住他  我就终止了调查
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.57,0:01:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命案停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.77,0:01:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你打道回府
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.37,0:01:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该知道原因
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.87,0:01:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.17,0:01:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与魔鬼的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不再追踪我 我将不再杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们俩都活着
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.47,0:01:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.77,0:01:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你同意我的条件
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.17,0:01:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在密歇根邮报上刊登一则私人广告
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.47,0:01:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一份合约
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.47,0:01:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们彼此都履行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.57,0:01:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们没有抓他
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.57,0:01:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这份合约不管用  我会重开调查
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.17,0:01:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是它却生效了  命案停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.97,0:01:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我让你回去之前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.67,0:01:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等了六周 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.77,0:02:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  Tom  你怎么知道他停手了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.27,0:02:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他只是去了别处
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.07,0:02:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有   我一直关注着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.47,0:02:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他停手了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.17,0:02:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是当时我们的调查迟早会出现转机的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.87,0:02:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那在出现转机之前
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.87,0:02:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有多少人要丧命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赌上那些性命值得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.47,0:02:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没有做出决定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.17,0:02:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让他侥幸逃脱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.77,0:02:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你必须帮我赎罪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.47,0:02:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.87,0:02:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合约就快到期了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.57,0:02:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他正看着我   他知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.37,0:02:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直在等着这一天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.87,0:02:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为他会再次大开杀戒?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.57,0:02:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这么做是想挽救性命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.47,0:02:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你告诉受害者的家属
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.77,0:02:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.77,0:02:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你告诉他们…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.87,0:02:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他们我别无选择
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.87,0:02:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你的歉意转达给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.57,0:03:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  Aaron Hotchner
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.07,0:03:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,O'Mara警官有号码
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.67,0:03:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.87,0:03:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.77,0:03:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.17,0:03:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密歇根邮报  1998年3月7日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.57,0:03:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.67,0:03:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,<i>如果你不再追踪他们 我也将不再追踪你  直到死亡</i>
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.87,0:03:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.87,0:03:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了  我能知道是关于什么的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.17,0:03:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.17,0:03:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如…波士顿死神?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.67,0:03:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道BAU调查过这个案子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.97,0:03:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1998年  那是我作为首席侧写员 接手的第一个案子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.07,0:03:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我说得不对
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.07,0:03:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我们的系统里没有关于死神的侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.57,0:03:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止  Penelope  你可以回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.87,0:03:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.47,0:03:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安  长官
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.37,0:03:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.57,0:04:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.27,0:04:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这么快地解脱 其实是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.77,0:04:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.77,0:04:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.57,0:04:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.47,0:05:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个轮胎都没气了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.87,0:05:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能两个都没气了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.57,0:05:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.37,0:05:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我打给汽车协会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.17,0:05:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是我们呢  你也希望有人帮你 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.67,0:05:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.77,0:05:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  两个轮胎没气了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.17,0:05:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个备胎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.37,0:05:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nina Hale
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.87,0:05:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,128号公路
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.67,0:05:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我拿我的给你换上  看能不能用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.17,0:05:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  我女朋友打给汽车协会了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.07,0:05:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我给你我的地址吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.97,0:05:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以用  你就给我寄张支票好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.47,0:05:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想整个晚上都耗在这儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.17,0:05:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随你便  只要你没事就好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.17,0:05:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  那我还是试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.07,0:05:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.47,0:06:01.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个轮胎没气了  我们只有一个备胎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.37,0:06:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.27,0:06:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚过Needham镇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.47,0:06:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在很感激
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.97,0:06:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很乐意帮上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.77,0:06:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Evan?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.77,0:06:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Evan
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.57,0:06:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手表给我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.47,0:06:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.17,0:06:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你别伤害我们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.47,0:06:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会疼的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.97,0:06:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  别
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.57,0:06:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会对你开枪的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.47,0:06:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.07,0:06:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.07,0:07:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nina
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.57,0:07:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撞到头了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.07,0:07:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nina死了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.27,0:07:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害怕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.57,0:07:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该觉得害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.14,0:08:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祸不单行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗马作家 Publilius Syrus
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.64,0:08:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.64,0:08:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  你想随时了解 波士顿发生的异常命案?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.64,0:08:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去波士顿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.34,0:08:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是应该先等正式的协查请求吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.04,0:08:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当地警方没有请求我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.04,0:08:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.54,0:08:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们要去波士顿了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.24,0:08:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神受控制欲驱使
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.44,0:08:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为什么他会提出停手的条件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.24,0:08:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀人给他以力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.64,0:08:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是多次杀人后  这种快感减弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.24,0:08:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是他决定转变策略
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.54,0:08:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提出条件使他觉得拥有最大程度的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.44,0:08:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是杀人无法相比的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.74,0:08:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至还为他出了书
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.94,0:08:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他赢了  那为什么又开始杀人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.84,0:08:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为唯一知道他赢了的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.64,0:09:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他达成交易的人  刚刚死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.44,0:09:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自恋型凶手需要他人认可自己的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.24,0:09:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们通知媒体
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.94,0:09:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他如何在10年内停手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.64,0:09:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在<死神之夜>一书中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.94,0:09:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作者暗示他因为其他案件而被捕  或死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.94,0:09:16.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许他想纠正此误解
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.24,0:09:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这些年来他一直在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.84,0:09:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划再次杀人 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.94,0:09:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从95年到98年
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.34,0:09:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他枪杀  刺杀  打死21个受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.14,0:09:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性  女性
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.64,0:09:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害者遍布各个年龄层  各种类型
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.44,0:09:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有特定的受害者类型  没有作案手法 你当初怎么侧写的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.44,0:09:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没找到机会侧写 Shaunessy就让我们回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.14,0:09:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BTK Zodiac和死神有相似之处 (均为连环杀手)
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.04,0:09:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都很聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.54,0:09:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受过训练  虐待成性
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.94,0:09:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其故事都被写成书
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.54,0:09:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头脑聪明或许只是一小部分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.84,0:09:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神和Zodiac杀手从未被捕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.54,0:09:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BTK杀手是在25年后才落网的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.14,0:09:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他去出版社理论
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.14,0:09:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书中他的结局是死亡  搬走或被监禁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.34,0:09:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:09:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到媒体  当这消息一公布
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.24,0:09:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定天下大乱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.24,0:10:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们知道了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.64,0:10:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波士顿警局会被挤破门
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.44,0:10:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对外宣布是模仿作案越久
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.04,0:10:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越有机会抓到他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.84,0:10:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Rossi Prentiss Morgan去警局
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.94,0:10:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,着手调查一切
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.84,0:10:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ和Reid  我们去案发现场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.94,0:10:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我调查了死神的案子18个月
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.84,0:10:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有任何证据证明 这个可怕的案件不是模仿作案
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.34,0:10:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会第一个告诉你们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.44,0:10:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我没有回你电话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.84,0:10:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看得出来  我很忙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.44,0:10:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是模仿作案 Mike
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.64,0:10:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望是  但其实不是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.04,0:10:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言  你并不了解
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.64,0:10:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没有请求你的协助
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.44,0:10:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Shaunessy叫我来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.24,0:10:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想请求协查吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.44,0:10:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.04,0:10:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会毁了警局
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.24,0:10:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是特别探员Jennifer Jareau
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.44,0:10:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Spencer Reid博士 这是Mike O'Mara侦探
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.04,0:10:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警局里布置好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.74,0:10:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这儿就交给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.24,0:11:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们需要的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.44,0:11:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.94,0:11:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nina Hale  19岁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.44,0:11:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Evan Harvey  23岁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.84,0:11:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nina被割喉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.14,0:11:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被刺46刀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.84,0:11:12.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Evan被重击  然后被枪击
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.64,0:11:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有发现弹壳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.24,0:11:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢左轮手枪  .44口径
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.34,0:11:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女性受害者约年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.14,0:11:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他花的时间就越多  通常凶器是刀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.24,0:11:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她手腕上有一圈没被晒黑的皮肤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.34,0:11:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能戴着手表或其他东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.54,0:11:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到他的钱包了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.14,0:11:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神从所有受害者身上拿走物品 再放在下一个受害者身边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.74,0:11:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们知道是他作案
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.44,0:11:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有矫正镜片
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.84,0:11:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜不是他的?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.14,0:11:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只从一个受害者身上拿走了眼镜 第九个受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.44,0:11:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们原本应该在第十个受害者身上找到 却没有找到
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.24,0:11:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有找到眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.14,0:11:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九个受害者有什么特别之处吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.14,0:11:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他逃过一劫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.14,0:11:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,George Foyet  28岁  第九个受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.34,0:11:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一一个从死神手中逃脱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.84,0:11:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过挣扎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.54,0:11:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amanda Bertrand 19岁   那晚他们在约会
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.84,0:11:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没有他走运
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.64,0:12:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢在车里或车旁袭击他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.64,0:12:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜晚  光线昏暗 人烟稀少的公路上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.24,0:12:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet说他假装迷路的游客 以此接近他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.34,0:12:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在医院里  我们让Foyet向画像员 描述凶手的长相
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.14,0:12:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神通常使用某种花招
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.94,0:12:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此接近受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.24,0:12:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他画的这只眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.04,0:12:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很像上帝之眼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.04,0:12:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被美国政府所采用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.94,0:12:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1782年  被作为美国国玺图案 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.44,0:12:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国玺背面印着拉丁文annuit coeptis 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.74,0:12:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是神佑我邦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.14,0:12:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来死神自认为是上帝的化身
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.74,0:12:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那Foyet如何逃脱的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.84,0:12:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,911  你有什么紧急情况
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.04,0:12:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚又杀了两个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.84,0:12:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 先生  你说你又杀了两个人?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.74,0:12:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第8个  第9个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.84,0:12:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Riverton镇的一辆银色丰田车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.74,0:12:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过Tyson Quarry区
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.64,0:12:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是由一个付费电话打出的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.14,0:12:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离案发现场大约一英里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.44,0:12:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救护车15分钟后到达
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.24,0:12:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bertrand送达时已死 Foyet呼吸微弱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.04,0:13:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次杀人后  死神打电话 告诉警察尸体的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.44,0:13:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到第9个受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.94,0:13:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他没打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.04,0:13:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet也就不会被及时发现
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.84,0:13:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那通电话救了他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.84,0:13:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说在这次之后 死神不再打911
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.94,0:13:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.44,0:13:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他学乖了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.84,0:13:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个案发现场留下Foyet的眼镜是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.14,0:13:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet可能有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.34,0:13:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.54,0:13:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  外面有个记者坚持要见你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.14,0:13:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roy Colson  他说他认识你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.24,0:13:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roy
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.14,0:13:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotchner探员
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.34,0:13:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真是模仿作案的话 你在这儿又是做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮警察抓凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.14,0:13:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真这么想的?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.94,0:13:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  我写了本关于这家伙的书
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.94,0:13:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还签了名  送给你一本
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.44,0:13:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你收到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.44,0:13:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正式地说  我们没有理由认为他不是模仿作案
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.34,0:13:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那私下呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.94,0:13:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roy  你觉得什么更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.24,0:13:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找故事  还是找凶手?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.24,0:13:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.94,0:13:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我见过那些受害者家属
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.14,0:13:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲述受害者的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.74,0:14:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你读了我的书  就会知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.14,0:14:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,书写得不错  Roy
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.44,0:14:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给予受害者以尊重
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.74,0:14:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我们的描写也公正客观
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.74,0:14:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的稿费我都给了受害者家属
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.44,0:14:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  所以我才来见你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.34,0:14:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有什么可以告诉你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.84,0:14:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会给你打电话的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.84,0:14:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.44,0:14:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是他的话  不会太久的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.44,0:14:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.74,0:14:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.84,0:14:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  别
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.34,0:14:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一没超速  二没喝酒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.74,0:14:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好 警官
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.84,0:14:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驾照  登记证  保险证明
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.14,0:14:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上回来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.34,0:14:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他居然连拦车的原因都不说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.34,0:15:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  一会儿就好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.94,0:15:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要给你记一次警告
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.04,0:15:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警告?   为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.74,0:15:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在错误的时间  出现在错误的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.24,0:15:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.94,0:15:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我要杀了你的妻子 Arthur
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.24,0:15:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  别
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.06,0:15:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一对遇害夫妇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.76,0:15:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次年纪大得多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.36,0:15:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人中弹  一人遇刺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.16,0:15:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无故在这儿停车
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.56,0:15:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的驾照和登记证散落在钱包外
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.76,0:15:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他又耍花招
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.46,0:15:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地点选得不错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.46,0:15:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荒郊野外  过往车辆稀少
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.66,0:16:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他留下了Nina Hale的手表
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.16,0:16:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那他带走了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.96,0:16:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的结婚戒指
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.06,0:16:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Arthur和Diane Lanessa
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.06,0:16:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Weymouth镇人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.66,0:16:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结婚32年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.86,0:16:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从Elks回家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.36,0:16:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每周两次去那儿玩宾果游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.26,0:16:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去通知家属
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.36,0:16:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想找个人和你一起去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.16,0:16:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.36,0:16:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他翻了她的钱包
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.76,0:16:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在找什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.86,0:16:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问号是新的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.96,0:16:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是给我们的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.96,0:16:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在说  这不是命运
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.06,0:16:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在说 我们有十年时间挽救他们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.56,0:17:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的两起命案是我们的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.76,0:17:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一个问号中就能看出这么多 真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.06,0:17:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我揭开他的真实身份  会知道得更多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.86,0:17:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.56,0:17:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是对死神进行了侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.86,0:17:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为在侧写前 我们就被中止了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.56,0:17:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被中止了刚  我开始侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.96,0:17:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就停止杀人  所以正式说来我们完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.56,0:17:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这个案子...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.46,0:17:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没放弃这个案子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.66,0:17:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年我一直回到这儿来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.36,0:17:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人调查
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.36,0:17:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从没告诉其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.46,0:17:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我一直说侧写是集体的智慧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.46,0:17:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这次不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.26,0:17:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  或许如果…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.56,0:17:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我错了  我会误导大家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.06,0:17:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是现在你觉得自己是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.26,0:17:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看得越多  越觉得正确
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.56,0:17:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.06,0:17:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就听听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.66,0:17:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神符合我们对无特定目标凶手的侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.46,0:17:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和大多数连环杀手不同
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.86,0:17:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不以某一类型的受害者为目标
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.16,0:17:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他更多的注意年轻的女性受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.26,0:17:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本质上他是一个掠夺者  任何人都会杀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.86,0:18:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他无选择杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.66,0:18:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他杀人和受害者本身并无关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.36,0:18:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他需要被认同  需要被我们所知
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.56,0:18:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,符号 把前一受害者的物品 放在后一受害者身上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.26,0:18:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.36,0:18:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.46,0:18:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.26,0:18:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给Shaunessy的信就是最明显的例子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.46,0:18:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让Tom Shaunessy向他屈服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.26,0:18:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不堪重负
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.86,0:18:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在某种真实的感受中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.46,0:18:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Tom Shaunessy是死神的第22个受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.66,0:18:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像BTK杀手 Dennis Rader
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.76,0:18:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神受过严格的训练
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.96,0:18:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他的日常生活中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会让他非常倔强顽固 无法与人产生亲密关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.26,0:18:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或与他人共事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.86,0:18:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信凶手还有另一个兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.56,0:18:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这给了我们抓住他的绝好机会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.06,0:18:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神最新的一个受害者是一名老妇人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.06,0:18:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他迅速地一枪了结她
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.06,0:18:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在前一名更年轻的受害者身上 他花了更多时间 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.46,0:18:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连刺46刀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.56,0:18:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.46,0:18:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他特别关注年轻的女性受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.26,0:18:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择的凶器是刀  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.36,0:18:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能深入体内的替代工具
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.86,0:19:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害者越年轻  他花的精力和时间越多
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.46,0:19:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他有恋幼癖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.16,0:19:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋幼癖?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.06,0:19:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被青春期  青春期前的人所吸引
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.86,0:19:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找有此权利的人  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.46,0:19:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中老师  辅导员 教练
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.26,0:19:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近十年内被指控性侵犯少女的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.86,0:19:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.86,0:19:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia找不到George Foyet
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.66,0:19:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一无所获 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.96,0:19:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.86,0:19:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他消失了  完全人间蒸发
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.36,0:19:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不见踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.46,0:19:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.76,0:19:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9个月前  他出院后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.66,0:19:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他辞职  卖车  注销银行账户
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.66,0:19:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取消信用卡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.06,0:19:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手机  公寓 一切
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.56,0:19:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有他的资料  那就完全追查不到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.16,0:19:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到他  因为他消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.56,0:19:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他是故意的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.66,0:19:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.16,0:19:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算人死了 资料也能保存几十年
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.06,0:19:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  要像这样把自己完全抹去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.66,0:19:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当困难
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.06,0:19:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要极强的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.36,0:19:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须愿意切断与所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.66,0:19:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有事情的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.16,0:20:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像…自杀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.86,0:20:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得说  这太强了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.66,0:20:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他经历过这种事之后 你能怪他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.86,0:20:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet是唯一知道死神长相的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.36,0:20:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.66,0:20:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们还是要找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.86,0:20:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我继续找
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.86,0:20:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  我们的时间不多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.36,0:20:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.76,0:20:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他完全与世隔绝
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.26,0:20:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定是独自一人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.56,0:20:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你如何切断所有的关系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.06,0:20:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总得和人交谈  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.56,0:20:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Colson
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.26,0:20:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roy  我是Aaron Hotchner 想请你帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.76,0:20:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Colson怎么找到这家伙的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.66,0:20:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为写书  他采访过Foyet
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.56,0:20:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们保持联系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.86,0:20:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们是朋友? -算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.46,0:20:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是Foyet没有给他手机号码
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.46,0:20:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他给了他一个别名的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.46,0:20:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.96,0:20:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,George Foyet?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.26,0:21:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我们是FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.56,0:21:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Rossi探员 我是Hotchner探员
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.96,0:21:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们见过一面  还记得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.76,0:21:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 记得
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.36,0:21:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,介意进屋再说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.96,0:21:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么找到我的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.06,0:21:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roy Colson
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.56,0:21:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要很久吗   我可不能上班迟到
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.76,0:21:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么工作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.96,0:21:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是自由职业者  电脑专家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.56,0:21:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰你  我们会尽快的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.76,0:21:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.56,0:21:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这不是模仿作案
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.96,0:22:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.26,0:22:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.76,0:22:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来打算那晚向她求婚
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.56,0:22:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在餐厅里   可是我太紧张了 临阵退缩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.36,0:22:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当他靠近我们时  戒指还在我口袋里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.36,0:22:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他迷路了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.06,0:22:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着一本观光手册
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.26,0:22:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正看的时候 他朝我一刀刺来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.26,0:22:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet  你没必要再回忆一次
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.46,0:22:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我动不了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.86,0:22:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能坐在那儿  血流不止
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.16,0:22:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睁睁看着他杀了Mandy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.56,0:22:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他朝她刺了67刀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.66,0:22:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道刺67刀需要多久吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.16,0:22:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到那枚戒指
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.56,0:23:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他本应该把你的眼镜放在下一个受害者身上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.06,0:23:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是却没有
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.66,0:23:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直留着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.16,0:23:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得他对我有特别的兴趣吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.06,0:23:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这11年来  我一直想着这个可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.76,0:23:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近你有没有收到奇怪的信件或电话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.76,0:23:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或什么麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.06,0:23:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的几处房子全用的是其他名字
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.16,0:23:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我时不时地变换住处
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.66,0:23:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢找小车下手  所以我坐公车
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.66,0:23:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我   我用尽全力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.16,0:23:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想忘掉你们刚刚说起的事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.56,0:23:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要知道你的其他名字   其他住所  以便随时保持联系
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.66,0:23:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在事情结束之前   我们可以带你去个安全的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.66,0:23:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我的家在波士顿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.76,0:23:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发过誓  不会让他把我的家也一并夺走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.36,0:23:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们在这儿保护你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.06,0:23:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们保护不了我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.96,0:23:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人能保护我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.86,0:24:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些千万要放好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.46,0:24:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.46,0:24:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会妥善保管的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.96,0:24:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是个人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.16,0:24:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个凡人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.26,0:24:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们就抓不住他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.66,0:24:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.36,0:24:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.96,0:24:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这东西扔在我办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.16,0:24:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿去实验室
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.06,0:24:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要写这个故事吗  Roy
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.46,0:24:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不写  他也会找其他人的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.06,0:24:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.16,0:24:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他来说  你很特别 他想让你知道他为什么停手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.56,0:24:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.76,0:24:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你写了他的传记  Roy
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.56,0:24:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  这十年来  这些故事他读了几千遍
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.36,0:24:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的书是支持他的动力
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.86,0:25:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得  你最了解他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.76,0:25:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最关心他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.56,0:25:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得十年前街上是什么情景吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.46,0:25:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人人自危?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.06,0:25:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时人们相信警察
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.46,0:25:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不把Shaunessy的事写进去
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.06,0:25:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这就是故事  写吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.26,0:25:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你在叫我做什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.96,0:25:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没叫你做任何事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.06,0:25:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我一辈子遇到的最重要的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.96,0:25:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的  绝对独家
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.46,0:25:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我允许你独家全程跟进BAU的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.46,0:25:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到我们抓住他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.26,0:25:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  如果我去掉这个故事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.46,0:25:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我可没说
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.26,0:25:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全程跟进?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.66,0:25:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是第一个
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.46,0:25:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.56,0:25:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.66,0:25:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…我是说  如果你们抓不到他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.96,0:25:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你要冒风险了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.56,0:26:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotchner
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.56,0:26:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.36,0:26:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不再追踪我 我将不再追踪他们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.96,0:26:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我会接受吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.36,0:26:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个条件不错
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.76,0:26:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看错你了  我以为你会更聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.56,0:26:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该接受条件
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.36,0:26:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你也看错我了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.16,0:26:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你最后的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.36,0:26:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不做交易
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.36,0:26:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作就是追踪像你这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.66,0:26:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人像我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.76,0:26:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这种人都是这么认为
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.46,0:26:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.46,0:26:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很快就会见面
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.86,0:27:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点你就赶不上了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.76,0:27:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开车
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.16,0:27:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个路灯右转
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.76,0:27:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把珠宝和钱包统统拿出来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.96,0:27:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿停车
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.66,0:27:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱你都拿走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.96,0:27:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别伤人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.76,0:27:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.12,0:28:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6具尸体  不包括司机
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.42,0:28:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用的是枪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.02,0:28:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能不只一把
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.62,0:28:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人用的是刀
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.42,0:28:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Arthur Lanessa的结婚戒指
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.92,0:28:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拿走了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.42,0:28:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很重要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.82,0:28:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.02,0:28:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚他打电话来酒店 向我提条件
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.82,0:28:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.92,0:28:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挂了电话 然后他就下手了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.72,0:28:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是你的错?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.22,0:28:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.72,0:28:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿  用我的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.02,0:28:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的话我信了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.62,0:28:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  你挂了他的电话
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.82,0:29:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上是你杀死了他们  动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.22,0:29:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛快了结了  别担心我们
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.22,0:29:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有你  我们照样抓住那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.52,0:29:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Dave  为了这事  我用了十年时间
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.72,0:29:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Shaunessy接受了条件
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.02,0:29:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他停止杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.02,0:29:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他终结了案子  把FBI赶回去
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.32,0:29:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10年来  你处理其他案子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.22,0:29:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我一直没忘这件案子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.52,0:29:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直惦记着这个侧写
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.22,0:29:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  我退休了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.62,0:29:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我巡回开新书签售会时
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.62,0:29:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生的每起命案  我都该怪罪自己吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.82,0:29:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  如果你想像Shaunessy Gideon那样
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.72,0:29:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都怪在自己头上  那就动手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.72,0:29:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你头脑里有个声音在说
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.82,0:29:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是因为你的良知
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.22,0:29:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是你的自尊心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.52,0:29:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我们的错 Aaron
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.42,0:29:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那些坏人 
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.72,0:29:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们要侧写他们
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.02,0:29:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他们犯下的错
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.42,0:29:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是尽职尽责
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.52,0:29:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们停手
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.22,0:29:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人也会的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.32,0:29:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.02,0:29:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.82,0:29:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我没说过
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.52,0:30:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.62,0:30:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得可真好  不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.92,0:30:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子总说我有表演的天赋
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.32,0:30:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪一个
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.82,0:30:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一个
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.62,0:30:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.42,0:30:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.52,0:30:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 写你的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.02,0:30:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没关系了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.42,0:30:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的  不过我会去掉Shaunessy的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.12,0:30:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害者家人不需要知道这事
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.52,0:30:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少在你抓到凶手之前
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.32,0:30:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.42,0:30:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet打来电话  他想见见我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.12,0:30:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把他的地址告诉我们  他生气了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.52,0:30:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得他不想和人谈话
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.32,0:30:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神会杀了他  只是时间问题
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.72,0:30:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会是第一个
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.02,0:30:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从没用过代码
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.92,0:30:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这既不是某种模式 也不是某种等式
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.62,0:30:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数学上说  几乎毫无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.92,0:30:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧  但我以前见过
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.02,0:30:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet说他喜欢在受害者车里下手
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.22,0:30:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚他却选择了公车
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.52,0:30:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以Foyet只坐公车
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.22,0:30:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是7号 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.82,0:30:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就停在Foyet家门口
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.92,0:31:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道Foyet的住址
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.92,0:31:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也想让我们知道这点
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.42,0:31:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1439  今天你们找他问话的公寓
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.42,0:31:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Yarbrough街1439号
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.32,0:31:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他给我们的其他地址
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.12,0:31:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brookline区201号
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.42,0:31:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Edenhurst1488号
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.72,0:31:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车上的数字是Foyet的地址
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.32,0:31:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分头行动 去每个地址
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.62,0:32:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去后面
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.62,0:32:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.02,0:32:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有发现
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.92,0:32:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿也是  Morgan呢
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.92,0:33:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒  Derek  见上帝去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.52,0:33:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他不知道是什么袭击了他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.32,0:33:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这也算安慰的话
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.92,0:33:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打给JJ
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.12,0:33:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,局里要发表声明
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.02,0:33:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.72,0:33:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拿走了我的证件
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.12,0:33:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是你没事
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.92,0:34:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他留下了这个
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.92,0:34:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力量和控制
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.92,0:34:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让他影响你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.72,0:34:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.42,0:34:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  轻点  伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.52,0:34:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Prentiss  他是告诉我"你被我击败了"
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.52,0:34:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan   你还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.02,0:34:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道为什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.02,0:34:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.42,0:34:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在还能坐在这儿 因为我被打昏了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.72,0:34:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他无法折磨我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.42,0:34:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他喜欢看着受害者惊慌失措
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.82,0:34:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在动手前先告诉他们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.62,0:34:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者让他们知道  他原本可以杀了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.02,0:34:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.12,0:34:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是想影响你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.52,0:34:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何  他击败了我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.32,0:34:47.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然O'Mara是在外面被杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.02,0:34:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿另有其人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.02,0:34:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有挣扎的痕迹  大量血迹
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.72,0:34:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是没有尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.82,0:34:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是拖拉的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.92,0:34:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人体内的血液是5夸脱
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.02,0:34:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢说这儿不止一半
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.32,0:35:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管流血的人是谁 他们都失血过多  无法存活
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.12,0:35:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet?  那是他最大的心病
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.82,0:35:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死神可能回来  完成杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.62,0:35:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们原想保护他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.22,0:35:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拒绝了 这是他自己的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.92,0:35:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他特别关注Foyet 他身上有什么特别之处
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.82,0:35:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是唯一幸存的受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.12,0:35:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一一个他无法打败的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.42,0:35:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他不存在威胁  打败他也不会带来成就感
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.12,0:35:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们漏掉了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.22,0:35:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的女朋友呢  Amanda Bertrand?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.42,0:35:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.62,0:35:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,19岁  大一新生  从密歇根来这儿上学
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.92,0:35:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet是Amanda修的一门课程的助教
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.22,0:35:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密歇根  正是死神让Shaunessy 刊登私人广告的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.72,0:35:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能这么巧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.72,0:35:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说她是他的最爱  他原打算向她求婚
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.52,0:35:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是她刚刚来此 
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.92,0:35:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是在课上认识的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.12,0:35:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她上了多久的课
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.52,0:35:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4周
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.72,0:35:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一见钟情吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.12,0:35:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道Foyet在撒谎?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.32,0:35:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个28岁的助教  负责大一新生的课程
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.12,0:35:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份工作能让他接触到很多年轻女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.92,0:35:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Garcia -在
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.22,0:36:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet的化名是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.92,0:36:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查找波士顿的人口记录
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.82,0:36:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kevin Baskin Miles Holden William Parker
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.62,0:36:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在教育部门查查
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.62,0:36:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮   长官 他们全都在教育部门工作
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.12,0:36:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是代课教师
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.22,0:36:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都教计算机
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.12,0:36:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.02,0:36:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.72,0:36:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.42,0:36:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们现在已经没在教育部门工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.72,0:36:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.72,0:36:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,William Parker因为对女学生行为不当被开除
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.92,0:36:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道刺67刀需要多久吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.92,0:36:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.72,0:36:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你们抓不到他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.42,0:36:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Coslon去见Foyet了 Garcia  定位Roy Colson的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.32,0:36:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,George Foyet就是死神
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.92,0:36:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.42,0:36:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  现在三角定位
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.22,0:36:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了  Budlong街2633号
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.12,0:36:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个地址Foyet对我们隐瞒了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.52,0:37:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  George
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.12,0:37:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.42,0:37:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有阵子没见了 -进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.72,0:37:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把笔记本带来了  很好 -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.62,0:37:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放在桌上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.02,0:37:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.92,0:37:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他将Amanda Bertrand刺死
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.62,0:37:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开出一英里之外  拨打911
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.12,0:37:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再回来  在身上自己制造伤口
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.32,0:37:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道急救人员能及时挽救他
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.12,0:37:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那通电话  以及他的严重伤势
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.02,0:37:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从未怀疑他
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.72,0:37:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.02,0:37:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让他能够了解调查进度
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.92,0:37:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道的一切他都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.72,0:37:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把自己的眼镜留在案发现场
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.62,0:37:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们把调查方向转到他自己身上
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.12,0:37:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们却还是没发觉
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.52,0:37:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.52,0:37:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实…
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.62,0:37:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点生你的气
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.32,0:37:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  因为我把你的名字告诉了FBI?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.62,0:37:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个原因吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.12,0:37:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是因为你告诉了他们什么
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.52,0:37:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是因为我告诉你了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.42,0:38:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我告诉了你 我和Shaunessy的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.02,0:38:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却没写进去?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.92,0:38:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.22,0:38:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是份礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.62,0:38:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.12,0:38:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.52,0:38:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只需要写下来  然后出版
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.42,0:38:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不可能…
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.62,0:38:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本我可以就这样再次消失
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.92,0:38:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是你  George
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.12,0:38:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  别  George
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.52,0:38:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,George  求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.52,0:38:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能是你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.92,0:38:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能是你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.22,0:38:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.12,0:38:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你坐下  好好写故事
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.12,0:38:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.22,0:38:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你写我不是被捕  就是死了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.22,0:38:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你知道结局并非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.02,0:38:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.52,0:38:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打败了他们
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.62,0:39:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要所有人都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.82,0:39:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.42,0:39:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.62,0:39:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.32,0:39:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要他为你写故事
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.42,0:39:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带他一起走
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.82,0:39:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要保证我安全  我就放了他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.52,0:39:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你走不了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.92,0:39:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.12,0:39:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了他  我杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.72,0:39:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我会怕死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.92,0:39:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.82,0:39:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你贪心又自恋
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.62,0:39:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想获得他的书出版后带给你的认可
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.42,0:39:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想得到媒体给你的名声
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.12,0:39:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像Bundy (著名连环杀手)
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.72,0:39:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会比Bundy更有名
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.42,0:39:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你死了  可就享受不到了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.52,0:39:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你这么了解我  为什么等到命案发生后  你才来这儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.52,0:39:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的选择  不是我的 你才是连环杀手
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.52,0:39:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.22,0:39:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  Derek
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.92,0:40:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的警徽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.02,0:40:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪儿  你个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.82,0:40:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会比你们想的更有名
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.42,0:40:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做梦吧你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.22,0:40:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 Roy
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.42,0:40:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.42,0:40:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.12,0:40:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.52,0:40:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们将生命中的错误聚到一起
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.02,0:40:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,创造出一个恶魔  叫命运
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.02,0:40:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,John Hobbes  (著名作家)
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.92,0:40:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几处住所里都找不到你的证件
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.22,0:40:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet屋里的血
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.32,0:40:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid估计少了  验尸官说是4夸脱
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.82,0:41:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  那怎么可能  他会没命的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.02,0:41:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很久之前就开始计划自己的死
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.62,0:41:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他一次流一点血  采集足够血液
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.32,0:41:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让我们相信他死了  只是没找到尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.42,0:41:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan  你必须设法忘记这事
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.32,0:41:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.42,0:41:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.92,0:42:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Foyet越狱了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.52,0:42:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警卫发现他在牢房里吐血  抽搐
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.92,0:42:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们赶快送他去监狱医院
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.42,0:42:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知联邦执法官办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.62,0:42:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经联系了Don Reilly 说我们愿意协助
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.32,0:42:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说需要的话  会通知我们
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.92,0:42:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波士顿警局辨认出了Foyet房里的文件
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.12,0:42:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是西Woburn教养院 电力  热力和水力管道的图表
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.12,0:42:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有这些图表
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.02,0:42:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是Woburn的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.82,0:42:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Massachusetts州所有监狱   拘留所  法庭的都有
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.32,0:42:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十年的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.42,0:42:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会抓住他的 对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.32,0:42:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.92,0:43:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说过会比我们知道的更有名
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.22,0:43:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说的对
