[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.15,0:00:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪心理  前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.05,0:00:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我碰上了个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.95,0:00:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.34,0:00:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡屋 我帮他修电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.25,0:00:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我们可以一起吃顿饭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.15,0:00:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信吗  一个陌生人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.05,0:00:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事时有发生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.05,0:00:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会是我  不会是这样的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.65,0:00:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该相信自已的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.85,0:00:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许尝试着从另一个角度去想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.95,0:00:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想能否 把午餐改为晚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.85,0:00:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我约你出去 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.35,0:00:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整晚我都想着这事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.45,0:00:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在屋里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.35,0:00:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到枪声 但什么也没看见
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.05,0:00:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪伤 子弹由胸腔穿过腹部
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.35,0:00:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳90/50  持续减弱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.65,0:00:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好担架  以及护颈圈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.05,0:00:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她能活下来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.75,0:00:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.05,0:00:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到我说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.85,0:00:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.35,0:00:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 你叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.25,0:00:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血压
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.25,0:00:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,60  持续降低
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.45,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫Penelope
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.35,0:00:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 请离开
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.95,0:00:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切会好起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.35,0:00:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 你听到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.95,0:01:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来像扫帚柄断成两半的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.85,0:01:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起初我还没意识到这是枪声
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.95,0:01:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住 坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.35,0:01:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听到我吗 能听到我的声音吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.65,0:01:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.15,0:01:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.45,0:01:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 一切会好起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.45,0:01:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我你的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.75,0:01:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.95,0:01:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快送她进去 快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.85,0:01:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好像在FBI工作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.35,0:01:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope 你会没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.95,0:01:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做得很好 坚持
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.65,0:01:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心台阶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.55,0:01:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.05,0:01:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住 Penelope
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.05,0:01:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就这样 Penelope 做的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.75,0:01:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.15,0:01:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这待得这么晚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.55,0:01:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是想让我难堪吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.45,0:01:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.35,0:01:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短效甲状腺激素降到82
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.75,0:01:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.35,0:01:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肺换气不足 给我氧气包
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.85,0:01:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.15,0:01:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.65,0:02:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年龄30 一处枪伤  子弹由胸腔至腹腔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.25,0:02:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脉搏?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.55,0:02:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超过每分140
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.85,0:02:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心脏收缩压降至78
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.25,0:02:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插管 送到手术室 立刻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.65,0:02:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope  坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.35,0:02:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.95,0:02:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.55,0:02:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在手术室
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.05,0:02:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有消息
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.05,0:02:28.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.45,0:02:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看看I-PACK -好的 医生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.95,0:02:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-夹钳 -大出血
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.95,0:02:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我气道吸引机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.55,0:02:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找不到出血点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.85,0:02:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开气道吸引机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.85,0:02:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么信息
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.65,0:02:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方认为是一起持械抢劫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.55,0:02:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.35,0:02:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.75,0:02:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再打给他
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.75,0:02:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.85,0:02:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和一名送她进来的急救医生谈了谈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.05,0:02:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况不乐观
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.15,0:02:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心律不稳
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.25,0:03:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充电压到360
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.25,0:03:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 我们等找到出血点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.55,0:03:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-心室颤动 -必须找到出血点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.25,0:03:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂时没有消息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.65,0:03:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan手机一直转到语音邮箱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.15,0:03:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他到底在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.05,0:03:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸腔管再次出现750
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.05,0:03:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此严重失血  怎么数字还会这么高
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.15,0:03:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血压下降 67/42
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.55,0:03:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子弹肯定穿过了横隔膜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.15,0:03:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致脾脏动脉扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.65,0:03:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对此加压  就这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.15,0:03:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她失血太快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.25,0:04:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输血
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.25,0:04:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-赶不上 -加压
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.95,0:04:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缝合时持续给动脉加压
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.55,0:04:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.95,0:04:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心跳下降
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.65,0:04:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心室颤动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.75,0:04:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.35,0:04:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.85,0:04:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对骨头注射100单位的利多卡因 (一种局部麻醉剂)
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.75,0:04:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有起色
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.15,0:04:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充电
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.05,0:04:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,300
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.95,0:04:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.45,0:04:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没变化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.05,0:04:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-充电 -360
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.55,0:04:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.25,0:04:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充电
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.25,0:04:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.75,0:04:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.36,0:05:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎士比亚曾写道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.26,0:05:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱众人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.36,0:05:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信少数人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.56,0:05:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不害任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.86,0:05:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.16,0:05:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仍没有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.66,0:05:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.56,0:05:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有心跳了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.26,0:05:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  伙计们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.46,0:06:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.26,0:06:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸引机
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.16,0:06:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缝合线
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.56,0:06:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在手术室已有好几个小时 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.76,0:06:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在教堂 手机关机了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.76,0:06:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了也帮不上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.26,0:06:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方有什么线索吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.26,0:06:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与探长谈过
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.06,0:06:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说现场找不出什么线索
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.56,0:06:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.66,0:06:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的 -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.36,0:06:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子弹进入她的胸腔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.86,0:06:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反弹到腹腔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.66,0:06:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失血过多
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.16,0:06:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况非常危险
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.46,0:06:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们已把她救回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.06,0:06:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.16,0:06:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再往上一厘米
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.26,0:06:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就正中她的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.96,0:06:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是几天后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.96,0:06:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她便能出院了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.46,0:06:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得说  这真是个小小的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.46,0:06:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她需要休息
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.26,0:06:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天早上再来看她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.66,0:06:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.06,0:06:51.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和David去现场查看
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.56,0:06:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们留下来陪她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.76,0:06:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管规程
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.36,0:06:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不管我们是否正式调查此案
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.86,0:07:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没抓到凶手之前  我们不接任何新案子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.66,0:07:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.16,0:07:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们猜测他看到她进房
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.46,0:07:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾随其后 踹开门
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.56,0:07:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抢劫了她 于是她试着抓她
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.06,0:07:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他边跑边转过身开了枪 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.06,0:07:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预测枪击有多远
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.96,0:07:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约15英尺
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了门的因素外
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.66,0:07:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么让你认为这是一起抢劫
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.06,0:07:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抢了她的手袋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.66,0:07:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潜逃之前扔了其中一些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.16,0:07:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有找到弹壳吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.16,0:07:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说他从这开枪?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.86,0:07:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奔走时也能射这么准
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.76,0:07:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他要冒险进到这个封闭的院子里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.36,0:07:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就为了偷手袋?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.56,0:07:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史上最强悍的手袋抢劫犯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.86,0:07:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不合情理
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.36,0:07:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.46,0:07:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.76,0:07:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们马上过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.76,0:07:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.26,0:08:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.86,0:08:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准哭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.66,0:08:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心我一哭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.16,0:08:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又得进手术台了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.36,0:08:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.76,0:08:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又蠢...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.96,0:08:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又傻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.56,0:08:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又痛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.06,0:08:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能回答我们的问题了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.06,0:08:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本没想过会发生这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.56,0:08:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看来...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.86,0:08:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常正常
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.16,0:08:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.06,0:08:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.06,0:08:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该相信你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.66,0:08:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.06,0:08:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我和你提起过的那人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.86,0:08:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在咖啡屋碰上的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.86,0:08:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望相信他对我有兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.56,0:08:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.66,0:08:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放松了警惕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.06,0:08:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道他为什么要这么干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.16,0:08:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他危胁你? 他想要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.66,0:09:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是认为他喜欢我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.36,0:09:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.06,0:09:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们过会再来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.66,0:09:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.96,0:09:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,James Colby Baylor
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.06,0:09:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.86,0:09:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能待一会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.06,0:09:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.06,0:09:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉我该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.36,0:09:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得她怎么谈论他的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.06,0:09:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.96,0:09:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚和Hotch谈过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.06,0:09:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们认为他用的是左轮手枪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.66,0:09:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会用这种手枪?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.26,0:09:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想留下弹壳作为证据的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.16,0:09:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.36,0:09:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.16,0:09:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且他把现场设计成一场抢劫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.06,0:09:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明他足够聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.06,0:09:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道如何反利用物证
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.26,0:09:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极有可能这名字也是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.26,0:09:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.96,0:09:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她让我答应
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.26,0:09:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把她当作受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.96,0:10:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被害者研究 为什么是Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.56,0:10:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.06,0:10:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的意思是?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.76,0:10:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是一起意外
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.36,0:10:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她富有个性  彷佛附身盾牌一般
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.26,0:10:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导致有人对她充满敌意?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.86,0:10:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她引人注目  单身女性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.76,0:10:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能那人已经监视她一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.56,0:10:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个虐待狂首先骗取她的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.86,0:10:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后找机会杀她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.96,0:10:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很常见 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.26,0:10:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kemper  Bundy  Rober Anderson就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.76,0:10:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么困扰着你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.36,0:10:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个虐待狂只是 凑巧选择一名FBI的分析员?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.26,0:10:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我约她出去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.56,0:10:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她对我很生气
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.96,0:10:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.46,0:10:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你跑去教堂?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.06,0:10:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.36,0:11:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.76,0:11:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她与我出去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.96,0:11:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就不会受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.46,0:11:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.06,0:11:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我20年来第一次祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.46,0:11:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就出事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.36,0:11:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机率又有多大?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.46,0:11:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想见你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.86,0:11:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.46,0:11:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.56,0:11:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好消息也是坏消息
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.96,0:11:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吗啡的药效快退了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.56,0:11:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我躺在救护车上时
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.56,0:11:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脑海里能听到"英雄"这歌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.96,0:11:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时昏时醒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都很明亮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.66,0:11:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得当时在想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.86,0:11:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.66,0:12:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,David Bowie真的是上帝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.06,0:12:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一位...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.06,0:12:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一位素描专家来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.36,0:12:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是感觉有点模糊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.66,0:12:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.56,0:12:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的任何事都能帮助我们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.06,0:12:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.66,0:12:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他是做什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.16,0:12:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他是律师
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.86,0:12:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去的地方还有人认识他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.16,0:12:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他想让我看个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.46,0:12:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有半小时的路程
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.46,0:12:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们一起开车去?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.56,0:12:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.56,0:12:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.16,0:12:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.16,0:12:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四门轿车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.06,0:12:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国货
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.16,0:12:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闻起来像新的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.76,0:12:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是租来的?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.36,0:12:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.26,0:12:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.96,0:12:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看事情不像你们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.96,0:12:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看不到危险
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.96,0:13:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 放松点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.96,0:13:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还能记起什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.36,0:13:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他身上的味道很好闻
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.86,0:13:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.66,0:13:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.06,0:13:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他紧张吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.56,0:13:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为他只是害怕吻我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.56,0:13:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.96,0:13:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定你准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.06,0:13:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.56,0:13:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.06,0:13:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整晚我都想着这事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.96,0:13:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听到他的脚步声
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.46,0:13:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他靠向我 我屏住呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.56,0:13:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他以为我死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.66,0:13:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪击
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.16,0:13:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太恐怖了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.86,0:13:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在加护病房
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.46,0:13:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.46,0:14:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道她怎么活过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医学上的奇迹 对吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.06,0:14:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.06,0:14:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们抓到他了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.06,0:14:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何线索?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是瘾君子干的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.56,0:14:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.16,0:14:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方也不能保证你的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.06,0:14:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太疯狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.82,0:14:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看来很糟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.32,0:14:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4天了没有任何线索 自已感觉都很糟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.82,0:14:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医院有什么消息
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.22,0:14:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她搬出了加护病房
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.32,0:14:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说过几天就能出院
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.42,0:14:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid和Morgan与她重温案件
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.72,0:14:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时通知我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.42,0:14:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟这画像相似的人 我们能找出3百万来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.72,0:14:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方打来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把画像带到咖啡屋 饭店
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.02,0:14:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么结果
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.62,0:14:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至查了数据库
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.62,0:15:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一无所获
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.52,0:15:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汽车租借公司也没有消息
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.12,0:15:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现场没有指纹 没有弹壳
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.12,0:15:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给Garcia打电话的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.52,0:15:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是一次性的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.82,0:15:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是个谜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.12,0:15:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高度警惕 对吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.52,0:15:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.12,0:15:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今很多人都买半自动的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.32,0:15:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.12,0:15:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 子弹更多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.02,0:15:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果枪法准  子弹多了也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.72,0:15:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope 我了解重温现场很痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.22,0:15:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不知道要记起什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.12,0:15:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从他的行为开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.02,0:15:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实…其实侧写就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.32,0:15:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意他的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.22,0:15:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜心  任何细节
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.92,0:15:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都对我们有所帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.22,0:15:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.32,0:15:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.82,0:15:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 从你们刚到饭店开始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.72,0:15:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他紧张吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.82,0:15:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.12,0:15:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恰恰相反
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.12,0:16:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要先喝点什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.72,0:16:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一瓶桑塞尔白葡萄酒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.82,0:16:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我喝红酒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.32,0:16:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.32,0:16:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会爱上它的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.92,0:16:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他掌握主动权
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.22,0:16:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以令你印象深刻?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.22,0:16:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.82,0:16:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说他的表
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.52,0:16:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假的劳力士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.42,0:16:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.02,0:16:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道什么是假货
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.22,0:16:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显他在玩弄它
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.72,0:16:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他想让你注意
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.72,0:16:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想让你认为这是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.82,0:16:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.52,0:16:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉我真的很容易被攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.82,0:16:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.32,0:16:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.02,0:16:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为FBI工作
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.52,0:16:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.12,0:16:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.02,0:16:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.52,0:16:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你觉得一天工作14小时
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.52,0:16:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隐藏在一间狭小又昏暗的里
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.72,0:16:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周围充斥着暴力的图片很有趣   那么的确如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.02,0:16:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  就像20世纪的巴黎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.82,0:16:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也调查谋杀?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.82,0:16:56.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  全天候的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.12,0:16:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.42,0:16:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.52,0:17:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就像警察和老大的综合体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.92,0:17:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更喜欢把自已想成
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.02,0:17:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不依不挠的圣战士  为了世界命运而战
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.42,0:17:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.82,0:17:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.82,0:17:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.52,0:17:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在New Haven读书
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.12,0:17:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波士顿读法律
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.12,0:17:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是在剑桥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.92,0:17:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都在同一大学城
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.32,0:17:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你主攻什么法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个市律师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.42,0:17:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦你有件谋杀案  因司法渎职
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.52,0:17:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或间接再诉禁  而被驳回
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.02,0:17:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时私人律师就显得非常重要了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.62,0:17:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人会由于别人的失职
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.42,0:17:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃脱法律的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.32,0:17:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么和你讲这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.82,0:17:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定看过很多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.42,0:17:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为命运干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.22,0:17:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市律师不接手谋杀案
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.32,0:17:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.02,0:17:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很精通法律术语
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.32,0:17:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他可能不是律师
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.62,0:17:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们要找的是名法学院缀学
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.92,0:17:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者没有通过律师考试的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.92,0:18:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia有没有说他提到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.32,0:18:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他审问这些案件的细节
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.22,0:18:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.32,0:18:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他没过律师考试
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.52,0:18:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能解释为何他只知道这些术语
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.62,0:18:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时也能解释他的愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.22,0:18:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至在他编造的谎言中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.32,0:18:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他仍抱怨别人的失职
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.82,0:18:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显他是自恋狂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.32,0:18:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服 手表 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.32,0:18:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对就读学校的微妙的暗示
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.62,0:18:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他提到New Haven与剑桥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.82,0:18:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不说哈福与耶鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.32,0:18:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在假装谦虚
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.52,0:18:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J. 联系一名能够将我们的信息
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.12,0:18:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在法律数据库查到的分析员
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.52,0:18:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.32,0:18:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定她不介意我用她的系统
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.72,0:18:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们对此很在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.92,0:18:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只要你查一些法律协会的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.42,0:18:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么不做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.32,0:18:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还在医院
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.02,0:18:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说中枪的那名分析员
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.12,0:18:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.02,0:18:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道是谁干的?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.32,0:18:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能找到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.52,0:18:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.32,0:18:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是所有数据的守护人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.52,0:18:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些足以让我们疯狂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.32,0:18:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用自已的电脑就能办到
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.62,0:18:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先查这个名字James Colby Baylor
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.22,0:18:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看系统里是否有这人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.82,0:19:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.02,0:19:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.72,0:19:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这系统太疯狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.02,0:19:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全Linux系统
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.52,0:19:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开放源程序
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.02,0:19:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府系统可见不到这个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.02,0:19:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说瑞士以外的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.42,0:19:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,James Colby Baylor
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.32,0:19:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.12,0:19:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.92,0:19:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 再看看近五年来这一区
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.92,0:19:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有谁司法考试没过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.12,0:19:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者被法律公司给炒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.82,0:19:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没开玩笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.72,0:19:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定有上千人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.22,0:19:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再以名字大写字母J.C.B.缩小范围
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.22,0:19:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他穿印花衬衫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.72,0:19:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是廉价货
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.12,0:19:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.12,0:19:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我见过最酷的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.22,0:19:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从没看过她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.72,0:19:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的聊天软件太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.02,0:19:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名单
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.82,0:20:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.12,0:20:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.62,0:20:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch在干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.21,0:20:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.77,0:20:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.05,0:20:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有更好的约会
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.92,0:20:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.16,0:20:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在你电脑里发现一份加密文件
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.69,0:20:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么没有告诉我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.18,0:20:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.14,0:20:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.19,0:20:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这与枪击事件有关吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.12,0:20:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.49,0:20:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密码
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.07,0:20:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有必要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.65,0:20:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.99,0:21:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密码
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.67,0:21:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-GILMAN STREET -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.00,0:21:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会真把Garcia看成安全隐患吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.69,0:21:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.47,0:21:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内务部命令我们停止调查此案
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.58,0:21:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.12,0:21:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事水落石出之前...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.36,0:21:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你停职了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.95,0:21:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.53,0:21:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.35,0:21:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你干吗  -我得离开这
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.92,0:21:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.63,0:21:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会继续调查
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.21,0:21:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到揪出是谁干的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.32,0:21:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管内务部说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.27,0:21:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在你需要休息
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.89,0:21:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他枪击我之前  
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.47,0:21:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对他说的最后一句话是 事出皆有因
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.16,0:21:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Derek 如果对此话失去信心  那我的生活也就毫无意义了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.45,0:21:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道了  -不 你不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.94,0:21:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有必要?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.79,0:21:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是规程
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.98,0:21:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 有必要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.59,0:22:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lynch先生负责检查她的电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.02,0:22:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我则监督此案的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.75,0:22:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联邦调查员中枪受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.48,0:22:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却认为调查她比找出凶手更重要?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.45,0:22:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.43,0:22:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警方有此权调查此案
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且我会给他们提供FBI的全力支持
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.19,0:22:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言 长官 行为分析组也属于这一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.27,0:22:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我也知道这很难接受
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.10,0:22:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是? -但是你们先做受害者分析
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.12,0:22:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.43,0:22:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,局里想知道她参与了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.54,0:22:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底跟她中枪有何关联
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.72,0:22:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她什么也没参与
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.11,0:22:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你确定  -绝对
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.29,0:22:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她是如何被FBI雇用的?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.55,0:22:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母死后 我有点叛逆
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.75,0:22:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从CAL工学院缀学 深居简出
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.68,0:22:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直自学编程
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.61,0:23:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这件事让我能够坚持下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.33,0:23:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,局里追踪电脑黑客
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.81,0:23:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的技术或者极度有用 或者有潜在的危胁
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Garcia在这份监督名单上? -不 监督名单很长
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.52,0:23:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的是在这星球上只有一小部分人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.83,0:23:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.95,0:23:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无权透露
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.50,0:23:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以他们雇用了你  -嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.28,0:23:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像Frank Abagnale
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.07,0:23:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-局里认为与其为敌 不如纳入麾下? -差不多是这样...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.86,0:23:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 那份加密文件是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.71,0:23:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面要我对小组做的任何事保留一份记录
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.84,0:23:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从我的系统被人黑了 Elle中枪后
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.70,0:23:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让其他人再盯上你们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.56,0:23:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找医生问问你能不能出院了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.23,0:24:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 我是Mike Fleming
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.47,0:24:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我值班到12点 之后由Cranbeck负责
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.55,0:24:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢 -不客气
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.55,0:24:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我送你进去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.56,0:24:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.96,0:24:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会洗掉的 我答应你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.27,0:24:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.76,0:24:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与我想像中一样
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.26,0:24:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该感到荣幸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.80,0:24:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很多人进过我的闺房
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.64,0:25:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-SUPER-8?  -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.11,0:25:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总想像自已与罪恶作战
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.46,0:25:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的父母是嬉皮士
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.00,0:25:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这可能吓到他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.12,0:25:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你失去父母时多大?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.01,0:25:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,18岁 酒后驾驶
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.47,0:25:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个星期我都做志愿者 安慰被害者的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.11,0:25:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝 上班时这些东西还没看够吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.13,0:25:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天都看这些犯罪现场照片
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.80,0:25:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道这些家庭每天得经历些什么 我不能坐视不管
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.52,0:25:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道给文件加密是很蠢的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.17,0:25:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.96,0:25:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老习惯了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.25,0:26:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-去休息会  -对
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.82,0:26:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.34,0:26:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的爱人 你自由了 -我哪也不去
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.17,0:26:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事 外面还有警察守着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.18,0:26:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管有没有警察
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.71,0:26:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到找到那人为止 那边的沙发注定成为我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.81,0:26:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管那么多了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.85,0:26:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.63,0:26:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果你认为你可以占我便宜
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.40,0:26:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我先给医生打个电话  以免我两腿蹬跷了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.22,0:26:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.32,0:26:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你 你知道的 对吧? 
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.41,0:26:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.85,0:26:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上床吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.92,0:27:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.66,0:27:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.63,0:27:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.90,0:27:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.85,0:27:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待在那
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.16,0:27:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.40,0:27:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.61,0:27:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲到角落里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.35,0:27:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.49,0:27:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着这把枪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.65,0:27:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信枪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.96,0:27:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 是真的 拿着它
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.02,0:27:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 手别碰扳机
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.07,0:27:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人进来 你就扣动扳机
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.78,0:27:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开枪 听到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.76,0:27:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Morgan  -待在那
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.37,0:28:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Leavenworth107号 一名警员受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.47,0:28:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复 一名警员受伤 叫辆救护车
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.19,0:28:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是总部 收到
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.41,0:28:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-啊...  -Garcia 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.60,0:28:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开枪 是我 Morgan
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.67,0:29:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会发生在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.52,0:29:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.01,0:29:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-发生了什么事 -我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.81,0:29:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙越来越大胆了  我保证事情还没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.98,0:29:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你还好吧  -我不知道他想要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.95,0:29:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许你知道他什么 -我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.81,0:29:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你有他想要的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.70,0:29:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.43,0:29:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我很怕 -我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.69,0:29:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的长官通知我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.11,0:29:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说这案子由我们负责
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.55,0:30:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不希望你们插手此案
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.23,0:30:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是来安慰一位朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.54,0:30:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得告诉一位好友的妻子 他丈夫死了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.73,0:30:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管你们长官怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.76,0:30:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-希望你们能提供任何线索 -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.73,0:30:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌让这家伙先行一步
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.70,0:30:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得想法结束一切
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.29,0:30:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你看到他吗 -没有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.44,0:30:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Garcia 我们得把你送到医院  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.64,0:30:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该在那 她得待在安全的地方 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.42,0:30:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你们在一起我很安全
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.36,0:30:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以带你去BAU
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.51,0:30:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.62,0:30:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.60,0:30:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躲在角落
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.85,0:30:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起吃饭时  服务生本打算让我们靠窗坐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.48,0:30:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他坚持坐最差的一张桌子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.77,0:31:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的背就是靠着角落坐
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.03,0:31:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探长 能不能清理一下现场?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.29,0:31:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面还有名已死的警察
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.42,0:31:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这也是犯罪现场的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.01,0:31:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 只要几分钟就好
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.43,0:31:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-请便 -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.62,0:31:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说说汽车 -为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.68,0:31:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照他说的做
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.01,0:31:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是白色 4门 美国产 还有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.78,0:31:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这些 就是一辆车
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.98,0:31:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力想想
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.19,0:31:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全带扣在他的后面
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.14,0:31:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.45,0:31:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是租的车
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.94,0:31:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是用来监视的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.55,0:31:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探员不系安全带
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.82,0:31:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们需要快速行动
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.39,0:31:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 废话少说
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.95,0:31:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得有所隐瞒 现在
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.78,0:32:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我 不是他们
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.93,0:32:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没隐瞒什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.23,0:32:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你中枪了 很多人中枪都是有理由的 
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.97,0:32:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看着这 -放松点 Rossi
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.61,0:32:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有一整屋的FBI在这
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.07,0:32:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都愿意相信是一名特员想开枪杀你
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.90,0:32:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们你在上班时间干了些什么  而我们却不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.37,0:32:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -快点
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.65,0:32:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是坏事 快说
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.10,0:32:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安慰受害者家人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.52,0:32:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们知道我在哪工作
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.75,0:32:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候他们要求我帮他们调查案子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.64,0:32:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这代表什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.81,0:32:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说这些我标记的悬案
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.80,0:32:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是谁在调查 
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.87,0:32:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些人都知道FBI对此优先考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.21,0:32:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没权这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.47,0:32:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我只是想帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.43,0:32:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但调查这些案子的人 认为你在监督他们
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.20,0:32:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想给他们施压  这样他们才不会分心
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.90,0:32:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有多少案子 -我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.26,0:32:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7  8件 我得看看我的系统
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.50,0:32:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能 你被调职了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.15,0:32:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.41,0:32:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾说过这人曾向你 打听过你是否在调查谋杀案
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.50,0:32:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 我们得看文件
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.91,0:33:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了我讨厌这家伙老是先我们一步
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.78,0:33:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Dave说的对
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.89,0:33:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回到BAU
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.45,0:33:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan Reid Prentiss 你们待在那 确保没人忘记退出系统
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.25,0:33:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia不能进入
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.14,0:33:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.43,0:33:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.85,0:33:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.80,0:34:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没时间和你玩
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.19,0:34:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.17,0:34:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嗯 -还有...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.68,0:34:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想玩?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.66,0:34:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在里面干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.46,0:34:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想知道?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.20,0:34:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.57,0:34:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是真想砍我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.84,0:34:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.07,0:34:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小菜一碟
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.30,0:34:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 追我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.56,0:34:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你技艺不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.96,0:34:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.45,0:34:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虫洞大逃亡 玩得开心
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.18,0:34:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是我标识了的案子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.58,0:34:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 每个人拿一份
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.15,0:35:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得找出是否 有探员参与了所有案件的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.90,0:35:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.47,0:35:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想找什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.37,0:35:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有探员接这些案子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.71,0:35:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但同一名副治安官在3起案件中 都是第一个到达现场的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.43,0:35:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-叫什么 -Jason Clark Battle
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.82,0:35:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是些什么案
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.34,0:35:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是近距离驾车枪击  凶器都是左轮手枪
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.20,0:35:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是他吗  -是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.40,0:35:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被授予英雄奖章两次
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.80,0:35:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何他老做副手
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.53,0:35:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他上司也认为这人有点怪
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.09,0:35:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得通 光鲜的衣服  不动声色的吹嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.89,0:36:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是一名副治安官 却假扮自已为一名卓越的律师 
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.32,0:36:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在真实世界里未得赏识 又有自恋情结
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.08,0:36:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.66,0:36:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你碰到了死亡天使
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.64,0:36:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是专为人解除痛苦的护士吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.58,0:36:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 这只是其中一种
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.58,0:36:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一种是故意将人陷入险境  再去救人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.69,0:36:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他开枪杀人是为了救他们?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.55,0:36:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 但是无法挽救时  他就想法使其看来像随机谋杀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.52,0:36:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是为什么他第一到达现场
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.71,0:36:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这被称为英雄谋杀情结
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.57,0:36:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最常见的是消防员故意纵火  以充当救火英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.36,0:36:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 你标记这些案子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.15,0:36:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以为你知道他的所做所为
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.76,0:36:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.84,0:36:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是唯一能把这些事件联系起来的人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.00,0:36:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他的思想里他得解决你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.46,0:36:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请找Battle
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.93,0:36:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 他什么时候下班
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.40,0:36:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用留言 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.16,0:36:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没签外出记录 他的班到半夜才结束
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.62,0:36:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之前不要打草惊蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.90,0:36:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  侧写怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.27,0:37:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为掩盖罪犯越来越肆无忌惮
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.84,0:37:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没用 他就会开枪杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.04,0:37:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.85,0:37:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢通知我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.15,0:37:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想让你知道  我们非常重视 调查局干涉当地执法机构一事
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.11,0:37:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 深有同感
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.25,0:37:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Lynch先生 我想你来找些文件
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.21,0:37:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我有点忙
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.78,0:37:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来 只要一小会
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.52,0:37:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副治安官
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.16,0:37:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jason Battle
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.69,0:37:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,B-A-T-T-L-E
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.70,0:37:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.46,0:37:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你的分析员会去查我的谋杀案
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.55,0:37:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实话告诉你 我们谈到的这名女探员 现正处于调查中
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.47,0:38:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为她有没有牵涉到其中的谋杀案?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.48,0:38:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有结论
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.57,0:38:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我直接和她谈不会更容易吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.23,0:38:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在医院
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.61,0:38:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就是中枪的那人? -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.04,0:38:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在每名警察都在加班 但什么也没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.02,0:38:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许她有什么问题?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.70,0:38:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老话 还没有结论
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.85,0:38:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有结论之前
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.63,0:38:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否将我的案子从你们系统中移除?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.99,0:38:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然行 Lynch先生
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.86,0:38:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.81,0:38:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.33,0:38:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.35,0:38:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他登录了我的系统
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.69,0:38:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我屏幕上有个链接
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.62,0:38:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是个错误
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.95,0:38:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他很棒 不可能是错误
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.37,0:38:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他想向你展示什么
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.75,0:38:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他在给我下饵
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.44,0:38:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.67,0:38:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他在内务部
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.38,0:38:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我跟着他  不管是谁登陆  都会导致他被解雇
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.71,0:38:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的直觉怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.67,0:39:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是黑客 我们有代码
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.33,0:39:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-能信吗 -必须得信
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.50,0:39:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干吧 取得联系
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.04,0:39:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是BAU
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.66,0:39:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天噢 就是他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.65,0:39:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 我是Morgan 他在BAU
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.40,0:39:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副治安官 中间 刚过我的桌子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.44,0:39:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看到他了? -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.27,0:39:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打草惊蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.28,0:39:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是典型的自恋狂 且有着英雄谋杀情结 这症状不断加深
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.59,0:39:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让他知道了 他会开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.11,0:40:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要向自已证明  他比我们都聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.75,0:40:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里太挤了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.68,0:40:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开枪会伤及旁人
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.59,0:40:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得让人溜到他后面
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.26,0:40:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把摄像转到房间外吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.27,0:40:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.10,0:40:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 只是这不是我的系统
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.84,0:40:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花的时间长点
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.10,0:40:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 我的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.59,0:40:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点J.J. 接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.92,0:40:43.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.48,0:40:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J.我是Morgan 听我说 注意听
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.49,0:40:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.64,0:40:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定我的案件被清除了?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.51,0:41:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 长官
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.25,0:41:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 我会随时通知你我们的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.95,0:41:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道他们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.27,0:41:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太疯狂 我们得赶过去 我也一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.77,0:41:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能去 我得去
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.43,0:41:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没时间争了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.04,0:41:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是警察
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.98,0:41:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道事情会如何了结
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.49,0:41:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在身处FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.40,0:41:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我怕FBI?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.51,0:41:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道会如何了结 你也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.26,0:41:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是有功在身的警官
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.00,0:41:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.34,0:41:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想遗臭万年
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.37,0:41:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你占主导
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.48,0:41:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你来写结局
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.87,0:41:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌握在你手中
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.15,0:41:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI最聪明的人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.35,0:41:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都不能阻止我
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.05,0:42:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.02,0:42:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的结束了?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.54,0:42:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 真的结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.36,0:42:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在能否把你送到医院?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.09,0:42:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.55,0:42:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心你的复职文件
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.06,0:42:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的手一停止发抖就会签了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.08,0:42:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.15,0:42:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想让你这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.17,0:42:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我眼都没眨
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.49,0:42:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为家人的安全什么都会做
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.42,0:42:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:55.71,0:42:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.02,0:42:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢 你的信念呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.43,0:43:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日复一日地祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.87,0:43:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想有人看着你
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.01,0:43:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信事出皆有因吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.00,0:43:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是你 -是你
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.64,0:43:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你很棒 -你更棒
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.12,0:43:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Kevin Lynch -Penelope
