[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.94,0:00:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪心理  前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.10,0:00:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我碰上了个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.00,0:00:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我约你出去 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.20,0:00:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 Garcia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.20,0:00:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整晚我都想着这事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.30,0:00:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只要你查一些法律协会的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.90,0:00:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎么不做
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.90,0:00:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还在医院
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.00,0:00:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我见过最酷的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.40,0:00:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的聊天软件太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.40,0:00:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪也不去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.10,0:00:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的沙发注定成为我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.90,0:00:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到找到那人为止 别争了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.70,0:00:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.50,0:00:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kevin Lynch
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.70,0:00:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Penelope
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.20,0:00:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.80,0:00:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你更棒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.10,0:01:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人能懂黑夜...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.30,0:01:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不清黑暗中隐匿着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.30,0:01:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是他们看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.30,0:01:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是他们不去看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.10,0:01:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大自然的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.60,0:01:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直逼入他们思绪最深的角落
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.30,0:01:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们拒绝去探求源头...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.70,0:01:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些窥视他们 却无法触摸的东西...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.10,0:01:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒彻心底
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.00,0:01:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无人性
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.70,0:03:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2个星期内发现的第6及第7名受害者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.10,0:03:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶器全是刀片状?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.70,0:03:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.30,0:03:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻击越来越暴力
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.20,0:03:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前5名是单起案件
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.60,0:03:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凶手越来越嚣张
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.80,0:03:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且也越凶残
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.90,0:03:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知洛杉矶警方.我们9:30到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.10,0:04:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自已的门我还是能开的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.66,0:04:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我在就不行 闭嘴行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.06,0:04:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这TMD怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.06,0:04:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.66,0:04:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.66,0:04:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 一团糟吗 我来搞定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.06,0:04:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有部分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.96,0:04:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是那个逛你系统的那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.86,0:04:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kevin Lynch
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.86,0:04:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他搞得一团糟  别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.26,0:04:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这整个变了样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.96,0:04:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变了样? 你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.46,0:04:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他调整了...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.66,0:04:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 会...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.16,0:04:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走 你得去洛杉矶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.06,0:04:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我在这多呆会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.16,0:04:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你可能还需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.26,0:04:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆会?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.46,0:04:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.26,0:04:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个案子没有我 小组也能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.86,0:04:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.56,0:04:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的 我知道你爱我 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.96,0:04:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但一想到你像游魂似的转来转去 想要帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比中枪还恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.56,0:05:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia 你确定?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.36,0:05:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全康复了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.86,0:05:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 运动自如
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.26,0:05:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-停 停 -没痛 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.06,0:05:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别嗯嗯啊啊的  停
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.76,0:05:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.76,0:05:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事打电话找我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.86,0:05:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.66,0:05:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.46,0:05:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.26,0:05:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Kevin Lynch
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.46,0:05:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也许很可爱...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.16,0:05:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你要再敢乱动我的东西...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.36,0:05:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟 超人只是一种外星生物
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.96,0:06:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是个拥有人类外表的入侵者
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.56,0:06:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作家Clive Barker
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.36,0:06:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.66,0:06:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.26,0:06:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.06,0:06:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.06,0:06:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛挂掉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.86,0:06:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌这个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.16,0:06:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么大不了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.46,0:06:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想留下个蹩脚的语音信息 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.36,0:06:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要报出你的名字就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.66,0:06:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你的?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的有什么问题?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.16,0:06:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想来点有趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.86,0:06:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是作家 你答应过帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.76,0:06:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.16,0:06:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为何不说 "你不能接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.56,0:06:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你现在外面享受生活"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.06,0:06:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.96,0:06:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.46,0:06:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Vickie 现在不方便接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.06,0:06:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我正在外面享受生活
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.46,0:06:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到哔之后留言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.46,0:06:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.06,0:06:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公平交易?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.06,0:06:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱死你说拉丁语了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还会法语呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.16,0:06:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在 Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.26,0:07:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 Johnny 开门
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.36,0:07:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.16,0:07:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几个月没看你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.46,0:07:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,颓废成这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.76,0:07:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.56,0:07:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.96,0:07:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时后有个新书签名会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.36,0:07:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不去什么签名会
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.76,0:07:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.26,0:07:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你的经纪人 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.76,0:07:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发行商已预付了一大笔钱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.46,0:07:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退回去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.16,0:07:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.46,0:07:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是你的粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.06,0:07:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们晚上还在美术馆扎营
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.56,0:07:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一整晚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.96,0:07:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你注意了没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.46,0:07:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面下雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.26,0:07:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很大的雨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.86,0:07:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将与杀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.26,0:07:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.16,0:07:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车里给你准备了咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.66,0:07:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.36,0:08:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近在画的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.46,0:08:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.16,0:08:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这句话还要我解释?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.86,0:08:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那Blue 6怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.56,0:08:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在创作新的作品
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.86,0:08:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Blue还有2个星期截稿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.96,0:08:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.66,0:08:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.36,0:08:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没灵感了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没灵感了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.96,0:08:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要学舌了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.86,0:08:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny  停
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.86,0:08:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是签了合同的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.66,0:08:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是个职业画家
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.76,0:08:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.06,0:08:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血腥 砍头
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.66,0:08:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的画什么时候变得这么血腥了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.06,0:08:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在创作新的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.36,0:08:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得给发行商打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.86,0:08:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是所有的行人对公路有使用权
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.36,0:08:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.46,0:08:56.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大声嚷嚷 只会令我头昏脑胀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.56,0:09:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得承认
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.56,0:09:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些画太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.96,0:09:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴力虽暴力 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.06,0:09:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.66,0:09:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个角色  他叫什么  黑夜?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.76,0:09:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全名就是黑夜?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.66,0:09:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不易记
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.96,0:09:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑夜人怎么样?或者...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.96,0:09:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.06,0:09:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面加个"骑士"
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.96,0:09:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫"骑士"
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.16,0:09:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.96,0:09:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.56,0:09:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.66,0:09:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是问问题 Jon
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.26,0:09:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们该如何一起努力工作吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.26,0:09:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起工作?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.36,0:09:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是天才 你是吸血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.16,0:09:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.66,0:10:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.16,0:10:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算工作一整晚?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.46,0:10:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快截稿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.86,0:10:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.06,0:10:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么弱小的身体怎么能装得下那么多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.06,0:10:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去买点牛肉干吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.26,0:10:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都半夜了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.76,0:10:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想大半夜跑出去买牛肉干?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.86,0:10:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烧烤牛肉干
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.56,0:10:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.96,0:10:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能快点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.46,0:10:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的 能不能快点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.06,0:10:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓如果5分钟内不能到...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.76,0:10:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.46,0:10:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生大事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.06,0:10:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 肯定是大事 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.96,0:10:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早该听我的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.46,0:10:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不会省多少时间 Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.96,0:10:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.66,0:10:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,405与101高速公路交叉口
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.16,0:10:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直被认为是全世界 交通状况最差的交叉口
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.26,0:10:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.56,0:11:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政府报告
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.16,0:11:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎样?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.66,0:11:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为政府工作
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.56,0:11:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不读报告?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.66,0:11:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么要关心离家2500英里远的 城市交通状况?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.86,0:11:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2295 英里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.16,0:11:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要逼我当众揍你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.16,0:11:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Grady  洛杉矶警局的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.36,0:11:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Derek Morgan  Reid博士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.46,0:11:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人在后边那辆SUV上 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.16,0:11:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 交通阻塞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.06,0:11:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚又发现2名受害者?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.66,0:11:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约凌晨3:30被大厦清洁工发现
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.66,0:11:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以过去2个星期发现7名受害人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.06,0:11:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸体发现在小巷中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.16,0:11:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.06,0:11:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同样的受害者特征?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.16,0:11:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前还没确定死者身份
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.36,0:11:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是衣服吻合
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.36,0:11:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为是同一人所干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.56,0:11:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀戳的程度
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.66,0:11:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗示嫌疑犯精神崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.56,0:11:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是多名有精神问题的嫌疑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.86,0:11:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又在几乎同一地点作案
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.26,0:11:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这极度不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.46,0:11:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 极有可能是同一人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.26,0:12:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该下午1点到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.16,0:12:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在1:11
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.56,0:12:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚和他的经纪人通过话 路上塞车
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.56,0:12:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许早点出发就不会了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.96,0:12:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要不要打给经纪人质问他?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.86,0:12:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说说而已 该怎样就怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.66,0:12:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能是警察办案的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.86,0:12:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,广播漫天播报
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.96,0:12:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚附近有几桩命案
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.96,0:12:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几桩命案? 不止一桩?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.36,0:12:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两具尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.06,0:12:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重案组的人一整晚都在这儿 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.66,0:12:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重案组的可只办大案
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.76,0:12:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果Johnny McHale不出现 我发誓 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.76,0:12:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会后悔失去我这名大客户
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.06,0:12:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在就可以走 Milo
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.26,0:12:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑 你能上哪去 英雄的世界?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.56,0:12:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从来就没出过什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.16,0:12:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它总是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.26,0:12:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独一无二的...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.86,0:12:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny Mchale
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.56,0:12:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.36,0:12:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny 我爱Blue 看这边...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.26,0:12:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.96,0:12:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.26,0:12:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.06,0:13:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bobby 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.86,0:13:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也叫亲临现场?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.96,0:13:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Milo 说真的 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.06,0:13:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英雄世界的人恨我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.46,0:13:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.76,0:13:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.46,0:13:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.06,0:13:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.66,0:13:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Vickie
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.76,0:13:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不能接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.96,0:13:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我正在外面享受我的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.26,0:13:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到哔后留言
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.46,0:13:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie 给我打电话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.36,0:13:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回我电话 我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.96,0:13:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.26,0:14:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.16,0:14:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他直接冲上来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.16,0:14:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也不能做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.46,0:14:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 你能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.16,0:14:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好吗? 我能帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.46,0:14:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能站起来 你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.26,0:14:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.26,0:14:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.36,0:14:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.86,0:14:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.16,0:14:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jasper 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.66,0:14:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jasper  天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.56,0:14:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jasper 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.06,0:14:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这狗杂种 这是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.56,0:14:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你直冲冲地撞上来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.46,0:14:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.66,0:14:56.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的 你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.76,0:14:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jasper 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.46,0:14:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是我们要找的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.56,0:15:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相同的受害者特征
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.96,0:15:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.46,0:15:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙残忍至极
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:11.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  如果在普通社区里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.86,0:15:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放任一只家猫肆意妄为
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.26,0:15:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当于造成一场小规模的生态灾难
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.86,0:15:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.56,0:15:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们见谁杀谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.96,0:15:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昆虫 老鼠 鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.06,0:15:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他猫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.36,0:15:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至小狗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.76,0:15:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与此有何相关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.96,0:15:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神崩溃的嫌疑犯是最危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.66,0:15:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你直冲冲地撞上来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.26,0:15:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.86,0:15:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.56,0:15:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞎了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.16,0:15:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.66,0:15:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是犯罪现场 傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.16,0:15:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绕路走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.66,0:16:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.66,0:16:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你伤到自已了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.46,0:16:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么弄的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.76,0:16:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我摔跤了 我一直在跑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.56,0:16:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们死了?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.96,0:16:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.96,0:16:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.16,0:16:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫David Rossi 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.86,0:16:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.66,0:16:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jon Mchale
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.26,0:16:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住这附近?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.16,0:16:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.66,0:16:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.86,0:16:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.96,0:16:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得离开这
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.26,0:16:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 车在这边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.46,0:16:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.06,0:16:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想她生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.46,0:16:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.26,0:16:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不回电话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.06,0:16:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天留一大堆的言
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.46,0:17:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁? Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.36,0:17:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.16,0:17:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得向她道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.96,0:17:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好休息 Johnny
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.96,0:17:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.66,0:17:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Vickie
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.66,0:17:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不能接电话 因为我在外面享受生活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.43,0:17:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢牛肉干
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.67,0:17:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比任何人都喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.07,0:17:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.57,0:17:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能用喜欢这个词
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.77,0:17:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母亲也很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.77,0:17:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是遗传
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.77,0:17:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信这事也能遗传
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.07,0:17:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是环境因素
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.97,0:17:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想孩子会不会喜欢牛肉干
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.57,0:17:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.87,0:17:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天下午确定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.37,0:17:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我早有感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.97,0:17:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.87,0:17:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是男孩 就叫Jonny 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.27,0:17:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与他父亲一样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.07,0:18:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.57,0:18:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识一名...不错的心理医生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.17,0:18:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对我很有帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.57,0:18:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.77,0:18:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.47,0:18:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以帮你预约
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.17,0:18:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.97,0:18:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.47,0:18:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以改天去漫画店?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.77,0:18:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.97,0:18:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny  他们是你的粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.47,0:18:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 这跟你无关了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.67,0:18:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被炒了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.57,0:18:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.27,0:18:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.27,0:18:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你需要我帮你打理这些新书
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.77,0:18:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.37,0:18:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.37,0:19:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.67,0:19:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Vickie 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.87,0:19:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不能接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.97,0:19:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在外面享受生活
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.17,0:19:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到哔后留言
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.77,0:19:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.67,0:20:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我回家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.34,0:20:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一地区差不多是犯罪现场的地理中心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.76,0:20:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探长Brady正在组织搜寻队
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.33,0:20:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细搜查附近的3个街区
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.93,0:20:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道有多少居民?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.47,0:20:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia估计有 3000
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.20,0:20:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分都是单身公寓
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.89,0:20:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,租借频繁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.03,0:20:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暂住人口多 没有纪录可言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.64,0:20:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记者招待会顺利结束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.64,0:20:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想媒体知道我们的意图
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.96,0:20:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是当地居民了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.78,0:20:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能够缩小嫌疑犯名单
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.60,0:22:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天噢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.58,0:22:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想孩子会不会喜欢牛肉干
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.58,0:22:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.42,0:22:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么时候发现的 -下午确定的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.89,0:22:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我早有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.87,0:22:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是男孩 叫Jonny  与他父亲一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.34,0:22:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.17,0:23:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.08,0:23:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天噢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.45,0:23:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我保证明早第一件事 便是去买一枚超大的戒指
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.71,0:23:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny 你不用这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.00,0:23:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie Wright  你愿意嫁给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.07,0:23:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Vickie? -Jonny 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.10,0:23:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.08,0:23:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.02,0:23:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.45,0:24:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同类型受害者?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.81,0:24:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是帮派人员
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.94,0:24:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我说 杀得好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.46,0:24:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.78,0:24:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Benson  反黑组的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.29,0:24:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人因暴力致死...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.59,0:24:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现场是什么样的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.49,0:24:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  那是黑帮头子的私人住宅
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.08,0:24:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫Glen Hill
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.58,0:24:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俗称Reaper
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.91,0:24:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜为何
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.81,0:24:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有Benson与我进去过
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.65,0:24:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一看到状况  我就出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.59,0:24:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.56,0:24:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6人   4人在里面   2人在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.98,0:24:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无一幸免?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.19,0:24:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到有一天我也会为这些黑帮份子伤心
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.92,0:24:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几分钟后赶到
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.06,0:24:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跑到黑帮的地盘
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.14,0:24:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人都死于街头巷尾
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.94,0:24:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能嫌疑犯试着保护自已
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.77,0:24:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是Bernie Goetz携枪坐地铁  就等人和他扛上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.60,0:24:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了是他在挑人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.09,0:24:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为精神病患者病情慢慢恶化
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.12,0:24:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟早会变成周围人的威胁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.61,0:25:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 停
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.53,0:25:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.05,0:25:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.08,0:25:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny? 你吓到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.43,0:25:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要什么 甜心
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.20,0:25:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你伤到自已了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.67,0:25:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- Vickie去哪了 - 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.17,0:25:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚在逃生梯
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.59,0:25:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -Vickie  我未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.03,0:25:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有未婚妻?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.90,0:25:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她刚在逃生梯
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.73,0:25:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么时候 -我进来之前
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.07,0:25:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是Caesar在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.52,0:25:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见她进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.98,0:25:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny  没人进来
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.22,0:25:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别骗我  -我没骗你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.66,0:25:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她在哪 -不
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.76,0:26:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-T.S.K?  -23街杀手
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.09,0:26:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来他们试图反击
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.78,0:26:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.61,0:26:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定这不是黑帮仇杀之类的?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.33,0:26:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是反黑组的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.70,0:26:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾看过有人这么做?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.97,0:26:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是... 一个人?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.08,0:26:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 单枪匹马 又有精神病... 结果可想而知了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.23,0:26:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看学校或者工作地点的枪击案就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.83,0:26:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-现在做什么 -我们已经在做了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.93,0:26:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明嫌疑犯情绪异常愤怒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.16,0:26:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jareau探员让媒体播放了新闻发布会的内容
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.69,0:26:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她向大众公布罪犯侧写 
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.10,0:26:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人生活圈中肯定有人知道他出问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.32,0:26:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望他们能根据这些描述意识到
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.27,0:26:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 看看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.94,0:27:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婊子 我知道她来过 我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.88,0:27:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.39,0:27:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不 -洛杉矶警局热线 
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.48,0:27:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 先生
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.68,0:27:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.04,0:27:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接到个电话有  说这是上帝的复仇
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.98,0:27:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 也许能帮上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.02,0:27:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛杉矶警局热线 
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.14,0:27:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jareau探员?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.25,0:27:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得和这人谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.19,0:27:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士 请等等
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.03,0:27:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们看到你的新闻发布会
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.56,0:27:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探长 3号线
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.11,0:27:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.53,0:28:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.80,0:28:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.87,0:29:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也没做 你们搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.51,0:29:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会水落石出
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.11,0:29:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是画画而已 我是美术家
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.69,0:29:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人Bobby  我炒了他 也许他只是生气
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.86,0:29:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没有生你的气
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.61,0:29:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么他说我做了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.26,0:29:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是为此而来 对吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.04,0:30:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你记得我对你宣读过权利是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.53,0:30:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny 看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.59,0:30:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.78,0:30:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白律师没来前你不必说一句话
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.20,0:30:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要律师
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.15,0:30:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-告诉我你明白  -我明白 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.91,0:30:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快有人进来和你说话
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.34,0:30:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有误会
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.73,0:30:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也没做
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.16,0:30:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很多  -还有更多
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.04,0:30:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到凶器了?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.64,0:30:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.95,0:30:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.95,0:30:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Mchale先生病得不轻 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.58,0:30:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这不就是… -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.11,0:30:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能去拿Glen Hill的面部照片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.17,0:30:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 等会
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.25,0:30:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这全来自Johnny的工作室  -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.76,0:30:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.64,0:30:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是有病
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.42,0:31:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里是正确的  Kim先生
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.92,0:31:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说今天前已有好几个月没见他
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.90,0:31:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.77,0:31:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很忙...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.68,0:31:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没理由..  你知道的 去那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.18,0:31:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickey Wright  能嫁给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.82,0:31:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Glen Hill 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.84,0:31:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.38,0:31:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我知道他在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.95,0:31:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6个月前他和他的同伙 伤害了你与你女朋友 对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.75,0:31:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.05,0:31:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们在街上袭击了你们 -没有
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.79,0:31:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出院后你一个也辨认不出
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.45,0:32:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太疯狂了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.35,0:32:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.95,0:32:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的椅子怎么也调不好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.93,0:32:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是...除此以外 我感到很丢脸  -丢脸?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.55,0:32:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我不明疑犯不是Jonny Mchale
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.55,0:32:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别告诉你是这家伙的粉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.04,0:32:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.49,0:32:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他是天才 -甜心
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.93,0:32:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该看看他是如何杀人的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.57,0:32:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时对一名艺术家来说 疯狂与天才的区别就是成功
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.51,0:32:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你患有创伤后精神崩溃症
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.89,0:32:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神病?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.02,0:32:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好几个星期了  -得了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.87,0:32:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能你自已也没意识
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.71,0:32:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.55,0:32:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是我的作品 -我们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.90,0:33:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是2天前的犯罪现场
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.28,0:33:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.60,0:33:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天 我和你谈过话
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.80,0:33:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有你的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.59,0:33:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 这是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.88,0:33:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是23号街的凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.21,0:33:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Glen Hill的黑帮
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.87,0:33:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚有6名黑帮份子在这房子里被杀 
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.17,0:33:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被捕时  这些东西还粘在画板上
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.48,0:33:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.22,0:33:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没道理 -这房子是Glen Hill的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.43,0:33:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有拖拽的血迹一直延伸到后门
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.94,0:33:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信你离开时带走了Hill先生
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.80,0:33:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他的电话?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.35,0:33:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓他时电话掉在地上
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.58,0:33:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打的都是同一个号码
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.22,0:33:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拨拨看 也许能帮上忙
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.99,0:33:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少能帮上他
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.85,0:33:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Vickie
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.85,0:34:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现不能接电话 因为我在外面享受生活
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.48,0:34:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到哔后留言
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.18,0:34:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.52,0:34:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie是他女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.08,0:34:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是2天前打的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.05,0:34:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时不明嫌疑犯做的还真是有理可寻
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.51,0:34:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些只是画...我的想像
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.45,0:34:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严重的创伤后精神崩溃症 是有可能对受害者施暴造成犯罪的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.44,0:34:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-受害者? -你流血了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.37,0:34:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是枪伤
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.41,0:34:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们昨晚对你开枪了? -住嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.75,0:34:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是受害人   我一定会知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.21,0:34:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得你进过医院?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.46,0:34:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我从没有… -这是你的医疗纪录
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.50,0:34:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们给你开刀了  Mchale先生
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.49,0:34:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你几乎被开膛剖腹了 
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.73,0:34:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说你能活着是奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.73,0:34:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹?  你认为活着是奇迹?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.53,0:34:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所有的画都是真实犯罪现场的反映  只除了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.03,0:34:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个犯罪现场在哪儿 Jonny?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.85,0:35:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是Glen Hill?  -他在哪 Glen Hill在哪?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.04,0:35:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.02,0:35:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道那里有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.67,0:35:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人懂得夜
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.43,0:35:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想伤害你  Jonny
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.60,0:35:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事了 孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.08,0:35:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我救不了她
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.65,0:35:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny  你不需要...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.68,0:35:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie Wright  你能嫁给我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.52,0:35:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Vickie?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.50,0:35:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.29,0:35:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答他 这人问你问题呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.99,0:35:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想惹麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.09,0:35:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不想不重要
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.71,0:35:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我有一点钱 不多...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.85,0:35:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-回答他 -是的 我愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.44,0:35:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  Vickie  没事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.93,0:35:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟 你拥有的比你想像的要多
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.60,0:35:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有未婚妻
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.39,0:35:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -不 Jonny
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.98,0:35:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放开我  - Jonny
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.08,0:35:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.48,0:35:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要错过这个
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.18,0:36:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们逼我看
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.73,0:36:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能为你求情
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.13,0:36:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你告诉我Glen Hill在哪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.70,0:36:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们逼我看 -我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.90,0:36:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.81,0:36:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你病了 你不知道在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.01,0:36:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Glen Hill在哪里 Jonny?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.12,0:36:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要错过这个
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.70,0:37:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放那 等我回来
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.61,0:37:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.49,0:37:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心我回来后打你
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.92,0:37:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别听他的 Garcia 他光说不做
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.34,0:37:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,J.J.他打我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.15,0:37:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要乖 小心我将你俩禁足
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.07,0:37:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是Jonny Mchale的漫画吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.38,0:38:01.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 名字叫Blue
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.65,0:38:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讲的是一个女孩认为她是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.47,0:38:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却发现她只是他叔叔造的机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.44,0:38:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像匹诺曹
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.82,0:38:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 像匹诺曹
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.16,0:38:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过背景是外太空的一所高中
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.22,0:38:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对了  Vickie的电话怎么处理 -电话?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.99,0:38:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是有她留言  Jonny一直打的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.58,0:38:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个都给他了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.95,0:38:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能想像对一个人的回忆只有一通留言 (伤感)
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.03,0:38:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他会一直听下去
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.32,0:38:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 很惨
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.98,0:38:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道Carlo Lorenzini吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.52,0:38:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写匹诺曹的那人 据说迷恋人的鼻子
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.37,0:38:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-事实上 -哇
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.41,0:38:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-匹诺曹甚至不是他最初写的角色 -有趣 咖啡?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.11,0:38:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.36,0:38:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.67,0:38:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我第一个接触不是坏蛋的不明疑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.06,0:38:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.83,0:38:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6个月前
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.58,0:39:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jonny Mchale只是个普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.26,0:39:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一名不明嫌疑犯都是某种程度上的病态
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.41,0:39:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数和Jonny一样  控制不了自已的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.89,0:39:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在6个月里
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.32,0:39:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从一名成功的作家与画家 变成残忍的凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.77,0:39:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他经历了悲惨的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.58,0:39:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.96,0:39:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.82,0:39:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在想...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.62,0:39:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是都可能变成那样的人?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.31,0:39:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命无常  世事难料
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.24,0:39:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.69,0:39:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人 闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.81,0:39:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自已能行 只是不能抓东西太紧 
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.19,0:39:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试着这样做 它不停地掉下来
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.46,0:39:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能闭上你的机关枪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.24,0:40:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这样就好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.46,0:40:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-真的?  -太完美了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.04,0:40:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我的宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.08,0:40:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.44,0:40:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是谁的英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.76,0:40:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道Frank Miller是谁吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.66,0:40:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Frank Miller...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.80,0:40:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-耳熟 嫌疑犯? -不是
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.99,0:40:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漫画作家  300? 罪恶之城?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.97,0:40:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 电影很酷
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.15,0:40:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.88,0:40:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说过一些话 让我想起了你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.54,0:40:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑色英雄即是一名身穿带血盔甲的骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.83,0:40:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他脏兮兮的 
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.79,0:40:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却极力否认他就是一名英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.42,0:41:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 我是Vickie 
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.22,0:41:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现不能接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.59,0:41:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我正在外面享受生活
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.96,0:41:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到哔后...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.51,0:41:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(TO tentoes309: 不哭…向前走)
