[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HF0000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.96,0:00:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个地下室
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.86,0:00:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.06,0:00:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.86,0:00:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定是他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.76,0:00:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然还会是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.26,0:00:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想确认一下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.66,0:00:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.66,0:01:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最多6岁  太遗憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.76,0:01:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那儿有动静
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.66,0:01:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿怎么会有个婴儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ不会带她的宝宝来犯罪现场
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.26,0:01:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.26,0:01:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.56,0:01:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.86,0:01:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我做了个梦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.06,0:01:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.66,0:01:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们发现了一个6岁的受虐男孩被刺死身亡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.46,0:01:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的宝宝也出现在了犯罪现场
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.66,0:01:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把他带出去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.86,0:01:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.46,0:01:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.36,0:01:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid  根据简单的梦境分析
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.76,0:01:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你梦中出现的婴儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.76,0:01:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实就是你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.16,0:01:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信解梦那一套
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.46,0:01:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道   这还是有道理的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.56,0:01:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们手头这起案件和你的梦都和孩子有关
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.56,0:01:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你潜意识里不想插手这起案件
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.46,0:01:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.36,0:01:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许只是因为回到拉斯维加斯的家 你感到紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.46,0:01:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟你妈妈说你要回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.96,0:01:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我们不回顾整理案件资料
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.96,0:01:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.96,0:01:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是因为有人在飞机上睡着了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.26,0:02:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再从头开始
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.06,0:02:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Ethan Hayes  5岁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.16,0:02:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两周前在自家前院里被绑走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.76,0:02:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时父母在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.86,0:02:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她妈妈刚进屋拿钱包
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.56,0:02:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她出来时  孩子就不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.76,0:02:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前后不到两分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.06,0:02:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一周后  警察在沙漠中发现了他的尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.36,0:02:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身上的衣服换了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.16,0:02:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指甲剪得干干净净
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发梳得整整齐齐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.16,0:02:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不明疑犯后悔的表现
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.36,0:02:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有被性侵犯的迹象
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.36,0:02:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸检结果显示  他是窒息而死
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.96,0:02:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明疑犯将死亡视为一种仁慈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.16,0:02:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的被绑架小孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.36,0:02:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Michael Bridges
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.06,0:02:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天他独自步行去一个街区以外的朋友家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.36,0:02:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.36,0:02:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定这几起案件之间有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.16,0:02:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明疑犯给每个受害家庭都打了电话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.96,0:02:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却都没有索要赎金
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.76,0:02:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更像是奚落的语气
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.46,0:02:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说孩子出事都是家长的错
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.56,0:02:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来  这名不明疑犯有懊悔的表现
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.46,0:02:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并把自己的犯罪行为归咎于受害者的家长
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.76,0:02:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们运气好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.76,0:02:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在受害者被杀之前  我们有6天的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amos Bronson Alcott说过 (美国作家)
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.92,0:04:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与本能对话  
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.82,0:04:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即与最深层面的人性对话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.42,0:04:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能听见内心最深处的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.12,0:04:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ashby警探
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.32,0:04:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Jennifer Jareau 这是Aaron Hotchner
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.22,0:04:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-感谢这么快赶来 -早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.72,0:04:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么情况
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.42,0:04:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经发布安珀警戒 (失踪儿童警报系统)
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.02,0:04:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辖区里人们议论纷纷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.32,0:04:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打电话要了他的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.02,0:04:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电信公司给用户寄过话费传票吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  如果他使用的是陆上电信线路 就可以查到姓名和地址
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.52,0:04:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也会让总部的技术员查找电话的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.52,0:04:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可以对手机进行三角定位
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.92,0:04:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这儿的政府车辆清走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.12,0:04:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万一不明疑犯恰好开车经过 我不想引起他的恐慌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.02,0:04:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  介绍完后我就让他们离开
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.32,0:04:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们情况如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.52,0:04:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分头行动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.92,0:04:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Craig Amy Bridges 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.52,0:04:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是FBI的Jareau和Hotchner探员
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.92,0:04:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你们的遭遇  我们深表同情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.92,0:05:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我们会尽全力寻找Michael 带他平安回家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.22,0:05:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把对警察说的再对你们说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.22,0:05:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道其他孩子遭遇了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.02,0:05:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想听你说  如何找到Michael
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.42,0:05:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.12,0:05:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.62,0:05:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.32,0:05:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你究竟遭遇了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.92,0:05:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道如何破案
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.72,0:05:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要你们的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.02,0:05:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.82,0:05:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Michael一个人去朋友家  这正常吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.72,0:05:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.62,0:05:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是问问
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.72,0:05:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不正常
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.92,0:05:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为我们与此有关吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.72,0:05:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.52,0:05:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他经常这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.52,0:05:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有人之前已经观察过他了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.82,0:05:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只有过几次
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.32,0:05:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amy和我还为此吵过架
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.82,0:05:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得太纵容孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.12,0:05:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想他再爬上我们的床
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.52,0:05:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他应该能够自己一个人去朋友家玩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.42,0:05:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次这么做的时候  他真的很自豪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.22,0:05:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.92,0:05:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她无法面对事实
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.32,0:06:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 每人遇事的处理方法不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.22,0:06:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道其他孩子的遭遇
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.62,0:06:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死者颈部和脸部均无瘀伤
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.72,0:06:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计他用了枕头
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.02,0:06:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有反抗挣扎的痕迹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.22,0:06:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  不过他一定非常虚弱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.62,0:06:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.62,0:06:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪就怪在这儿  他很瘦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.72,0:06:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胃肠里空无一物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.42,0:06:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他挨饿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.72,0:06:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪之处在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.12,0:06:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想确定  营养不良是否是他的死因之一
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.82,0:06:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我查找饥饿性酮病的迹象
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.22,0:06:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我分析了眼部的玻璃状液
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.02,0:06:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没有发现酮体  (脂肪酸代谢的中间产物  饥饿时酮体在血液中含量增加)
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.12,0:06:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他仍以某种方式获取营养
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.12,0:06:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静脉注射?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.82,0:06:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有针眼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.32,0:06:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他可能性吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.52,0:06:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.62,0:06:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.02,0:06:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现场保持得不好 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.22,0:06:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是案发现场调查员造成的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.02,0:06:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都想扮警察  而非科学家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.02,0:06:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这儿踩了个遍
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.12,0:07:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在别处闷死了男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.92,0:07:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,处理尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.22,0:07:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在荒郊野外弃尸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.12,0:07:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸体的衣服上没有一丝不明疑犯的汗迹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.52,0:07:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.32,0:07:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这儿气温这么高
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.32,0:07:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他搬运尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.52,0:07:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服上应该会有汗迹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.22,0:07:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他把尸体包起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.82,0:07:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没发现纤维
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.12,0:07:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他一到这儿  就抓紧时间换下男孩的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.02,0:07:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他打扮了一番
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.32,0:07:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要用这么多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.12,0:07:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他必须在夜里行动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.92,0:07:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是还是有风险  一旦尸体被发现 可能有人记得他的车
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.02,0:07:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在路边停车就没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.12,0:07:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一有人发现车和自己的行踪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.82,0:07:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会把车停在远离弃尸地的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.12,0:07:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.22,0:07:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能开车去沙漠弃尸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.72,0:07:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不干脆再开远点  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.02,0:07:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开到远离公路  无人发现的地方去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.32,0:07:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他还想再到这儿来 看看尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.32,0:07:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他把受害者打扮一番
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.22,0:08:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像他为他准备葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.82,0:08:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.02,0:08:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.32,0:08:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.32,0:08:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侦探
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.62,0:08:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天为第一位受害者举行葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.02,0:08:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是否方便问问受害者家属 他们愿意公开葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.92,0:08:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.52,0:08:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果葬礼公开的话 不明疑犯有可能出现
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.02,0:08:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去和他们说说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.02,0:08:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Craig  希望你和你妻子也能去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.82,0:08:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.82,0:08:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是对Amy说说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.32,0:08:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-如果这有用的话  不需要商量 -我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.42,0:08:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 还是和她商量商量吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.02,0:08:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察来要Michael的照片时 我不知道该给他们哪张
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.82,0:08:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该不该拿他微笑的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.52,0:08:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的决定都是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.62,0:09:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫慌得不知所措
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.42,0:09:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得我们该出去找孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.52,0:09:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你最好的做法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.22,0:09:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是听从我们的指挥 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.22,0:09:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得我在怪他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.92,0:09:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.52,0:09:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是怪他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.32,0:09:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子被绑架了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.02,0:09:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全愣住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确责怪他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.22,0:09:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得自己是个恶人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.42,0:09:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们需要你时   
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.22,0:09:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会出现的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.42,0:09:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不了解我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.32,0:09:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.82,0:09:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被绑架后  我在他房里发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.32,0:09:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不准他在床上吃东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.62,0:09:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有扔掉它  
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.52,0:10:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.22,0:10:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想他因为不听话而难受
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩还是女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.72,0:10:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.42,0:10:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.32,0:10:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Gracia 准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.52,0:10:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.82,0:10:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Bridges先生  再重复一遍 -我儿子在他手上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.02,0:10:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.62,0:10:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持积极态度
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.02,0:10:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我写了些重要的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.72,0:10:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快接电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.92,0:10:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bridges先生  听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.02,0:10:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该让Amy接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.12,0:10:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不想接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.42,0:10:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我不想接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.62,0:10:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据经验   家长越冷静越好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.82,0:10:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Amy  你能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.22,0:10:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把握机会人性化Michael
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.52,0:10:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他需要得到尊重
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.22,0:10:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量延长通话时间
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.02,0:10:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通话时间越长  暴露的信息越多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.92,0:11:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.72,0:11:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.52,0:11:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我丈夫在旁边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.42,0:11:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么静静待在家中
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.82,0:11:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们该出去找孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.12,0:11:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.42,0:11:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该出去找
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.72,0:11:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和我在一起更好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.02,0:11:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你打来电话   告诉我们Michael一切都好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.32,0:11:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说他一切都好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.72,0:11:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是相信 他没事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.32,0:11:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在在一个更好的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.62,0:11:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能和Michael说几句吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.72,0:11:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不想和你说话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.52,0:11:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他知道你是个坏妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.72,0:11:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3分钟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.52,0:11:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  有发现吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.62,0:11:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个即用即抛手机
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.32,0:11:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法三角定位
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.52,0:11:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过信号来自两个发射塔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.02,0:11:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么意思 -他在移动
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.12,0:11:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还在拉斯维加斯  没有去其他城市
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.72,0:12:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是开始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.12,0:12:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过  他说的越多  我们越了解他
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.02,0:12:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是Morgan探员和Reid探员
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.02,0:12:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们晚上留在这儿  以防他再打来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.82,0:12:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去躺会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.42,0:12:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.02,0:12:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该陪着她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.02,0:12:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.72,0:12:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸检有什么结果
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.82,0:12:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认为他不给孩子食物
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.72,0:12:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他对尸体却非常细心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.12,0:12:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挨饿是虐待的一种
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.92,0:12:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有性侵犯的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.32,0:12:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能用这种虐待方式代替性侵犯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.52,0:12:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和Rossi和Prentiss联系一下 有消息通知我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.72,0:13:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没发现强行闯入的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.22,0:13:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很重要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.22,0:13:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这说明他可能认识袭击者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.92,0:13:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.12,0:13:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄掉  Morgan  快弄掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.32,0:13:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄掉  Morgan  快帮我弄掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.82,0:13:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快帮我弄掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.12,0:13:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan  快帮我弄掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.82,0:13:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid  醒醒  我是Morgan
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.42,0:13:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.52,0:13:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  没事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.12,0:13:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都被吵醒了  这还没事?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.42,0:13:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道吓到你们了 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.52,0:13:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.02,0:13:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.32,0:13:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.32,0:13:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生 请上楼去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.12,0:13:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去好好休息
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.52,0:14:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一场误会而已   一切正常  我保证
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.92,0:14:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.82,0:14:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了个梦  很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.42,0:14:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦到Michael了?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.12,0:14:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.02,0:14:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕闭上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.42,0:14:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕会看到他死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.92,0:14:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.02,0:14:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这很难受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.12,0:14:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你得回去好好休息
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.12,0:14:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.32,0:14:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉打扰你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.22,0:14:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把事情越搞越糟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.62,0:14:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.62,0:14:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都受这些案子的影响
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.72,0:15:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在他们客厅失控了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.92,0:15:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.52,0:15:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦到死去的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.62,0:15:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我浑身都是水蛭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.42,0:15:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怕什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.92,0:15:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只能眼睁睁看着孩子丧命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.70,0:15:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.40,0:15:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.80,0:15:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.80,0:15:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不去葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.10,0:15:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.10,0:15:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你说  我听而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.90,0:15:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请告诉她  这是我们唯一的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.40,0:15:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划可行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.30,0:16:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我们参加一个5岁男孩的葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.40,0:16:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睁睁看着他被泥土吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.10,0:16:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而杀害他的人绑架了我们的儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.20,0:16:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果绑架Michael的人就在葬礼上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.80,0:16:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的出现会让他大吃一惊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.70,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想尽一切办法引他出现
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.70,0:16:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能看着一个孩子被埋葬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.60,0:16:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们的儿子就是下一个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.90,0:16:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认为这个计划成功的可能性很大
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.70,0:16:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们觉得我再次见到儿子的可能性有多大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.40,0:16:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10%?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.30,0:16:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,20%?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.50,0:16:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法给你数字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.60,0:16:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你实在去不了  我也能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.80,0:16:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过如果你能去  我们可以谈谈要找的人  
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.60,0:16:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信  要找的是个白种人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.50,0:16:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约二三十岁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.50,0:16:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过分析他为第一位受害者换上的衣服质量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.50,0:16:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信 他来自中产阶级
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.80,0:16:49.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在葬礼上不会衣着笔挺
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.20,0:16:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能密切关注最近孩子遭绑架的家长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.40,0:16:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加关注这些家长
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.20,0:16:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而非葬礼本身
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.40,0:17:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他或许驾驶汽车
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.50,0:17:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这类哀悼者格外注意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.60,0:17:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记下所有车牌号
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.10,0:17:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明疑犯最后一次的弃尸点远离城市
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.00,0:17:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他并不打算隐藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.00,0:17:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  在路上就能看到弃尸点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.10,0:17:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这说明他试图将自己的行为 和个人本身区别开来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.30,0:17:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还能再开车去看看尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.90,0:17:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是懊悔表现
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我们相信他今天很可能出现
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.20,0:17:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.80,0:17:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你觉得谁在看你  一定告诉我们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.90,0:17:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能感受到恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.10,0:17:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脖子后面一撮头发
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.40,0:17:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会告诉我们真相
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.70,0:17:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ留在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.90,0:17:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是电话响了  她会自称你们的朋友 告诉对方你们去葬礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.40,0:17:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.20,0:17:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  小子  我们准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.40,0:18:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.90,0:18:04.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们抓到不明疑犯时
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.20,0:18:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他正企图弃尸  或绑架另一个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.10,0:18:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这个可能性  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.20,0:18:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.30,0:18:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事情一直挥之不去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.10,0:18:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.10,0:18:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识的所有男孩都有很多恐龙玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.70,0:18:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.30,0:18:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有书和笔记本
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.20,0:18:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈在上面写满了Merwin Bob Dylan的诗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.70,0:18:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我背下了诗  她就很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.60,0:18:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她坚信他们看着我们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.30,0:18:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写下我们生活之歌
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.60,0:18:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地下室是修建房屋时最先开工的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.40,0:18:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你不断梦到地下室
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.60,0:18:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像与你内心深处对话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.90,0:18:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是不相信解梦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.80,0:18:49.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗洛伊德被质疑
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.80,0:18:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过荣格的理论仍有可取之处 (均为心理学家)
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.70,0:18:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我梦到死去的男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.10,0:18:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.70,0:19:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小开始就一直做这样的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.20,0:19:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.90,0:19:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你理清思路  没人会看轻你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.00,0:19:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想找到孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.50,0:19:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天很多人到场
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.60,0:19:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是悲伤的自然流露
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.90,0:19:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对逝去生命无比惋惜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.20,0:19:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也提醒我们 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.50,0:19:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有另一个孩子处境危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.40,0:19:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我们祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.90,0:19:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们为他而祈祷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.60,0:19:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿他平安归来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.50,0:20:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.20,0:20:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.40,0:20:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Spencer  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.00,0:20:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.10,0:20:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.40,0:20:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.00,0:20:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来过这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.90,0:20:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以圣父 圣子 圣灵之名 阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.90,0:20:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们借助马太福音  寻求安慰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.60,0:20:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十八章
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.60,0:21:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门徒前来 询问耶稣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.90,0:21:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天国之中 谁最伟大
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.80,0:21:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣叫来一孩童
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.70,0:21:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站立其中
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.90,0:21:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.10,0:21:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你们变为孩童
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.80,0:21:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们无法进入天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.30,0:21:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持谦卑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.30,0:21:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是这家人的朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.80,0:21:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.60,0:21:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在报上看到消息
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.90,0:21:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就决定来参加葬礼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.70,0:21:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  太悲伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.70,0:21:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让家属感到人们的关心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.80,0:21:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还拍下来 给谁看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.50,0:21:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.00,0:21:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻轻地  别打扰别人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.00,0:22:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Ethan Hayes和Michael Bridges 被绑架时你在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.40,0:22:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.60,0:22:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问都不问是哪一天吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被捕了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.10,0:22:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  你爱孩子  你只是协助我们调查
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.70,0:22:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们无权搜查我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.00,0:22:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  我们能搜出什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.60,0:22:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道除了葬礼之外 你还喜欢拍点别的?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.90,0:22:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.10,0:22:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.10,0:22:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们试图控制他
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.00,0:22:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.90,0:22:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们单独待一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.20,0:22:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.50,0:22:50.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让警探调出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.30,0:22:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说过Riley Jenkins吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.20,0:22:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.80,0:22:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再想想
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.80,0:22:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想你小时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.80,0:23:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候  我有个虚幻的朋友叫Riley
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.40,0:23:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Riley Jenkins
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.60,0:23:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6岁时  在拉斯维加斯被害
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.30,0:23:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算起来  当时你大概4岁
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.50,0:23:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他家地下室的烘干机后发现了尸体
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.50,0:23:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭虐待 被刺身亡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.60,0:23:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Michael Bridges在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.60,0:23:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想陷害我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.20,0:23:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了Ethan Hayes  
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.00,0:23:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又绑架了Michael Bridges
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.90,0:23:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没有 -那你为什么拍葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.70,0:23:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡让你兴奋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.10,0:23:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  慢着  我懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.80,0:23:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡让你有高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.60,0:23:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了  不是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.30,0:23:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是杀了他们  之后找到新方法看看他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.00,0:23:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又没病
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.00,0:23:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没病才怪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.90,0:23:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你迫不及待想告诉我们
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.80,0:23:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底有多病态  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.00,0:23:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我们搜查你电脑和你家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.90,0:24:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你满脑子都是懊悔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.10,0:24:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道该停止了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.30,0:24:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有猥亵那个男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.90,0:24:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个男孩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.50,0:24:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葬礼上那个
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.40,0:24:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotchner
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.50,0:24:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不知道谋杀的细节
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.10,0:24:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.90,0:24:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以为那孩子被性侵犯了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.60,0:24:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.60,0:24:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是凶手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.70,0:24:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.60,0:24:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说会有结果的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.60,0:24:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.10,0:24:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他在拍葬礼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.30,0:24:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们相信他是个潜在的的性侵犯者
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.70,0:24:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但Michael不在他手上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.70,0:25:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底还有多少这种人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.40,0:25:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多到你无法想象
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.40,0:25:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂 -让FBI接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.10,0:25:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.50,0:25:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在葬礼上看到他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.30,0:25:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们接电话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.30,0:25:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是Aaron Hotchner特别探员
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.90,0:25:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想耍我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.90,0:25:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想锁住我  可惜抓错了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.00,0:25:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们慢慢说
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.50,0:25:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有3分钟
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.50,0:26:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  说多久都行
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.60,0:26:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不合规则
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.60,0:26:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 听你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.20,0:26:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则你来定
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.10,0:26:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天不错  去了葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.10,0:26:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定非常关心Ethan
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.90,0:26:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱他  
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.90,0:26:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的父母不配拥有他
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.70,0:26:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他照顾的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.80,0:26:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你给他买新衣服?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.50,0:26:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们给他穿傻兮兮的蓝色运动鞋 和绿色牛津鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.50,0:26:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他根本不喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.90,0:26:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许你可以好心地帮Michael送回家
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.00,0:26:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以告诉他父母  他真正喜欢什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.60,0:26:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.70,0:26:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他永远不会再回家
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.10,0:26:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了那个所谓的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.00,0:26:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和我对视
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.70,0:26:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她知道他更喜欢和我一起睡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.10,0:26:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.20,0:26:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过求你把我的孩子还给我  求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.80,0:26:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我做什么都可以  求你别伤害我的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.60,0:26:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间到了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.48,0:27:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想耍我
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.08,0:27:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人耍你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.23,0:27:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想锁住我  可惜抓错了人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.13,0:27:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们单独工作一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.03,0:27:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就在葬礼上
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.03,0:27:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.03,0:27:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们抓错了人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.97,0:27:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们要找的不是男人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.07,0:27:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到她描述衣物的方式了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.67,0:27:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说蓝色鞋 
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.27,0:27:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色牛津鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.67,0:27:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性不会如此说起细节
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.37,0:27:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid说得没错
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.67,0:27:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说到孩子想要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.47,0:27:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何入睡 
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.47,0:27:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她如何照顾他
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.27,0:27:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说  "我爱他"
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.47,0:27:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性不明疑犯会着重与警方较量 而不是满口照顾孩子的事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.87,0:27:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会炫耀自己比FBI更聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.17,0:27:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声称永远不会被抓到
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.67,0:27:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以男女一起查
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.17,0:27:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,统计数字说明一切
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.47,0:27:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女性绑架新生儿
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.87,0:27:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性绑架儿童
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.97,0:27:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Gracia
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.77,0:27:51.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.17,0:27:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查查警察给你的车牌号 其中登记的有女性吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.87,0:27:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有…
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.67,0:27:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零个
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.57,0:27:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.57,0:28:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通话记录来看  她似乎进过某种机构
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.67,0:28:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说她是个疯子
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.57,0:28:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说过"锁住"
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.57,0:28:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是"逮捕"或"抓住"
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.67,0:28:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且大多数心理治疗机构 对每天通话时间有严格规定
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.77,0:28:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想她只通话3分钟 并不是对我们的规定
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.27,0:28:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是她在心理治疗机构养成的习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.87,0:28:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  查查上个月从心理治疗机构中 出来的女性资料
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.17,0:28:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的资料里很有可能记录了 她曾受到的严重心理创伤
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.77,0:28:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是丧子
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.77,0:28:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 查不了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.57,0:28:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护病人隐私
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.07,0:28:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中央数据库没有记录
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.57,0:28:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能挨个侵入医院的资料库
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.47,0:28:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是就算如此 大多数的诊断书由医生分别保存
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.77,0:28:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能有办法
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.17,0:28:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid博士
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.27,0:28:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈没说你回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.67,0:28:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不知道   我在办案
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.67,0:28:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想也许你能帮助我们
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.67,0:28:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.47,0:28:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道最近的谋杀孩子案和绑架案吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.97,0:28:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.77,0:28:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认为一名女性与此有关
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.37,0:29:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能进过心理治疗机构
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.87,0:29:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是几周前被释放了 就在第一起绑架案之前
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.07,0:29:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.97,0:29:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你和其他医院的主管有密切的工作关系
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.47,0:29:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道没人能拿到他们的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.97,0:29:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我想请你把这份侧写交给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.47,0:29:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我们是很大的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.97,0:29:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她患臆想症
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.07,0:29:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满怀悲伤  她的孩子可能在5岁左右时死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.77,0:29:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽力而为
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.07,0:29:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Spencer?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.47,0:29:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这儿做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.17,0:29:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公事
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.77,0:29:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调查5岁小孩遇害和遭绑架的案件
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.57,0:29:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢你这样的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.17,0:29:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此伤感的案件
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.27,0:29:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.47,0:29:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧你瘦得皮包骨头
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.67,0:29:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算一破案就来看你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.67,0:29:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.67,0:30:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.17,0:30:02.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对妈妈可别撒谎  Spencer
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.57,0:30:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知子莫若母
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.37,0:30:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都会感知事情
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.07,0:30:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想有人盯着你的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.37,0:30:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.67,0:30:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.47,0:30:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过  他就在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.17,0:30:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.17,0:30:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.97,0:30:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  中间的金发女子  看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.07,0:30:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.87,0:30:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分离图像  在数据库里查找    看能不能发现线索
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.47,0:30:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.37,0:30:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识一个叫Riley Jenkins的男孩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.67,0:30:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Riley Jenkins
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.17,0:30:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是你想象出来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.67,0:30:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他是个实实在在的人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.67,0:30:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4岁时遇害
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.77,0:31:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你是搞错了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.97,0:31:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都看到些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.07,0:31:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.97,0:31:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从小就不断梦到他死了 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.67,0:31:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你读了很多书
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.17,0:31:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日有所思  夜有所梦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.57,0:31:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得4岁时  
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.47,0:31:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去一个葬礼
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.77,0:31:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是你叔叔Danile的葬礼 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.97,0:31:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还记得我们搬家
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.47,0:31:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和爸爸还为此吵架
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.07,0:31:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对爸爸说  我很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.17,0:31:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确实很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.27,0:31:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.97,0:31:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道为什么  可我就是知道你有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.37,0:31:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.97,0:31:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是动物  Spencer
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.97,0:31:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们感知事情
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.07,0:31:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了  我和9家医院院长谈过了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.77,0:31:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人符合你的描述
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.87,0:31:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.87,0:31:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这个人精神状态极度混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.97,0:31:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是她是否按时服药 而非她是否被释放
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.57,0:31:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.67,0:31:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.47,0:31:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怀你之后  
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.97,0:32:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就停药了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.37,0:32:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终日惶惶  
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.77,0:32:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还是熬过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.37,0:32:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了你
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.37,0:32:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命变美好了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.47,0:32:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.07,0:32:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.67,0:32:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人绑架新生儿
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.77,0:32:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.97,0:32:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.27,0:32:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.47,0:32:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个女人有没有可能把一个5岁孩子 当作自己的新生儿
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.07,0:32:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她的精神严重混乱
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.77,0:32:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且有人停了她的药   当然有这个可能
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.97,0:32:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.57,0:32:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch 
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.17,0:32:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道为何尸检结果如此不可思议了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.07,0:32:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她用母乳喂养孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.57,0:32:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪就在这儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.27,0:32:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.27,0:32:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.17,0:32:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖睡
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.17,0:33:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪就在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.87,0:33:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖睡
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.77,0:33:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖睡
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.53,0:33:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,视频里的女人有线索了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.93,0:33:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经搜索  她叫Claire Bates
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.93,0:33:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3年前因袭击律师事务所一名秘书
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.83,0:33:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入心理治疗机构
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.53,0:33:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她咬掉了对方的半边耳朵
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.53,0:33:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查到地址了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.83,0:33:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有最近的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.03,0:33:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再试试车牌号
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.03,0:33:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.43,0:33:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  情况不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.63,0:33:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.53,0:33:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登记者是她父亲  他住在Reno
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.43,0:33:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是两年前去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.83,0:33:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  查她的生育记录
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.33,0:33:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她还能用母乳喂养
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.83,0:33:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定才生了孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.43,0:34:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.33,0:34:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Claire Bates3周前生下一名男婴
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.73,0:34:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.33,0:34:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.73,0:34:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过7天的评估 社会服务机构带走了她的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.33,0:34:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她要先留下孩子7天
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.53,0:34:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她重现痛失爱子的场景
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.03,0:34:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可她绑架的是5岁孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.33,0:34:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混乱的精神状态使她把能得到的孩子 误认为是自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.03,0:34:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Garcia  读读社会服务机构的评估报告
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.93,0:34:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然病人为了胎儿的健康
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.13,0:34:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停用精神治疗药物的行为值得令人钦佩
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.33,0:34:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们坚信  鉴于病人的暴力史和臆想症
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.53,0:34:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将她作为孩子的监护人  是非常危险的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.23,0:34:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此州政府将担任监护人职责
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.43,0:34:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到病人能完全行使监护权
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.53,0:34:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有地址吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.83,0:34:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Brookside街2509号
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.43,0:34:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ和你们待在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.53,0:34:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有消息马上通知你们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.23,0:34:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.33,0:35:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.23,0:35:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她真有臆想症
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.13,0:35:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会有片刻清醒  意识到自己的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.03,0:35:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Morgan和我从后面进去
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.13,0:35:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Prentiss和我从门进入
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.63,0:35:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Claire
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.33,0:35:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑 Claire
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.23,0:35:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跑向后门
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.63,0:35:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心  她手上有孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.83,0:35:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  我们看到她了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.33,0:36:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她朝车库跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.13,0:36:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Claire
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.03,0:36:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离火堆远点  把孩子放下来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.43,0:36:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子死了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.23,0:36:26.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他没死
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.43,0:36:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人很好的照顾他
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.43,0:36:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也要好好照顾这个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.83,0:36:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把他照顾的很好
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.63,0:36:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.53,0:36:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.93,0:36:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是要你离开火堆 
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.73,0:37:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把孩子放下
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.03,0:37:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的孩子死了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.93,0:37:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 他还活着  我们证明给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.03,0:37:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不射伤她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.93,0:37:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有武器 Rossi
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.23,0:37:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果孩子还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.63,0:37:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却被扔进火堆
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.13,0:37:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可能就救不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.83,0:37:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.03,0:37:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.03,0:37:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到Michael了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.83,0:37:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.83,0:37:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.73,0:38:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得接受医生检查
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.43,0:38:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你能陪着他
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.93,0:38:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚他就能回家睡觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.23,0:39:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.63,0:39:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会是个好妈妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.93,0:39:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.83,0:39:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真是不错
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.13,0:39:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.13,0:39:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在想那个孩子吗 你自己都不确定是否真见过他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.23,0:39:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4岁时  我母亲感到我有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.93,0:39:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.43,0:39:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈在心理治疗机构
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.53,0:39:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这案子的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.83,0:39:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Reid  你的记忆力惊人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.73,0:39:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是你读到的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.43,0:39:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个和你一样的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.53,0:39:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是引起了你的想象
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.63,0:39:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真这么想吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.43,0:39:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道我的真实想法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.53,0:39:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想  这世上的事  你无所不能 而你选择了这份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.33,0:40:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣格说过  潜意识是我们一生真正的追逐
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.93,0:40:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.83,0:40:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不管因为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.13,0:40:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多年来  那个案子一直在你脑海里挥之不去
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.03,0:40:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它不仅让你选择了这份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.43,0:40:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也带你来到这座你母亲居住的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.13,0:40:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我们有机会救下这个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.23,0:40:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.83,0:40:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过  今天真不错
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.53,0:40:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受此刻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.43,0:40:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hotch  我们能够明天再回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.43,0:40:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斯维加斯的晚上有什么乐子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.13,0:40:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Bob Dylan说过 (著名乡村歌手)
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.13,0:40:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中  真正自然的是梦境
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.43,0:40:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不受自然的腐蚀
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.33,0:41:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你自豪 Spencer
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.33,0:41:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.23,0:41:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救下那个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.53,0:41:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.73,0:41:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过  母亲的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.13,0:41:13.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Norman医生允许我 今晚睡在你屋的沙发上
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.53,0:41:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你同意的话
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.53,0:41:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人留他多住几天
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.73,0:41:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把你眼睛挖出来
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.03,0:41:25.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只准一晚
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.63,0:41:28.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们觉得你疯了 这很管用
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.63,0:41:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不和你争
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.03,0:43:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,FBI
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.73,0:43:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举起手来
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.23,0:43:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转过脸来
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.53,0:43:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸?
